<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="BaseExpect1">
			<DisplayName>Calming Down from Fright</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Multiple days on the run really leaves one exhausted, but it's better than being dead...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Escaping from that disaster was a stroke of luck</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BaseExpect2">
			<DisplayName>Far from Chaos</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Even though there's nothing here, but it's worlds better than the chaos outside.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing safe as it is far from that chaos</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BaseExpect3">
			<DisplayName>A New Life</DisplayName>
			<Desc>It seems like you've all grown to like this place. There's no war nor taxes, and although things are a bit difficult, but the situation is livable. Could this be a new beginning? Everyone is full of hope.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling not unusual to secretly hope for a new beginning</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect1">
			<DisplayName>Atrocious Housing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Is this place even fit for humans to live?</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that These kinds of conditions make tempers flare easily</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect2">
			<DisplayName>Frightening Housing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This environment is frightening to say the least. Sleeping out in the wilderness would probably be more comfortable.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling not difficult to complain about such living conditions</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect3">
			<DisplayName>Horrid Housing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>These conditions are basically only good for sheltering one from the wind and the rain.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling easy not to be happy when having to put up with such crude conditions</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect4">
			<DisplayName>A Typical Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This room is pretty standard in every way.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>thinking thatHow could this room be improved</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect5">
			<DisplayName>Better-than-average Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The room's not bad.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that This room is quite comfortable</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect6">
			<DisplayName>Exquisite Room.</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Whoever designed and arranged this room really put some thought into it.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that This room is really quite nice</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect7">
			<DisplayName>Resplendent Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>They really went all out with this room.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that This room is fantastic!</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect8">
			<DisplayName>Room Needed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I need a room!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling easy to be pissed when you don't even have a room to your name</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="IndependentRoomNeed">
			<DisplayName>Living with Outer Disciples</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The outer disciples are proving more of a distraction than anything else... I hope to move out of this living situation soon.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Living with the outer disciples is vexing</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LiveWithBadMan">
			<DisplayName>Awkward Cohabitation</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[TXT] and I really aren't even able to be conducting practice in the same room.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Engaging in practice in a room with someone that one isn't very familiar with is vexing</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomFengShuiExpect1">
			<DisplayName>Deficient Feng Shui</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The Feng shui where I live is no where near ideal.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Deficient Feng shui can really get on one's nerves</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomFengShuiExpect2">
			<DisplayName>Unlucky Domicile</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This place where I live is just not lucky, is it really all right to live here?</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that There's something wrong with the Feng shui here and it's setting everything off kilter</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomFengShuiExpect3">
			<DisplayName>Unlivable Domicile</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The Feng shui here is so bad that this room is unlivable.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that There's something so wrong with the Feng shui here that it makes anyway in the room upset</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomFengShuiExpect4">
			<DisplayName>Good Feng Shui</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The Feng shui in my room really isn't half bad.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Good Feng shui really lifts one's spirits</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomFengShuiExpect5">
			<DisplayName>Auspicious</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The Feng shui in my room is pretty great, whoever arranged this room really knew what they were doing.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that A room with great Feng shui is enjoyable by all</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect9">
			<DisplayName>Cramped Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Man, this room is so cramped!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that A cramped room can really get on one's nerves</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BedroomExpect10">
			<DisplayName>Barren Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This room is just desolate.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that A barren room needs to be fixed</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ClosedRoom">
			<DisplayName>Can't Get Out</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Where's the door!? I'm trapped!!!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Realizing that a room has no door causes one to bristle with anger</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ClothesExpect1">
			<DisplayName>Terrible Clothing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Do I really not have any clothing better than this? (Quality less than 30)</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling hard to be satisfied with such terrible clothing</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ClothesExpect2">
			<DisplayName>Suitable Clothing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This clothing really suits me.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Such suitable clothing really puts a smile on the wearer's face</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ClothesExpect3">
			<DisplayName>Magnificent Clothing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This set of clothing isn't just comfortable, but it looks great to boot.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Wearing such fine clothing really adds a radiance to the wearer's face</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect1">
			<DisplayName>Atrocious Environment</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This environment is hideous. Not even a beggar would be willing to stay here.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Such an atrocious environment easily puts a look of disgust on any face</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect2">
			<DisplayName>Filthy Environment</DisplayName>
			<Desc>How is this place so messy and filthy?</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Such a filthy environment really gets on one's nerves</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect3">
			<DisplayName>Ordinary Scenery</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The scenery here isn't half bad.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Such ordinary scenery is at least not discomforting</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect4">
			<DisplayName>Unique Scenery</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Such comforting scenery really is a feast for the eyes.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling easy to lose oneself in such unique scenery</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect5">
			<DisplayName>Incredible Landscape</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Scenery this beautiful is difficult to come find in this world.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling difficult not to appreciate such incredible scenery</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BeautyExpect6">
			<DisplayName>Heaven on Earth</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Is this Heaven?</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that This heavenly landscape entrances any who happen upon it</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NeedFabao">
			<DisplayName>Artifact Needed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>How can on proceed down the Law to Immortality without an artifact?</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Not having an artifact leaves one dissatisfied</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NeedWeapon">
			<DisplayName>Weapon Needed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I need a weapon to protect myself.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Not having a weapon is unsafe</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Jingguai_HappyHuman">
			<DisplayName>Manifestated into Human</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I...I became a human? I've finally become human!!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeing that Delighted for having transformed into a human</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>