<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="BottleNeck1">
			<DisplayName>Breakthrough</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I have finally managed to breakthrough.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Breakthrough leaves one rhapsodic</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BottleNeck2">
			<DisplayName>Failed Breakthrough</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Practice is harder than I thought...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Failing to perform a Breakthrough really leaves one dispirited</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BottleNeck3">
			<DisplayName>Obscured Law to Immortality...</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This state has lasted too long without a Breakthrough...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Being stuck in one's training really leaves one restless and testy</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BottleNeck4">
			<DisplayName>Finally, a Breakthrough!</DisplayName>
			<Desc>My hard work is finally paying off!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that A long-awaited Breakthrough really fills one with joy</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BottleNeck5">
			<DisplayName>Wavering Along the Road to Immortality</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This state has lasted too long without a Breakthrough...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Being stuck in one's training really leaves one restless and testy</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ThunderDisaster1">
			<DisplayName>Impending Tribulation</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I can sense the upcoming tribulation.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling difficult to put one's mind at ease in this type of situation</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ThunderDisaster2">
			<DisplayName>Tribulation Survived!</DisplayName>
			<Desc>It was close, but it's over.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Surviving a tribulation really puts a smile on one's face!</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ThunderDisaster3">
			<DisplayName>Foundation Destroyed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Heavenly Tribulation are vicious...it looks like there is no hope of ascension now.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that The tribulation was a failure, and that it looks like the Law has come to an end for this one is crippling</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Dan1">
			<DisplayName>Immortal in Sight</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Immortality is within sight!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that One is invigorated by their approaching immortality</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Dan2">
			<DisplayName>Becoming an Immortal</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Forming the Golden Core, becoming an earthly Immortal, this is the first step to true immortality.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that the Golden Core has been formed helps one to breathe a sigh of relief</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Dan3">
			<DisplayName>High-grade Golden Core</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I formed a high-grade Golden Core, this is fantastic news!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that A sense of pride wells up at such a great accomplishment</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Dan4">
			<DisplayName>Mid-grade Golden Core</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A mid-grade Golden Core is rare.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Such an accomplishment really imbues one with a sense of accomplishment</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="StageUp">
			<DisplayName>Elevated State</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Long periods of training eventually have their benefits.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Such a Breakthrough leaves one quite pleased</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind1">
			<DisplayName>Mental Breakdown</DisplayName>
			<Desc>There's too much to do, I can't do it all!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that A scattered mental state led to a breakdown</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind2">
			<DisplayName>Unstable Mental State</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I'm distracted and can't settle down...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that An unstable mental state can really get on one's nerves</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind3">
			<DisplayName>Good State of Mind</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Things are normal, not bad or good.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>feeling not bad when things are so normal</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind4">
			<DisplayName>Fulfilled</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I feel as full as the moon and vigorous like the sea.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that A sense of fulfillment like this is gratifying</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind5">
			<DisplayName>Clear Headed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Your mind is like glass.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that A sense of clarity like this is gratifying</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FrameOfMind6">
			<DisplayName>Flawless</DisplayName>
			<Desc>My mind feels flawless like nothing is corrupting it.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Such a sense of flawlessness is highly unusual to say the least</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="TravelExperience">
			<DisplayName>Antsy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I haven't been on an adventure in so long, I'm quite antsy.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Being stuck in one place for too long can cause one to yearn for adventure</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="SitCrosslegged1">
			<DisplayName>Sitting Meditating</DisplayName>
			<Desc>If only there were a more comfortable place to train...</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Meditating on the ground causes distraction</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="SitCrosslegged2">
			<DisplayName>Pleasant Practice</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I feel like I'm getting twice as much work done with half the effort!</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Pleasant practice feels truly rewarding</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeLing1">
			<DisplayName>Intense Qi</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This place possesses such intense Qi, this place is truly great for one's Practice.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Practice goes smoothly in such a place of intense Qi</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeLing2">
			<DisplayName>Sufficient Qi</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This place has enough Qi to make it a pretty good place for Practice.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Practice goes well in a place like this</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeLing3">
			<DisplayName>Insufficient Qi</DisplayName>
			<Desc>There's not enough Qi here, but sometimes you just have to make do.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Places with such insufficient amounts of Qi are not ideal</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeLing4">
			<DisplayName>Poor Qi</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This place is not good for Practice, there's no where near enough Qi.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Trying to practice in a place with poor Qi leaves one discontent</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeElement1">
			<DisplayName>Perfect Alignment of the Five Elements</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The Five Elements here are perfectly attuned to my own, this is excellent for Practice.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that The Five Elements being in perfect alignment really makes one feel like a fish in water</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeElement2">
			<DisplayName>The Five Elements are in Harmony</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This place is not bad for my Practice.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Things go smoothly when the Five Elements are in harmony with one's own</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeElement3">
			<DisplayName>The Five Elements are in Disarray</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This is not a good place for my Practice.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that Trying to practice in place where the Five Elements are in disarray gets on one's nerves</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PracticeElement4">
			<DisplayName>The Five Elements are Restraining Each Other</DisplayName>
			<Desc>I can't stay here for long, the Five Elements are in opposite alignment from mine own.</Desc>
			<StoryDesc>Feeling that The Five Elements being so out of alignment bears down on one's spirit</StoryDesc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>