<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="BQLabel_LOST">
			<DisplayName>Lost Item</DisplayName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Base">
			<DisplayName>Tag</DisplayName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Special1">
			<DisplayName>Firestruck Spine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Remolds the spine with a special secret Law to fundamentally transform it.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's bone remolding cap greatly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Special2">
			<DisplayName>Illusionary Brain</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Remolds the brain with a special secret Law to fundamentally transform it.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's organ remolding cap greatly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Special3">
			<DisplayName>Transcendent Heart</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Remolds the heart with a special secret Law to fundamentally transform it.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's flesh remolding cap greatly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Base_Organ">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Invigorates the organs through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's max True Qi by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's physical strength slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Base_Bone">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Reinforces the bones through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a moderate amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a moderate amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's max True Qi cap by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's physical strength slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's lifespan slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's appetite slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Base_Flesh">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Exercises the flesh through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's max True Qi by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's physical strength slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's lifespan slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's appetite slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Spine">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Spine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Reinforces the spine through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's max True Qi by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's physical strength slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's lifespan slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's appetite slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's bone remolding cap by a tiny amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Brain">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Brain</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the brain through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the max number of painful memories by a tiny amount.\n Increases the duration of the physical cultivator's furious berserk by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's pain endurance greatly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's organ remolding cap by a tiny amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Eye">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Eyes</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the eyes through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge by a tiny amount.\n Increases the attack accuracy of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the defense success rate of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the artifact suppression chance of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's perception radius by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Ear">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Ears</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the ears through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge by a tiny amount.\n Increases the attack accuracy of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the defense success rate of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the artifact suppression chance of the physical cultivator's secret bodies by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Nose">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Nose</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the nose through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's breathing efficiency by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Mouth">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Mouth</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the mouth through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the max tier of items to be devoured by the physical cultivator by a tiny amount.\n Increases the chance to gain essence from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the amount of essence gained from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Throat">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Neck</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the neck through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's breathing efficiency by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Heart">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Heart</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the heart through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the ability improvement rate during the physical cultivator's furious berserk by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's remolding rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's flesh remolding cap by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Liver">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Liver</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the liver through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's remolding rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the amount of essence gained from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Spleen">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Spleen</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the spleen through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's self-healing rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Lung">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Lungs</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the lungs through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's breathing efficiency by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Kidney">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Kidneys</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the kidneys through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi cap by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's stamina acquisition rate moderately.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Stomach">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Stomach</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the stomach through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the max tier of items to be devoured by the physical cultivator slightly.\n Increases the chance to gain essence from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the amount of essence gained from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's food consumption bonus moderately.\n Increases the physical cultivator's stamina acquisition rate moderately.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's appetite greatly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Intestines">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Intestines</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the intestines through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the max tier of items to be devoured by the physical cultivator by a tiny amount.\n Increases the chance to gain essence from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the amount of essence gained from devouring items by a tiny amount.\n Increases the physical cultivator's food consumption bonus moderately.\n Increases the physical cultivator's stamina acquisition rate moderately.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv0_Genitals">
			<DisplayName>Tempered Phallus</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Enhances the basic function of the phallus through remolding. The process can be accelerated by using Life Essence to change the fate and remold the body.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's base Mood value by a tiny amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_F01_All">
			<DisplayName>Blessed Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Blesses the flesh and makes it more flexible and nimble, which has more chance of happening during the normal remolding of flesh, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_B01_All">
			<DisplayName>Sharpened Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Sharpens the bones and makes them more aggressive, which has more chance of happening during the normal remolding of bones, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_B02_All">
			<DisplayName>Steel Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Metalizes the bones and makes them more resistant to damage, which has more chance of happening during the normal remolding of bones, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_O01_All">
			<DisplayName>Vitalized Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Invigorates the organs to provide the physical cultivator with more True Qi, which has more chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi cap slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_All">
			<DisplayName>Enhanced Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Makes the flesh grow stronger and transform into muscles, which has a chance of happening during the normal remolding of flesh, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F02_All">
			<DisplayName>Corrosive Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Makes the blood more corrosive and flow faster while the physical cultivator attacks, which has a chance of happening during the normal remolding of flesh, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_All">
			<DisplayName>Baleful Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Curses the bones and makes them penetrating while attacking, which has a chance of happening during the normal remolding of bones, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance by a moderate amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_All">
			<DisplayName>Void Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Creates miraculous energy in the organs and generates True Qi out of thin air, which has a chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_All">
			<DisplayName>Vitalized Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Vitalizes the flesh and makes it strain while under threat, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of flesh, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body artifact suppression chance by a small amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_All">
			<DisplayName>Psychic Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Blesses the bones and makes them more flexible, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of bones, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_All">
			<DisplayName>Dire Potential</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Activates the potential of the organs and uses it in a dire situation, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs, and refining with Cursed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Slightly reduces the duration of the physical cultivator's weakened state after the exhaustion of True Qi.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O02_All">
			<DisplayName>Innate Restoration</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Integrates innate energy in the organs to continuously generate True Qi, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs, and refining with Blessed Feng Shui Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_F01_All">
			<DisplayName>Ancestral Throwback</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Awakens the ancestral blood and substantially strengthens the flesh, which has a very slim chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a large amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a large amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_B01_All">
			<DisplayName>Ancestral Throwback</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Awakens the ancestral blood and substantially strengthens the bones, which has a very slim chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power drastically.\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_O01_All">
			<DisplayName>Ancestral Throwback</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Awakens the ancestral blood and substantially strengthens the bones, which has a very slim chance of happening during the normal remolding of organs.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi cap drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_A01_Jin">
			<DisplayName>Metal Blessing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Imbues the body with Metal energy to provide it with Metal effect, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of body, and refining with Metal Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance by a small amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_A01_Mu">
			<DisplayName>Wood Blessing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Imbues the body with Wood energy to provide it with Wood effect, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of body, and refining with Wood Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_A01_Shui">
			<DisplayName>Water Blessing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Imbues the body with Water energy to provide it with Water effect, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of body, and refining with Water Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_A01_Huo">
			<DisplayName>Fire Blessing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Imbues the body with Fire energy to provide it with Fire effect, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of body, and refining with Fire Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv1_A01_Tu">
			<DisplayName>Earth Blessing</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Imbues the body with Earth energy to provide it with Earth effect, which has a slight chance of happening during the normal remolding of body, and refining with Earth Essence will further increase the chance drastically.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_Chun">
			<DisplayName>Regenerative Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The blood is to some extent regenerative that can reduce the cost of True Qi during use, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Germination Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body True Qi consumption rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_Chun">
			<DisplayName>Restoring Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones to some extent can restore themselves to reduce the cost of True Qi during use, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Germination Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body True Qi consumption rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_Chun">
			<DisplayName>Metabolic Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The metabolism of the organs helps generate more True Qi, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Germination Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_Xia">
			<DisplayName>Flowing Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Faster flowing blood makes the body more agile, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Blossom Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy slightly.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_Xia">
			<DisplayName>Sprouting Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Further grows the bones to improve their strength, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Blossom Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power slightly.\n Increases the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_Xia">
			<DisplayName>Activated Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Activates the function of the organs for better performance at a critical moment, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Blossom Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the ability improvement rate during the physical cultivator's furious berserk slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_Qiu">
			<DisplayName>Withering Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Turns the blood corrosive, but meanwhile, its corrosiveness will negatively affect the resistance to damage. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Withering Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance slightly.\n Reduces the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_Qiu">
			<DisplayName>Harrowing Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Changes the bone structure to enhance its instant power, but meanwhile, some resistance to damage will be lost. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Withering Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_Qiu">
			<DisplayName>Smooth Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Activates the full function of the organs, but it will also use too much of the secret body's energy and negatively affect the resistance to damage. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Withering Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate drastically.\n Reduces the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_Dong">
			<DisplayName>Resting Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Slows down the blood flow and reduces the reaction speed, but the instant power will be increased at a critical moment. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Reversion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body endurance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_Dong">
			<DisplayName>Receding Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Changes the bone structure to reduce some of its strength, but the instant power will be increased at a critical moment. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Reversion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body power slightly.\n Reduces the secret body endurance slightly.\n Increases the ability improvement rate during the physical cultivator's furious berserk moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_Dong">
			<DisplayName>Reverted Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Restrains the function of the organs and reduces the efficiency of generating True Qi, but the instant power will be increased at a critical moment. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Reversion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body True Qi recovery rate moderately.\n Increases the ability improvement rate during the physical cultivator's furious berserk moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Bestial Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates after being corroded by power of Yaoguai, which drastically increases the reaction speed but also makes it harder to control. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy moderately.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Bestial Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate after being corroded by power of Yaoguai, which drastically increases the power but also makes it harder to move. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance slightly.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Bestial Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate after being corroded by power of Yaoguai, which drastically increases their ability but also damages the source. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate moderately.\n Reduces the physical cultivator's True Qi cap moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F02_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Unhinged Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates after being corroded by power of Yaoguai and becomes imbued with power. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy slightly.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B02_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Unhinged Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate after being corroded by power of Yaoguai and becomes imbued with power. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy slightly.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O02_DaYaoYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Unhinged Function</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate after being corroded by power of Yaoguai and can now create mutated True Qi that is extremely aggressive. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Yaoguai Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy slightly.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_GuShouJingXue">
			<DisplayName>Unbridled Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates and gains instinctual awareness, which lowers the control and reduces the secret body power and endurance, but also helps the body react to different situations appropriately. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Ancient Beast Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body power moderately.\n Reduces the secret body endurance moderately.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.\n Increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_GuShouGuFen">
			<DisplayName>Wild Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and grow like a wild ancient beast, which is very difficult to control for a normal physical cultivator, but the increased power is truly magnificent. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Ancient Beast Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power drastically.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy moderately.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate moderately.\n Reduces the secret body's artifact suppression chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Inactivating Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates and generates True Qi that inactivates functions. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Bloodthirsty Muscle</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates and blood capillaries are dead, so the muscles become eager to draw blood from the outside and therefore incredibly aggressive. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power moderately.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F02_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Senseless Skin</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The surface of the flesh is keratinized and has lost most senses, which makes the barrier stronger and resistant to normal damage. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance moderately.\n Increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Gray Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones are corroded by the dead and become gray, which can activate True Qi with weak power. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance moderately.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Hollow Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and become hollow inside, which increases the agility drastically. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy moderately.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Rotten Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs suffer from necrotizing mutation that can generate extremely corrosive True Qi. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_SiHunZhiXi">
			<DisplayName>Void Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate after resisting the corrosion of the dead and can provide themselves with mysterious energy generated from the void. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Wraith Breath.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_F01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Mutator Tissues</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates under harsh stimulation and grows many attached granulation tissues. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Parasite Eyes</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates under harsh stimulation and grows many perceptive eyes. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_B01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Demonic Pattern</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate under harsh stimulation and grows many demonic and strange patterns, which drastically increases the tolerance during berserk. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the duration of the physical cultivator's furious berserk slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Devouring Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate under harsh stimulation and become hungry for energy, which are more difficult to control but can also better weaken the enemy's Qi barrier. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance drastically.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B02_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>External Deformity</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate under harsh stimulation, break through the flesh and form distorted external structures, which affect the controls but also drastically increases the power. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy moderately.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate moderately.\n Reduces the secret body's artifact suppression chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv2_O01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Internal Deformity</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate under harsh stimulation and grows tissues that generate True Qi reactively. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the duration of the physical cultivator's weakened state after the exhaustion of True Qi slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_WuHuiJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Split Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate under harsh stimulation and split into multiple parts, which are more demanding for the body but can drastically increases its resistance to damage. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Filth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance moderately.\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_WuXingZhiJing">
			<DisplayName>Invisible Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh gradually transform into something invisible, which reduces the power but makes it hard for others to notice the details of the body movement. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Ethereal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body power moderately.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy moderately.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_WuXingZhiJing">
			<DisplayName>Shapeshifting Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones gradually become pliant and able to change forms at will, which reduce the power but help to accomplish more difficult skills. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Ethereal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body power moderately.\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance moderately.\n Increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_WuXingZhiJing">
			<DisplayName>Elusive Energy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate and produce invisible and elusive energy surrounding themselves. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Ethereal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_JiaoLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Dragon Scaling</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates and grows dragonesque scales. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Flood Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_JiaoLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Dragonesque Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and form patterns that look like dragon horns. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Flood Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_JiaoLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Thunderstruck Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate and become able to generate True Qi that is merged with the strong, numbing power of thunder. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Flood Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_XiongFengYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Blazing Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh mutates and becomes blazingly hot and aggressive as if merged with phoenix blood. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Phoenix Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_XiongFengYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Imperishable Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and become as firm but light and airy as those of a phoenix. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Phoenix Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_XiongFengYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Firestruck Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate and generate mysterious True Qi that can continuously burn the target like fire. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Phoenix Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Phantom Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The blood mutates and becomes dark as ink after merging with icy Yin energy. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body endurance moderately.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F02_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Luminous Muscle</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The muscles mutate and become luminous with True Qi as stimulus after merging with pure Yang energy. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.\n Reduces the secret body defense success rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Infernal Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and amass the energy of evil souls that can burst out when necessary. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power drastically.\n Reduces the secret body attack accuracy moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B02_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Benevolent Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and nurture kindness inside, which loses some forceful power but gains the merit of stability. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the secret body power moderately.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Yin-Yang Rotation</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate and thus generate two forms of True Qi that rotate between Yin and Yang and sustain for a very long period, but it will be hard to recover once it is exhausted. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's True Qi recovery rate.\n Increases the duration of the physical cultivator's weakened state after the exhaustion of True Qi drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O02_ZhuLongYuanJing">
			<DisplayName>Good and Evil</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs mutate and generate both good and evil energies, which continue to clash with each other and keep the organ functions overloaded. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Torch Dragon Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body True Qi consumption rate drastically.\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_YongJiJingSui">
			<DisplayName>Rejected Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh is strangely mutating and being rejected by the other parts of the body, thus causing localized tissue necrosis. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Everlasting Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the performance of the secret body slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's flesh remolding cap slightly.\n Postpones the next Heavenly Tribulation moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_YongJiJingSui">
			<DisplayName>Rejected Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones are strangely mutating and being rejected by the other parts of the body, thus causing localized tissue necrosis. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Everlasting Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the performance of the secret body slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's bone remolding cap slightly.\n Postpones the next Heavenly Tribulation moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_YongJiJingSui">
			<DisplayName>Rejected Power</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs are strangely mutating and being rejected by the other parts of the body, thus causing localized tissue necrosis. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Everlasting Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Reduces the performance of the secret body slightly.\n Increases the physical cultivator's organ remolding cap slightly.\n Postpones the next Heavenly Tribulation moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_EXJin">
			<DisplayName>Thunderous Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh transforms with heavenly Metal energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Innate Metal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_EXJin">
			<DisplayName>Metalized Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with heavenly Metal energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Innate Metal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_EXJin">
			<DisplayName>Ironside Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs transform with heavenly Metal energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Innate Metal Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Weakens the Wood damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_EXMu">
			<DisplayName>Tendril Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh transforms with heavenly Wood energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Innate Wood Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_EXMu">
			<DisplayName>Ligneous Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with heavenly Wood energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Innate Wood Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_EXMu">
			<DisplayName>Elm Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs transform with heavenly Wood energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Innate Wood Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Weakens the Earth damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_EXShui">
			<DisplayName>Tidal Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh transforms with heavenly Water energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Innate Water Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_EXShui">
			<DisplayName>Cloudburst Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with heavenly Water energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Innate Water Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body True Qi recovery rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_EXShui">
			<DisplayName>Equable Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs transform with heavenly Water energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Innate Water Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Weakens the Fire damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_EXHuo">
			<DisplayName>Fervid Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh transforms with heavenly Fire energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Innate Fire Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body power drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_EXHuo">
			<DisplayName>Burnished Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with heavenly Fire energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Innate Fire Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body power drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_EXHuo">
			<DisplayName>Ardent Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs transform with heavenly Fire energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Innate Fire Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Weakens the Metal damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_EXTu">
			<DisplayName>Dust Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh transforms with heavenly Earth energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Innate Earth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_EXTu">
			<DisplayName>Rockbound Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with heavenly Earth energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Innate Earth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power by a small amount.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance by a small amount.\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_EXTu">
			<DisplayName>Stoneshield Organ</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs transform with heavenly Earth energy, which has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Innate Earth Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Weakens the Water damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_TaiYangJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Sunray Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The blood mutates and radiates glowing beams of light. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Solar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's remolding rate moderately.\n Increases the secret body attack accuracy drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_TaiYangJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Ablaze Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones mutate and emit blazing energy from within, as if burning with invisible flames. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Solar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's remolding rate moderately.\n Increases the secret body power drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_TaiYangJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Solar Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A cavity is created inside the organs, which generates energy like a micro sun to provide strong and powerful True Qi for berserk. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Solar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's remolding rate moderately.\n Increases the ability improvement rate during the physical cultivator's furious berserk drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_F01_TaiYinJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Lunafrost Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh evolves and becomes glittering and translucent as if basking in moonlight. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Lunar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge moderately.\n Increases the secret body defense success rate drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_B01_TaiYinJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Icebound Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones evolve and emit cold air from within as if the marrow has turned into ice. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Lunar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge moderately.\n Increases the secret body endurance drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv3_O01_TaiYinJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Lunar Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A cavity is created inside the organs, which generates True Qi that can pacify blazing energy. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Lunar Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's global dodge moderately.\n Weakens the elemental damage received by the secret body moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A01_JieMieJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Force of Destruction</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body mutates with the Creed of Heaven energy and destroys everything without mercy. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Tribulation Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body power by a huge amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A02_JieMieJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Force of Creed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body mutates with the Creed of Heaven energy and morphs into justice itself that intimidates all evils. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Tribulation Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body endurance by a huge amount.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A03_JieMieJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Heavenly Unison</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body mutates with the Creed of Heaven energy and merges with the light of heaven and dust of earth. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Tribulation Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the physical cultivator's breathing efficiency drastically.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_F01_JiuYangZhenHua">
			<DisplayName>Firebringer Blood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The blood blends with combined Yang energy and becomes crimson red and thick like cream. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Ignis Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body attack accuracy moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_B01_JiuYangZhenHua">
			<DisplayName>Igneous Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with Greater Yang energy and every inch is surrounded by nine holy flames. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Ignis Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body power moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_O01_JiuYangZhenHua">
			<DisplayName>Furnace Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The organs experience a drastic change within and refine True Qi as if forging copper into steel in a huge furnace. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Ignis Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body Qi barrier penetration chance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_F01_XuanYueZhenJing">
			<DisplayName>Crystalline Flesh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The flesh merges with combined Yin energy and becomes crystal-like. This change has more chance of happening when refining the flesh with Aqualuna Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body defense success rate moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_B01_XuanYueZhenJing">
			<DisplayName>Emerald Bone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The bones transform with Greater Yin energy and become emerald and jade-like with spiral patterned light spots. This change has more chance of happening when refining the bones with Aqualuna Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body endurance moderately.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_O01_XuanYueZhenJing">
			<DisplayName>Occult Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The internal structure of the organs transforms and creates nine cavities with true Yin energy that generate resistible True Qi. This change has more chance of happening when refining the organs with Aqualuna Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Fundamentally increases the secret body's artifact suppression chance.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A01_TaiXuJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Void Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to the origin of time, Divine Void, and thus a wave of Void Force is blended into the True Qi inside. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Illusion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the power of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A02_TaiXuJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Acupoint Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to the origin of space, Earth Points, and thus a wave of Acupoint Force is blended into the True Qi inside. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Illusion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the endurance of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A03_TaiXuJingHua">
			<DisplayName>Impermanence Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to the force of chaos and thus gains a little ability to form elements and creatures. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Illusion Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the artifact suppression chance of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A01_XuanTianZiQi">
			<DisplayName>Astral Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to all the stars in the universe and thus a gleam of starlight is blended into the True Qi inside. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Nimbus Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the attack accuracy of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A02_XuanTianZiQi">
			<DisplayName>Enclosure Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to the Three Enclosures, i.e., Purple Forbidden, Supreme Palace and Heavenly Market, and thus a wave of Enclosure Force is blended into the True Qi inside. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Nimbus Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the defense success rate of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="QuenchingLabel_Lv4_A03_XuanTianZiQi">
			<DisplayName>Insulation Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The body is mysteriously connected to the force of chaos and thus gains a little ability to separate from all elements and creatures. This change has more chance of happening when refining the body with Nimbus Essence.[size=10][color=#D06508]\n Increases the secret body performance moderately.\n Increases the Qi barrier penetration chance of the physical cultivator's secret bodies slightly.[/color][/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>