<Helps>
	<List>
		<Help Name="1">
			<Title>Introduction</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="2">
			<Title>Character Menu</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="3">
			<Title>Outer disciple's Work</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="4">
			<Title>Buildings &amp; Rooms</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="5">
			<Title>Five Elements &amp; Feng Shui</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="6">
			<Title>Inner Disciple's Cultivation</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="7">
			<Title>Sect War</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="8">
			<Title>Trade &amp; Expand</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="9">
			<Title>Law of Shendao</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="10">
			<Title>Secrets &amp; Social</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="11">
			<Title>Pet Raising</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="12">
			<Title>Animal Shapeshifting</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="13">
			<Title>Training &amp; Practice</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="14">
			<Title>Taoist Animism</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="P1">
			<Title>Other Systems</Title>
			<Text>[img]ui/Help_en/001[/img]</Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="C1" Root="1">
			<Title>Game Concept</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[img]ui/Help_en/002[/img]
			Amazing Cultivation Simulator is a roguelike simulation game combining elements from several game genres, including survival, role playing, strategy, and more. 
			
			From God's perspective, players will guide characters to survive, produce, and eventually build their very own sect, after which they breakthrough several times and ascend as immortals. Therefore, you can only issue [color=#2E589A]general orders[/color] to the characters, and the characters will complete your orders according to their work schedule. Under most circumstances, you cannot directly ask a character to do a specific task. 
			Monitoring each character's emotions and moods as an [color=#2E589A]outsider[/color] is where the joy of this game lies.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="C2" Root="1">
			<Title>Controls</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				[color=#9e6404]Adjust Camera[/color]
					Use the middle mouse button, W A S D keys or arrow keys to move the camera. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/003[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]Game Speed[/color]
					Use the buttons in the top left corner to adjust game speed. The four buttons are: Pause (Hotkey: Spacebar), 1x Speed, 2x Speed, 3x Speed. (Use the Q key to reduce game speed, and the E key to increase it.) 
				[img]ui/Help_en/004[/img] 
				[color=#9e6404]Select & Cancel[/color]
					Left-click to select a target. Right-click to cancel a selection. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/005[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="C3" Root="1">
			<Title>Hotkeys</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[color=#9e6404]View Custom Hotkeys in the System Menu[/color]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="21" Root="2">
			<Title>Character Menu</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[img]ui\Help2_en\001[/img] 
				The character panel contains information about character stats. You can view their basic stats, such as [color=#D06508]hunger[/color], [color=#D06508]Qi[/color], [color=#D06508]mood[/color], etc.
				The buttons in the top left corner of the character panel are battle-related. Use them to issue attack/escape orders.
				The buttons on top of the character panel are for direct interaction. Use them to issue specific orders to directly interact with characters.
				The miracle panel ('spell' if in a battle) is on the right side of the character panel. View/Use miracles or spells that the character can perform or cast.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="22" Root="2">
			<Title>Base Stats</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Perception: A character's ability to explore and gather intelligence from the outside world. Affects a character's field of vision and their efficiency of fine work.
				Constitution: The strength of a character's body. Affects a character's lifespan, cold and heat resistance and efficiency when it comes to physical labor.
				Charisma: A character's ability to gain favor with others, no matter using their appearance or disposition. Affects a character's social ability.
				Intelligence: A character's ability to think. Affects the speed of learning. Luck: The extent to which a character is favored by Heaven. Affects stats related to chance. 
				Potential: A younger character with better Five Attributes will have a higher potential. Potential affects the speed of a character's foundation training. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/006[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="23" Root="2">
			<Title>Moods &amp; Needs</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Generally speaking, you can understand a character's needs via their moods. If a character is "feeling cold", then it means the character needs a more effective way to keep warm. 
				You can view a character's mood via the [color=#2E589A]Mood & Social[/color] tab in the character panel.
				
				You should pay attention to the moods of characters. If a character has too many negative emotions, it will cause a series of problems.
				For outer disciples, being in a bad mood means that they will [color=#2E589A]slack[/color] in their work, and it will also increase their level of dissatisfaction. A high level of dissatisfaction may lead to them running away. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/007[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="24" Root="2">
			<Title>Social Relations</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				A character will build relationships with others in the sect: friends, lovers, love rivals, etc.
				Characters will have different interactions with one another according to their relationships: Friends and lovers often talk to each other, while rivals and enemies will insult one another or even engage in fights.
				Therefore, it is very important to keep members of your sect on good terms with each other.
				
				You can view a character's social relationships via the [color=#2E589A]Mood & Social[/color] tab in the character panel.
				
				Characters eating together at a table will effectively improve their relationship. You can use this method to manage the social relations between sect members. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/007[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="25" Root="2">
			<Title>Health</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				You can view a character's health via the [color=#2E589A]Health[/color] tab in the character panel. 
			[color=#9e6404]Wound[/color] 
				[img]ui\Help2_en\032[/img]
				When a character is wounded and there is no suitable medication for it, the character in charge of medical treatment will automatically come and treat the wounded.
				
				The recovery from the wound is related to the [color=#D06508]resilience of the wounded[/color], [color=#D06508]medical experience of the healer[/color], and [color=#D06508]medication[/color]. If the injured person is not recovering after being healed, try to improve one or more of these. 
				
			[color=#9e6404]Inner Injury[/color]
				[img]ui\Help2_en\033[/img]
				As the game progresses, characters can be injured through the invasion of alien Qi. A character cannot recover from an injury caused by alien Qi. The injury can only be healed by giving the injured the [color=#D06508]right kind of elixir[/color] refined in the alchemy furnace.
				The recovery from an internal damage is related to the [color=#D06508]resilience of the injured[/color] and the [color=#D06508]effect of the elixir[/color]. If the injured person is not recovering after being healed, try to improve one or more of these. 
			[color=#9e6404]Functions[/color]
				Info related to Function is in the Health tab, in which you can view whether a character's functions are working or not. Functions affect a character's efficiency when doing something relevant to that specific function. 
				
				Pain: The degree to which a character is feeling pain, which affects a character's consciousness. Each character has different tolerance of pain. Painkillers can be used to relieve pain.
				Consciousness:  A character's consciousness, affected by any kind of brain injury or acute pain.
				Meridians:  The flow of a character's meridians, which affects the character's cultivation process and Max Qi.
				Movement:  A character's ability to move, affected by any leg or spine injury. Movement affects a character's movement speed and efficiency for most types of work. 
				Dexterity:  A character's ability to perform maneuvers, affected by any arm or spine injury. Dexterity affects a character's efficiency for most types of work. 
				Observation: A character's ability to perceive the outer worlds, affected when the character's eyes and ears take damage. Observation affects one's viewing distance and efficiency for most types of work. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/008[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="31" Root="3">
			<Title>Work Schedule</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				You can use the [color=#2E589A]work[/color] menu at the bottom right corner to schedule characters' work.
				Characters will finish their work according to the listed priorities, descending from left to right. If a task is not assigned to a certain character in the work menu, the character will not perform the task.
				Therefore, a strategic use of the work menu can increase the efficiency of the whole sect. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/009[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Prioritized[/color] 
				Characters will finish their prioritized task first before any other tasks. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/010[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Outer disciple's Schedule[/color]
				An overall schedule for outer disciples' daily activities. A suitable schedule will arrange characters to eat, drink and sleep before harboring any negative emotions due to hunger, thirst or sleep deprivation. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/011[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="32" Root="3">
			<Title>Building Order</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[img]ui/Help_en/012[/img]
				You can issue a building order in the building menu at the bottom left corner.
				As the game progresses, more buildings will be unlocked.
				Feel free to build your own special and unique sect.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="33" Root="3">
			<Title>Basic Order</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				You can use the row of orders at the bottom of the screen to issue basic orders. 
				You can issue a resource collecting order targeted at multiple objects by drawing a selection box.
				
				Harvest: Harvest plant products such as fruit and grain in a selected area.
				Chop: Chop down wood in a selected area.
				Mine: Mine ores in a selected area.
				Clear: Clear vegetation in a selected area.
				Demolish: Demolish buildings in a selected area.
				Explore: Set a destination for exploration. The character will head towards the selected spot and disperse any fog along the way.
				Put Out Fire: Put out fire in a selected area.
				Cancel: Cancel all orders issued in a selected area. [img]ui/Help_en/013[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="34" Root="3">
			<Title>Manufacture Order</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Some buildings can be used to manufacture items. Click on 'Manufacture' in the interaction panel of the building to open the manufacture menu.
				In the manufacture menu, left-click on a product to add the product to the queue for manufacture. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/014[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Select Main Material[/color]
				In the manufacture menu, right-click on the icon of a product to select the main material used to make this item. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/017[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Repeat Manufacture[/color] 
				In the manufacture menu, left-click on the 'Repeat' button in the queue for manufacture to select a repetition type for the product. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/016[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Arrange Queue[/color]
				In the manufacture menu, left-click on the 'Top Priority' button in the queue for manufacture to select a task to be prioritized. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/015[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="35" Root="3">
			<Title>Interaction Order</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				When a character is selected, interaction orders that can be issued to this character will be listed on top of the character bar.
				You can select an interaction order and then a target to issue a specific interaction order for the character.
				
				Interaction orders include, but are not limited to the following: 
				Eat: Try to eat an item. 
				Equip Item: Try to equip an item. 
				Attack: Try to attack a creature. 
				Craft Artifact: Try to craft an item into an artifact. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/018[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="36" Root="3">
			<Title>Area Planning</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				As the game progresses, you can plan three kinds of areas, including storages, fields and herb gardens. 
				[color=#9e6404]Storage Area[/color]
				[img]ui\Help2_en\021[/img] 
				After a storage area is planned, characters in charge of hauling will move any item that meets the storage requirement into the storage area. 
				You can select a storage area and set its filter rules, which can sort items into different categories and make them easier to find. 
				
				[color=#9e6404]Field & Herb Garden[/color]
				[img]ui\Help2_en\019[/img]
				After a field is planned, characters in charge of planting will come and perform the task.
				You can select a field and choose which crops to be planted in the area. Creating a suitable environment for the crops can accelerate the growth of the crops. 
				[img]ui\Help2_en\018[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]Expansion[/color]
				You can expand an existing area by drawing out a selection box overlapping with it.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="41" Root="4">
			<Title>Select Main Material</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				You can select different [color=#2E589A]main materials[/color] for the construction of a building.
				Main materials affect the color of the building. Buildings will inherit the element of the main material and be endowed with specific features. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/019[/img]
				
				[color=#9e6404]For example:[/color]
				A wall made of iron will be imbued with Metal element, which makes it more solid and less likely to catch on fire than wooden walls. 
				A furniture made from jade stones will be infused with Earth element, which makes it less durable but with higher Attractiveness. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/020[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="42" Root="4">
			<Title>Interactive Spots of Buildings</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Some building requires characters to stand at a designated spot to interact with it.
				When placing buildings, be sure to leave out space for interactive spots.
				[img]ui/Help_en/021[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="43" Root="4">
			<Title>Room</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				A room is a space fully enclosed by walls and doors. 
				A room must have at least [color=#2E589A]3[/color] but less than [color=#2E589A]400[/color] tiles in total. 
				Rooms are classified according to their sizes, which are listed as follows: 
				Narrow, no more than 10 tiles; Small, 10-20 tiles; 
				Medium, 20-50 tiles; Large, 50-100 tiles; 
				Huge, more than 100 spaces. 
				
				Walls can function as thermal insulation for the room. Control the source of heat in the room to maintain comfortable room temperature. 
				
				Rooms have different ratings. See the example below: 
			[img]ui/Help_en/022[/img]
				You can improve the room rating by flooring it or placing furniture in it.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="51" Root="5">
			<Title>Five Elements</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Establishing a sect unlocks the building: [color=#2E589A]Observatory[/color]. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/023[/img]
				After building an observatory, you can view the degree of concentration of the Five Elements of a specific area, the influence of a unit on its surroundings, and the Feng Shui of a building. 
				[color=#9e6404]Five Elements[/color]
				Hover your mouse over a specific tile, and the Five Elements Diagram at the top of the screen will show the respective degree of concentration of the Five Elements. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/024[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]Element of a Unit[/color] 
				Left-click and select a unit, for instance, a building, a plant or an item. If this unit affects the Element concentration of its surroundings, a circle that represents its Element will be shown around the unit. The color of the circle indicates the element, while the radius of it shows the area influenced by the unit. 
				
				[color=#9e6404]Feng Shui of a Unit[/color] Green means that the building has good Feng Shui. A more opaque color of green means better and more auspicious Feng Shui. 
				Yellow means that the building has bad Feng Shui. The color yellow will change into red when the Feng Shui is even worse and more ominous. 
				A building without any color (e.g. wall) means that it has no effect in terms of Feng Shui. 
				See below for the interactions between the Five Elements: 
			[img]ui/Help_en/025[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="52" Root="5">
			<Title>Cultivation &amp; Five Elements</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				A character's cultivation is closely related to their Element. Generally speaking, each cultivation Law will be assigned with an elemental attribute. 
				
				If the elemental attribute of the character's environment overcomes that of the cultivation Law, the character will experience great difficulties during their cultivation, and even fail, become injured or perish at a breakthrough. 
				In contrast, if the elemental attribute of a character's environment begets that of the cultivation Law, it will make the cultivation and breakthrough easier than usual. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/026[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]Take the Sixteen Supreme Steps Law (Water) as an example: [/color]
				Because Earth overcomes Water, this Law is not suitable for cultivation in an environment imbued with Earth element. In that case, avoid using stones to build furniture in the room. 
				On the other hand, because Metal begets Water, this Law is suitable for cultivation in an environment infused with Metal element. Thus, putting more furniture with an elemental attribute of Metal in the room will help with cultivation along this Law.
				]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="53" Root="5">
			<Title>Feng Shui &amp; Five Elements</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Feng Shui describes the relationship between a building and its environment, which is affected by the [color=#2E589A]interactions between the Five Elements[/color]: 
				If the elemental attribute of a building does not go along with that of the environment, it will have bad Feng Shui; otherwise, the Feng Shui will be good. 
				
				[color=#9e6404]Take a table made of wood as an example:[/color]
				If there are iron ores placed nearby, the Feng Shui of the table will suffer from them for Metal overcomes Wood. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/036[/img]
				If a well is built beside the table, the Feng Shui will turn good because Water begets Wood. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/035[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="54" Root="5">
			<Title>Feng Shui of a Building</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			There are two types of buildings: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Decorative Buildings[/color]
			Generally speaking, most buildings in the [color=#2E589A]Decoration[/color], [color=#2E589A]Structure[/color] and [color=#2E589A]Floorboard[/color] can be classified into this category. 
			A decorative building can affect the Element of its surroundings according to the main material used to build it.
			Feng Shui does not apply to decorations. They are often used to change the Element of a tile in order to adjust the Feng Shui of a functional building. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Functional Building[/color] 
			Generally speaking, most buildings classified under [color=#2E589A]Life[/color], [color=#2E589A]Work[/color], [color=#2E589A]Sect[/color] and [color=#2E589A]Entertainment[/color] belong to this category. 
			Feng Shui applies to functional buildings. The phrase "Feng Shui Building" is displayed in the tips for any functional building (see below). 
			The Feng Shui of a functional building is affected by the distribution of the Five Elements at its location. The more compatible the elemental attribute of the building is with that of its location, the better its Feng Shui of the building will be. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/038[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="55" Root="5">
			<Title>Feng Shui of a Room</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			The Feng Shui of a room is affected by the following factors:  
			I. The Feng Shui of all the Feng Shui buildings in the room. 
			II. The layout of the room. (Being cramped or empty will both impair the Feng Shui.) 
			III. When a functional room is facing the right direction, its Feng Shui will be good. 
				Facing South: Bedroom, Founder's Hall. 
				Facing East: Workshop, Artifact Pavilion, Alchemy Lab. 
				Facing West: Kitchen. 
				
			Empty rooms have no Feng Shui.
			When a room is assigned with multiple roles, its Feng Shui is determined by the lowest one of the multiple Feng Shui scores given according to each role. 
			
			After building an observatory, you can view the details of Feng Shui at the Feng Shui Panel of a room. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/037[/img]
			
			Special Situations:
			When a room has multiple doors, its Feng Shui is decided according to the following rules: 
				Any room with no Feng Shui attribute is considered the outside. 
				1. If there is only one door that leads to the outside, it will decide the orientation of the room. 
				2. If there are more than two doors that lead to the outside, then they will incur a Feng Shui Leakage, which will immensely impair the room's Feng Shui score. 
				3. When no door leads to the outside, the Feng Shui of the room will be decided by the door that is closest to the right direction.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="56" Root="5">
			<Title>Feng Shui of a Sect</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			The Feng Shui of a sect will be decided by that of all the rooms and other separate buildings in the sect. 
			The Feng Shui of the sect will affect all the disciples' luck. Even if it has little effect on their daily life, it might mean life and death at a critical juncture. 
			View the Feng Shui of the sect in the sect menu. After building an observatory, you can directly view it by using the Feng Shui Board in the top left corner. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/039[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="61" Root="6">
			<Title>Cultivation</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			When a character becomes an inner disciple, you can select a behavior for that character by changing the following setting. 
			[img]ui\Help_en\028[/img]
			[color=#9e6404]1. Auto[/color] 
			The character will carry out a well-rounded cultivation regime on a preset pattern. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Practice[/color] 
			The character's goal will be to raise the cultivation state by focusing on training along a specific Law and making a quick progress. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Mind[/color] 
			The character's goal will be to seek peace by adjusting their mental state. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Train[/color] 
			The character's goal will be to train different skills and quickly earn more Inspiration.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="62" Root="6">
			<Title>Cultivation Speed</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			You can view a character's current cultivation speed in the cultivation menu. Pay attention to anything that affects the cultivation speed, which can be improved to accelerate the cultivation. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Law Matching[/color] 
			How well the character's main stats and the cultivation Law matches. It can be improved by adjusting the main stats. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Element Matching[/color] 
			How well the Element of the cultivation location and that of the Law matches. It can be improved by choosing a suitable location. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Teaching[/color] 
			If the character is taught by a master with a higher state than them, the cultivation speed will be improved. It will drastically improve the speed if the master cultivates along the same Law. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Qi Bonus[/color]
			How well the density of Qi at the training location helps the cultivation. It can be improved by choosing a suitable training location. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Comfort Bonus[/color]
			How well the furniture used in the training helps the cultivation. It can be improved by using blessed material to build the furniture. 
			[color=#9e6404]6. Season Bonus[/color] 
			How well the season helps the cultivation. Wood represents spring; Fire represents summer; Metal represents autumn, while Water represents Winter. Cultivation along Earth Laws will be the most effective at the end of each season. 
			[color=#9e6404]7. Mood Bonus[/color] 
			How well the character's mood helps the cultivation. It can be improved by meeting the character's needs. 
			[color=#9e6404]8. Mental State Bonus[/color] 
			How well the character's mental state helps the cultivation. It can be improved by minding. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/027[/img]
			After a character reaches the state of Golden Core, the cultivation experience that is needed to progress into the next the state will drastically increase. Learn to use Miracles like meditation to quickly improve the experience. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/040[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="63" Root="6">
			<Title>Stamina &amp; Cultivation</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				After becoming an inner disciple, the character will start to consume a new type of resource named Stamina. By consuming Stamina, a character can refine Qi and increase their max Qi. 
				The consumption of Stamina is related to the cultivation speed. The efficiency of Qi refinement is related to the character's Potential. 
				
				Consuming food can provide a character with Stamina. Each time a character consumes a certain amount of food, they will replenish Stamina. 
				As the cultivation progresses, the consumption speed of food will be accelerated, but the character will have the ability to gain energy from nature. This is called 'Qi Absorption & Fasting'. 
				Adjust the speed of food consumption and the efficiency of Qi absorption to keep the balance between sect resources and cultivation speed. 
				
				Other than that, some rare medicine or treasure can be directly used to gain Stamina. 
			[img]ui/Help_en2/030[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="64" Root="6">
			<Title>Mental State</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			The idea of mental state is very important for inner disciples. 
			An inner disciple's mental state affects them in various aspects, including: 
				1. Practice; 
				2. Breakthrough; 
				3. Alchemy; 
				4. Artifact Crafting. 
				Usually, a better mental state means a better final result. 
				
				An inner disciple's mood plays a significant role in the change of their mental state. 
				A bad mood will make the mental state deteriorate faster and slow down its recovery, but a good mood means a slower deterioration and faster recovery. 
				
				If an inner disciple's mood is too low, it might cause their falling to the demonic side. 
				If an inner disciple becomes fallen, you will lose control over the character. 
				[img]ui/Help_en/028[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="65" Root="6">
			<Title>Breakthrough</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			When a cultivator reaches a bottleneck, it will be impossible to progress further. A breakthrough is needed to continue into the next state of cultivation. 
			A bottleneck can be the following:  
			[color=#9e6404]1. Common Bottleneck[/color] 
			Select a right location for breakthroughing. If the character's stats and the condition of the selected location meet the requirement, the breakthrough will have a chance to succeed. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Adventure Bottleneck[/color] 
			This type of breakthrough requires the cultivator to have an adventure. If the character's social skills are sufficient enough, it will be an easy breakthrough. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Void Bottleneck[/color] 
			Once started, this type of breakthrough cannot be stopped midway. The cultivator will lose all their magic powers and become an outer disciple again. They will need to regain their purest intention through laborious daily work to breakthrough. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Golden Core Bottleneck[/color] 
			Select a right location for the core shaping. If the character's stats and the condition of the selected location meet the requirement, the quality of the shaped core will be ideal. A better Golden Core means an easier cultivation process in the future. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Thunder of Tribulation[/color] 
			Select a location to survive the tribulation before the countdown ends. The cultivator's progress will decide whether they can survive the tribulation.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="66" Root="6">
			<Title>Inspiration &amp; Attainment</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Characters can gain [color=#2E589A]Inspiration[/color] during cultivation. In 'Inspiration' under the Cultivation tab, you can spend a character's Inspiration to enable them to study a manual, which will improve their ability.
				
				Each time a character studies a new manual by spending Inspiration, they become more acquainted with the Creed of Heaven. A character's Attainment will increase as they study more manuals. 
				
				[color=#2E589A]Attainment[/color] means how much knowledge a character has stolen from Heaven. Cultivation is not a natural progress. A character with more Attainment will attract more notice from Heaven, and the Inspiration cost for new manual learning will increase as well. 
			[img]ui/Help_en2/043[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="67" Root="6">
			<Title>Acknowledged as Master</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			When a sect has a disciple that has entered the [color=#2E589A]state of Golden Core[/color], other inner disciples can acknowledge them as their master. 
				When the master's cultivation state is higher than the disciple, the teaching will facilitate the disciple's cultivation. If they cultivate along the same Law, it will facilitate the disciple's cultivation even more. 
				When a disciple is breakthroughing, their master will guard them and help, which increases the success chance. 
				
				A master can pass down learned manuals to their disciple. As the old saying goes, the worthy disciple will excel their masters. 
			[img]ui/Help_en/029[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="68" Root="6">
			<Title>Magic Craftsmanship</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			[color=#9e6404]Alchemy[/color]
			[img]ui/Help_en/030[/img]
			If a sect has one or more inner disciples and alchemy furnaces, you can click on the interactive button 'Alchemy' to concoct elixirs. Unlocking new elixirs requires new elixir recipes, which can be acquired in adventures. 
			
			[color=#9e6404]Artifact Crafting[/color]
			[img]ui/Help_en/031[/img]
			If a sect has one or more inner disciples and crafting tables, you can click on the interactive button 'Artifact Crafting' to craft artifacts. Any item can be crafted into an artifact. According to the different physical traits of the items, the crafted artifacts will have different stats. A high-tier item is harder to be crafted into an artifact, but the end product will be more powerful. If the item has a large amount of Qi, it will make it easier to craft an advanced artifact. 
			
			[color=#9e6404]Draw Talisman[/color]
			If a sect has one or more inner disciples, you can click on the interactive button 'Draw Talisman' to draw a talisman. Talisman drawing will require talisman paper, which can be created at the talisman drawing table. The better talisman paper is used, the stronger the talisman's effect will be. Learn new drawing patterns requires new talisman charts, which can be acquired in adventures. A finished talisman is only effective when equipped on a character. 
			
			[color=#9e6404]Smelt[/color] 
			If a sect has one or more inner disciples, you will be able to smelt items into Spirit Stones. The number of spirit stones gained will be determined by the Qi value of the item. Every 500 Qi means one spirit stone generated. Smelting an artifact will always produce spirit stones. Smelting a higher tier artifact will result in more spirit stones produced.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="69" Root="6">
			<Title>Miracle</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[img]ui/Help_en/032[/img] 
				As a character reaches a higher state along the Law, they will learn to perform more Miracles. Some of them can help the growth of plants, some can be used to possess others for one's own cultivation, some can predict the future, while some can make rain. 
				Besides these, cultivators might acquire a Miracle Manual during adventure, which can be used to learn a new Miracle.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="610" Root="6">
			<Title>Adventure</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			[img]ui/Help_en/033[/img] 
				After a sect has got one or more inner disciples, you can click on 'World' at the bottom right corner of the screen to send them out for adventure. 
				Cultivators will experience various events and gain rewards and resources during adventure. 
				As the game progresses, more locations will be unlocked to be explored by the cultivators. It will take longer for cultivators to go on adventure in a farther place. 
			[img]ui/Help_en2/007[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="611" Root="6">
			<Title>Sect</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			[img]ui/Help_en/034[/img] 
			After a character succeeds in Foundation Training and becomes an inner disciple, you can click on 'Sect' at the bottom right corner of the screen to enter the sect menu and establish a sect. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Sect Level[/color] 
				A sect can progress through three levels as it gains more reputation.
				A higher sect level will increase the maximum population of the sect and unlock more sect buildings and game mechanics. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Sect Reputation & Battle Difficulty[/color]
				Going on adventures can improve the sect reputation. Meanwhile, enemies attacking the sect will become more powerful. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Sect Management[/color] 
				You can kick a disciple out of the sect in the sect member menu. 
				Use the 'Auto Cook' function in the sect menu to order your outer disciples to cook automatically at mealtimes. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Sect Relation[/color] 
				Go on adventure and build relations with other sects. 
				As the friendship grows, characters can earn more rewards from other sects by visiting them. 
			
			[img]ui/Help_en2/006[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="612" Root="6">
			<Title>Sect Structure</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Sect structure will be unlocked when the sect becomes Heavenly Abode (Level 3). You can manage your sect in 'Sect Structure' of the sect menu. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Appoint[/color]
				An inner disciple can be appointed as sect leader or branch leader. 
				Different positions require different skill levels. For example, the alchemy branch requires adequate alchemy skills, while the crafting branch requires adequate artifact crafting skills. 
				A disciple with better skills will perform better at the position. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Branch Area[/color] 
				You can plan an area in 'Branch Area' of the area tab in the building menu. 
				After an area is planned, you can assign this area to a particular branch. 
				A disciple under the branch will have a stats bonus while in this area. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Pressure, Distraction & Sect Leader's Ability[/color] 
				A character will feel pressure when managing too many tasks. 
				Pressure will transform into distraction, affecting a character's mental state, cultivation speed, etc. 
				A sect leader's ability can effectively reduce one's own and other branch leader's pressure. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Branch Expertise & Branch Leader's Ability[/color] 
				After a sect has a branch with a selected expertise, disciples under this branch will have a stats bonus in relation to the branch leader's ability. 
				Branch disciples can have two types of stats bonuses. 
					1. Area Bonus: Granted only in an area assigned to the branch. 
					2. Normal Bonus: Granted as long as the disciple is under this branch. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Retirement & Fatigue[/color] 
				When relieved from all duties, a character will experience a lasting fatigue. 
				The fatigue will be decided by how exhausting their work used to be. 
				The duration of fatigue will be decided by how many days the character was on duty. If the character had multiple duties, the time on duty will be from the start of the first duty to the end of the last one. (Shortest: 14d; Longest: 84d) 
				Note: There will not be any fatigue if a character is only on duty for a short time before retiring.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="71" Root="7">
			<Title>Explore the World</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			[color=#9e6404]1. Entering Locations[/color]
				Most locations in game are now available for your cultivators to enter and explore. 
				You may dispatch a cultivator to an enterable location, and click the "Enter" button to further explore it. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/044[/img]
				A Demi-God can enter any location instantly. However, Demi-Gods are still subject to their Heavenly Tribulation. 
				If there's time for a Tribulation, a Demi-God exploring a location will have to gather their whole spirit to fight it off, which greatly impairs their fighting prowess. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Explore the Location[/color] 
				There're various treasures, enemies and mysteries hidden in location maps. 
				After entering a location, a character may move (Hotkey: V) around to explore the area and search for them. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/045[/img] 
				Your cultivator might encounter hostile units when exploring a location. Make sure to keep an eye out for them. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Interact with Objects[/color]
				You can collect items in a location map by clicking 'Collect' (F1) beside the character panel. Note that this action may induce other characters' hostility. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/046[/img] 
				A cultivator may take at most 6 items with them during an exploration. You can find the collected items in the [Collected] slots of a Character's Gear panel. You may also discard collected items there. 
				Your sect won't officially gain these items until the characters carrying them return to the sect safely. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/047[/img] 
				There are also objects with special interactions lying about in location maps for you to explore. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/049[/img] 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Hide[/color] 
				When in a location map, a character can use the 'Hide' button (Hotkey: F2) to sneak around. 
				When sneaking, the chance of being spotted is determined by the character's Constitution and Perception, the distance between them and other characters, as well as the difference between their States. 
				A sneaking character is more likely to be spotted when they're collecting rare (tier III or above) items, so make sure to be careful. 
				
				You can tell your character's chance of being spotted by the color of the eye-shaped icon on character. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/050[/img] 
				If there's no eye-shaped icon on your character, this means no one pays attention to your character's actions. 
				A white eye icon means the character won't be spotted. 
				A yellow eye icon means that there is a small chance that your character will be spotted. 
				A red eye icon means that there is a big chance that your character will be spotted. 
				If your character is spotted by a friendly NPC, nothing will happen. However, if a hostile NPC spots you character, they will attack immediately. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Sect Wars[/color] 
				You may declarer war on any of the 11 NPC sects in game and beat them into submission. After you win, you can plunder them at will, and receive annual tributes from them. 
				Now NPC sects will interact with the world just like your sect do, and react upon each other. Their power will also wax and wane along with the plot development.
				A NPC character's power is positively associated with the power of their sect. 
				You may check a sect's power and its diplomatic relations by clicking its name on location panel. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/051[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="72" Root="7">
			<Title>Legacy Artifact Crafting</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				[color=#9e6404]1. Obtain Schemes[/color]
					You can obtain Manuals regarding the crafting methods of Legacy Artifacts through various means. After obtaining scheme for a Legacy Artifact, you may craft a Legacy Artifact using the Craft Artifact button on character panel. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/052[/img] 
				[color=#9e6404]2. Incubation[/color] 
					A newly crafted Legacy Artifact is still an Incubation. To activate its magical power, you'll have to perform a series of designated actions. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/053[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]3. Claiming Legacy Artifacts[/color]
					After being activated, a Legacy Artifact need to Claimed by a cultivator to be put into use. You may equip the Legacy Artifact on a character, and use it by right-clicking to claim it.  
					[img]ui/Help_en2/054[/img]
					A claimed Legacy Artifact can only be used by its master.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="73" Root="7">
			<Title>Sub-Spirits</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			After achieving the State of Primordial Spirit, a cultivator can split their spirit into Sub-Spirits. 
			Sub-Spirits are important resources for a character of Primordial Spirit State to get stronger. 
				[color=#9e6404]1. Split Spirit[/color] 
					A cultivator can split their spirit at most 64 times. One can split one's spirit into more Sub-Spirits by Practicing, surviving Heavenly Tribulations, consuming pills or studying Secret Laws. 
				[color=#9e6404]2. Put Sub-Spirits into Use[/color] 
					After being able to split up one's spirit, a cultivator can Attach their Sub-Spirits onto objects to further strengthen themselves. 
					The more Sub-Spirits Attached, the higher the State of the cultivator's Primordial Spirit. 
				[color=#9e6404]3. Attach Segments[/color] 
					A cultivator possessing Primordial Spirit can Attach their Sub-Spirits in the Craft Artifact screen. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/055[/img]
					To Attach a Sub-Spirit to a piece of equipment means infusing a portion of the cultivator's power into it using the Sub-Spirit as the vehicle. 
					After Attaching a Sub-Spirit, while losing part of their power, the cultivator gains room to explore new powers. 
					The higher the State of a cultivator's Primordial Spirit, the stronger the power can be attached through Sub-Spirits. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/056[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]4. Spiritual Equipment[/color] 
					The pieces of equipment Attached with Sub-Spirits become Spiritual.
					A Spiritual equipment takes effect unconditionally when equipped by the cultivator who produced the Sub-Spirit residing in it. 
					However, other cultivators shall equip multiple pieces of Spiritual equipment to have them actually take effect, and the Sub-Spirits within them should come from the same cultivator. 
					The stronger the power of the Spiritual equipment, the more other pieces of equipment are needed to activate it. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/057[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="74" Root="7">
			<Title>Tribulation Challenge</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				After achieving the State of Primordial Spirit, a cultivator can take on a Challenge of Life Tribulation or Attainment Tribulation in the Cultivation panel. 
				[img]ui/Help_en2/058[/img]
				For every 100 Attainment a character has, they can take on Challenge of Attainment Tribulation for once. If they succeed, they'll lose Attainment and gain Sub-Spirits. 
				For every 1000 Lifespan a character has, they can take on Challenge of Life Tribulation for once. If they succeed, they'll gain Sub-Spirits and extend their lifespan. 
				Moreover, each time a character survives a tribulation to remain in the physical plane, they will also gain Sub-Spirits and lots of Inspiration. 
				
				Surviving Heavenly Tribulations can be an important source of Sub-Spirits, allowing one to explore new powers.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="75" Root="7">
			<Title>Formations</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Cultivators may now form Formations to fight their enemies. 
				By forming Formations, individual cultivators are integrated into a whole with shared destiny. Aside from sharing each other's damages, they can also enabled to wield mighty Artifacts and Magic Spells, which are far too powerful for individual cultivators, to annihilate their enemies. 
				[color=#9e6404]1. Formation Structure[/color] 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/059[/img]
					A typical Formation consists of one Pillar and several Auxiliaries. 
					The Pillar is the heart and brain of the Formations,  while the Auxiliaries form the body of the Formation and provide various bonuses. 
					Through Adventuring around the world, you can obtain assorted Manuals regarding different types of Pillars and Auxiliaries, unlocking them one by one. 
				[color=#9e6404]2. Formation Arrangement[/color] 
					After unlocking at least one type of Pillar and one of Auxiliaries, you may access the Formation Arrangement screen by clicking the Formation button in the bottom right corner. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/060[/img]
					You have to create a new Plan when you enter the Formation Arrangement screen for the first time.
					[img]ui/Help_en2/061[/img]
					Appoint a character as the Pillar to create a new Plan. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/062[/img]
					After appointing an Pillar, you may check the ratings of the Formation in the making. A Formation's Complexity or Power can't exceed the Pillar' personal capacity. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/063[/img]
					Stability indicates whether a Formation can operate steadily. A Formation can't be formed if its Stability drops under 0. 
					Size is determined by the number of Auxiliaries in a Formation. An oversized Formation will suffer a great Stability penalty. 
					Load indicates the complexity of a Formation. If a Formation becomes overly-complicated, the cost to maintain it will be greatly increased. 
					
					As long as the Pillar can take it, you can place Pillars and Auxiliaries at will to form a Formation Plan at the right side of the screen and joining them using Links. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/064[/img] 
				[color=#9e6404]3. Formation Links[/color] 
					When you are arranging your Formation, you will find that the Pillars and Auxiliaries are presented as hexagons with different word tags on some of their edges. 
					You will rely on them to form Links among Pillars and Auxiliaries. Only edges with the same word tag can be joined together and form a Link. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/065[/img]
					Different Links have different effects. Choose Auxiliaries with the most desired effect, and plan out your ideal Formation carefully. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/066[/img]
					For a Formation to work as expected, all of the tagged edges should be joined with one another, otherwise the Formation will be unable to function due to uncompleted Links. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/067[/img]
					The "Null" tag can be Linked with any other tags. Links formed this way are devoid of any special effects, yet enables the Formation to function normally. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/068[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]4. Assigning Roles[/color] 
					When you have completed the planning, you may name your Formation by clicking the "Formation Settings" button in the bottom right corner, and enter the Role Assignment screen. 
					You may assign characters to each of the Auxiliaries and the Pillar. 
					Along the route from a Auxiliary to the Pillar, each time a character's Element begets that of the next character, the Links of this character's Auxiliary will enjoy amplified special effects. However, if a character's Element overcomes that of the next character along the route, the special effects of their Auxiliary will suffer a penalty. So make sure to pay attention to the Element of characters in your Formation! 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/069[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]5. Formation Attributes[/color] 
					Each Formation has 9 attributes, jointly determining its power and effect. 
					In the Role Assignment screen, you can check each of the attribute's meaning by hovering over their names and reading the tooltips displayed. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/070[/img]
				[color=#9e6404]6. Complete Your Formation[/color] 
					Your Formation is completed after following the steps shown above. 
					You can form the completed Formation be selecting the character appointed as the Pillar, and click the "Form Formation" button which should appear on their character panel. If all characters required to form the Formation are healthy and in the same area with the Pillar, they will automatically form the designated Formation. 
					[img]ui/Help_en2/071[/img]]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="76" Root="7">
			<Title>Formation Battle</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Once the Formation is successfully formed, you can use it to battle your enemies. A few things need to be clarified before rushing into battle with your newly-formed Formations. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Damage Sharing[/color] 
				Any damage dealt to the Formation will be shared equally across every character forming it. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Qi Balance[/color] 
				Every once in a while, the Qi of all characters forming the Formation will be proportionally balanced. 
				The interval of the balance is determined by the Formation's overall power. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Formation Stability[/color] 
				The Formation's Stability will decrease as the Pillar' Qi is being depleted. 
				A breached Auxiliary will greatly reduce Stability. 
				A breached Pillar means the Formation's Stability will drop to zero,  which will lead to the total collapse of the Formation. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Weak Point[/color] 
				Each time the Formation's Stability drops, there's chance that one of the Auxiliary will become the Formation's Weak Point. 
				The lower the Stability, the higher the chance a Weak Point will appear. 
				Damage Sharing will not apply to a Auxiliary that has become a Weak Point, which makes it highly vulnerable and enables one to cripple the entire Formation. 
				Once a Weak Point appears in your Formation, you can conceal it by change its formation.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="80" Root="8">
			<Title>Sect Trade</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			You can tread with other Sects once you've established your own Sect. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Trade Area[/color] 
				Before trading with NPC Sects, you have to plan out a Trade Area. Only items placed in a Trade Area can be sold to other Sects. Items you obtain through trading will also appear here. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Visit Your Trade Partner[/color] 
				You have to pay a formal visit first to trade with a Sect. Click the Sect's icon, then Click "Visit" to do so. Gifts must be prepared to form a partnership. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Trade[/color] 
				Click "Trade" to open Trade Panel. The NPC Sect's items for trade are shown in the left panel, while yours shown on the right. Items colored red are not for sale due to insufficient Sect Favor. Click "Negotiate" to see whether the NPC Sect is willing to strike a deal. Once they show willingness, click "Confirm" to close the deal. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Connection[/color] 
				Some high-tier items require high Connection between your sect and the trade partner to be available in trade. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Gift[/color] 
				Click "Give Gift" to give items to an NPC Sect. You can complete Sect Quests or simply cater to the Sect Leader's needs by sending gifts. 
			[color=#9e6404]6. Restricted Area[/color] 
				Areas colored red on map are Restricted. You can buy authorization to enter these areas by trading with corresponding Sects.  Character entering Restricted Area with authorization will be penalized after a while. 
			[color=#9e6404]7. Favorites[/color]
				Every Sect Leader has their favorite gifts. You will gain Connection and Favor of a Sect after giving the Sect Leader their Favorite items by Visiting and Trading. However, a favorite gift works only the first time it's given. 
			[color=#9e6404]8. Artifact Renting[/color] 
				Once you have achieved Friendly relationship with an NPC Sect, you can rent their Artifacts. The rented Artifacts will be automatically returned when it's due. If an Artifact is damaged before returned, you will lose Connection and Favor of the Sect renting it to you. 
			[color=#9e6404]8. Seeking Help[/color]
				Once you have achieved Friendly relationship with an NPC Sect, you can have them send their disciples to your sects as reinforcements. The character sent to your Sect will stay for a couple of days. You can't control these characters, but they'll automatically attack your enemies. The disciples will leave after a period of time. If an NPC Sect's disciple died during their stay, you will lose Connection and Favor of their Sect.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="81" Root="8">
			<Title>Sect Quest</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Various random events will occur in NPC Sects, and they will give Quests to you. Some events will also give you Quests. 
				[color=#9e6404]1. Gift Quest[/color] 
					Click "Expand" in the World screen to see the items needed to complete the Quest. You will gain rewards after delivering Quest items. 
				[color=#9e6404]2. Other Quests[/color] 
					NPC Sects may ask you to slay a certain character at one of the enterable locations. You will have to enter the location map to kill them.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="83" Root="8">
			<Title>Trade with Traveling Merchants</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Traveling Merchants will come to your Sect once in a while. They take with a variety items for sale, and you can see their price directly. However, the items sold by Traveling Merchants are generally more expensive. You can also learn from them news about Auctions.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="84" Root="8">
			<Title>Participate in Auctions</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Read an Auction Invitation to participate in an Auction. Auctions are held once in several days. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Auctioned Items[/color] 
				All auctioned items will be displayed at the beginning of the Auction. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Auction Rules[/color] 
				You can click the price shown below the item to increase your bid. Once you've give up, then you can't bid on this item anymore. At the end of the auction, the highest bidder wins the item. If the price is colored in red, then you haven't got enough Spirit Stone to actually buy the item. Bid at your own risk. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Unknown Items[/color] 
				In some of the Auctions, you don't know what you are bidding for until you win the bid. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Auction Results[/color] 
				Items purchased in this Auctions will be listed in this screen.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="85" Root="8">
			<Title>Expand</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			You can dispatch Agents to various locations once you've establish a Sect. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Establish Agencies[/color]
				Click a location and select "Dispatch" to send there an Outer disciple of your Sect. The Outer disciple you've selected will arrive in the location of your choice and become your Agent at your Agency there. You may spend Influence to establish an Agency. Agencies will also generate Influence. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Agency Construction[/color] 
				Once you've established an Agency, you may open its Expansion panel. You can spend resources to construct various Buildings in an Agency. You can upgrade your Main Hall once you've had enough Followers and resources. Upgrading your Main Hall unlocks more building slots for your Agency. Each of the buildings will yield different products, which will enter your Storage. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Policy[/color]
				Some of the Buildings will unlock Policies. Each of the Policies has their cost, and will lead to different Events. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Policy Events[/color]
				Once you've selected a Policy for an Agency, an Event will occur once in a while. When an Event occurs, you will see notifications colored in red appear on the left side of your screen and a red exclamation mark on "Power" button on the right. The Events will yield different results depending on your choice. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Dispatch More Outer disciples[/color]
				You can dispatch more Outer disciples to established agencies for a Stat Bonus for the Agent. The Agent's Stats will affect the rewards and outcomes of Policy Events. Once dispatched, an Outer disciple won't be able to return to your Sect. 
			[color=#9e6404]6. Recruit Disciples[/color] 
				Select Spirit Master Hall and click "Recruit" to recruit disciples. You can send the recruited discipled to your Sect or any of the Agencies. 
			[color=#9e6404]7. Other Sects[/color] 
				You will also meet other Sect's Agent at an Agency. The NPC Sects will also attract their Followers. If you want to win their Followers over, you will have to use some special strategy. 
			[color=#9e6404]8. Wonders[/color] 
				You can build Wonders once you've upgraded your Main Hall to Advanced Main Hall. Wonders will grant great bonuses, but you may only build one Wonder in a location. There are also restrictions regarding Wonders you can build depending on the location. 
			[color=#9e6404]9. Disasters[/color]
				Different disasters will befall different locations. A disaster will unlock Disaster Relief options for you. Different amount of resources will be spent each day to fill up the Disaster Relief Meter depending on your choice. Other Sect's Agents will also help with the Disaster Relief. Once the Disaster Relief Meter is filled completely, the Disaster will be over. On the other hand, if the Meter isn't filled after a certain period of time, there will be serious consequences. 
			[color=#9e6404]10. Power Panel[/color] 
				Press K or click "Power" button to open the Power Panel. You can deal with Events, transfer items in Storages to your Sect, or click on a location's icon to open its Expand Panel.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="91" Root="9">
			<Title>Belief</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Once a character learns of the Law of Shendao, they may become a Shendao Cultivator and embark on it toward Divinity. Cultivation along Law of Shendao relies on a special type of resource called Belief. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Obtain Belief[/color] 
				Belief is the one resource that lies at the heart of Law of Shendao. You may obtain Belief by means listed below. 
				1. Send a disciple cultivating along the Law of Shendao out for adventure. You may gain Belief through events triggered during their adventure. 
				2. You can obtain Belief through some special Secrets and Events. 
				3. A Shendao Cultivator may go to your Sect's Agency to collect accumulated Belief. After establishing your Divine Realm, you can erect Statues at your Agencies to collect Belief automatically. 
				4. Followers of a Shendao Cultivator will sustain them with Belief. 
				5. A Core Follower will provide a Shendao Cultivator with numerous Belief. 
				Whenever a Shendao Cultivator would obtain Belief, the amount of Belief obtained is positively associated with their Mental State and Tier of their Sacred Relic, and negatively associated with their Divinity and Distress. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Put Belief into Use[/color]
				As Law of Shendao's essential resource, Belief can be used to: 
				1. Replenish Qi. A Shendao Cultivator can consume Belief to fill up their Qi reservoir.
				2. Enhance Cultivation. A Shendao Cultivator can perform certain miracles to convert Belief into their Cultivation. 
				3. Construct Divine Realm. Belief will be consumed when constructing Divine Realm for a Shendao Cultivator. 
				4. Grant wishes. By listening to their Followers via the Divine Realm, a Shendao Cultivator can grant their wishes and gain new Followers.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="92" Root="9">
			<Title>Followers</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Followers are of vital importance to a Shendao Cultivator. There are two types of Followers: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Common Followers[/color]
				You may gain Followers or Divine Residents by means listed below. 
				1. Send a disciple cultivating along the Law of Shendao out for adventure. You may gain Followers through events triggered during their adventure. 
				2. You can gain Followers through some special Secrets and Events. 
				3. After establishing your Divine Realm, you can erect statues at your Agencies to gain Followers gradually. 
				4. By listening to their Followers via the Realm, a Shendao Cultivator can grant their wishes and gain a great number of new Followers. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Core Followers[/color] 
				A Core Follower can learn to perform Miracles as you construct your Divine Realm. A Shendao Cultivator can make a person their Core Follower by Persuasion. 
				The amount of Belief a Core Follower can provide is determined by their Extent of Belief. 
				Once a Core Follower's Extent of Belief reaches 100%, they can be appointed as a Guard on the Altar of Investiture, granting greater power to the Shendao Cultivator. 
				You can raise a Core Follower's Extent of Belief by listening to their wishes and grant them. 
				The effect of a follower's Persuasion and their starting Extent of Belief is positively associated with their Predestiny with your Cultivator, as well as the Difficulty of the Topic of the Conversion.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="93" Root="9">
			<Title>Distress</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[color=#9e6404]Distress[/color] 
				Unlike your average Cultivators, a Shendao Cultivator's Mood will always cause Distress, no matter positive or negative. The more Mood a Shendao Cultivator feels, the more distressed they are. 
				[color=#9e6404]Decrease Distress[/color]
				A character's Distress can be lowered through the following means: 
					1. Performing the Miracle "Mind Fasting;" 
					2. Raising Divinity; 
					3. Setting the character's Behavior to Self-Discipline.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="94" Root="9">
			<Title>Shendao Mental State</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			The Law of Shendao is extremely demanding when it comes to one's Mental State. Only the most stable mind can bear the ceaseless prayer of the numerous Followers. There're seven Mental States for a Shendao Cultivator. A Shendao Cultivator must meet different requirements each time they advance to a higher Mental State. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Moving[/color]
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'moving', it will be naturally raised, as a better mood means a faster rise. 
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 100 for 3 days in Self-Indulgence. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Calm[/color] 
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'Calm', it will be naturally raised at a steady pace, not affected by outside factors. 
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 200 and Distress under 50 when performing Mind Fasting for a period of time. The greater the character's intelligence, the longer it takes to achieve the mental state. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Still[/color] 
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'Still', it will only be raised if the distress is lower than 100. A lower distress means a faster rise. However, once Distress exceeds 100, their Mental State will begin to decay. 
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 30 and Divinity over 20 under Self-Discipline after achieving the Divine Realm. The greater the character's intelligence, the longer it takes to achieve the mental state. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Sagely[/color] 
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'Sagely', it will only be raised if the divinity is higher than 50, as a higher divinity means a faster rise. However, once Distress exceeds 100, their Mental State will begin to decay.
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 400 for a period of time. The greater the character's intelligence, the faster it is to achieve the mental state. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Wise[/color]
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'Wise', it will only be raised if the intelligence is greater than 8, as a greater intelligence means a faster rise. However, once Intelligence drops below 8, their Mental State will begin to decay. 
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 500 and Distress under 10 when performing Mind Fasting for 10 days after achieving Perfection. 
			[color=#9e6404]6. Empty[/color] 
				Increasing speed: When the mental state is 'Empty', it will only be raised if the distress is lower than 50, as a lower distress means a faster rise. However, once their Distress exceeds 50, their Mental State will begin to decay. 
				To advance through this state, one must keep their Mental State at 600 and Humanity over 60 in Self-Indulgence for a period of time. The greater the character's luck, the faster it is to achieve the mental state. 
			[color=#9e6404]7. Spirit[/color] 
				Increasing speed: The perfect Mental State.
				No further requirements must be met to advance further.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="95" Root="9">
			<Title>Behavior</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				After becoming a Shendao Cultivator, the character can regulate their own behavior for different needs. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Balanced[/color] 
				A character with Balanced behavior do anything as they please. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Restrained[/color] 
				A character with Restrained behavior will restrain their own desires, resulting in a faster increasing speed of Divinity. 
				The lower their Distress, the faster Divinity will increase. 
				A Restrained character will also receive a Divinity bonus up to 150% of their normal Divinity. 
				They will also be less affected by Moods, and will need generally less to survive. 
				Their Mental State won't automatically drop under this state, and its increasing speed will enjoy a 50% bonus. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Self-Indulgence[/color] 
				A character in Self-Indulgence will indulge their own desires, resulting in a slower increasing speed of Divinity. 
				The higher their Distress, the lower Divinity will increase. 
				A character in Self-Indulgence will also suffer a Divinity penalty up to 50% of their normal Divinity. 
				They will also be more affected by Moods, and will need generally more to survive. 
				Their Mental State won't automatically increase under this state, and its decaying speed will receive a 50% bonus.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="96" Root="9">
			<Title>Humanity and Divinity</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				As one proceeds along the Law of Shendao, they will gradually gain Divinity while losing Humanity. 
				It's an almost irreversible process, and one can only reclaim their Humanity by limited means. Once a character's Divinity reaches 100, they will automatically lose all Humanity and trigger a Belief Tribulation. If the Tribulation is successfully survived, the Shendao Cultivator will leave their mortal body behind, become a Deity, and leave the physical plane. 
				Divinity will affect Cultivation along the Law of Shendao in various ways: 
				1. The higher a character's Divinity, the strong their mastery of the divine power, and the stronger they are in battle. 
				2. The higher a character's Divinity, the more difficult it will be for them to capture the fleeting thoughts of their Followers, resulting in slower acquisition of Faith. 
				3. The higher a character's Divinity, the less they will be affected by Moods.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="97" Root="9">
			<Title>Sacred Relic</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				A Shendao Cultivator can craft their own Sacred Relic. Their can only be one Sacred Relic for each character. 
				A Shendao Cultivator can enhance the power of their Sacred Relic by managing Divine Realm. They can: 
					1. Increase the Tier of the Sacred Relic. 
					2. Add Traits to the Sacred Relic and change its Inclination. 
					3. Add rare affixes to the Sacred Relic's name and make it truly unique.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="98" Root="9">
			<Title>Divine Realm</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Once the Shendao Cultivator become accomplished enough, they may establish their own Divine Realm. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Establish the Divine Realm[/color] 
				The starting size of a Divine Realm is positively associated with the character's number of Followers, Mental State progress, Divinity, as well as its location when established. The size is also negatively associated with the character's Distress. 
				The starting size of a Divine Realm can be up to 49 Domains. 
				To expand a Divine Realm, the Shendao Cultivator shall confront their inner obsessions and trigger a Heavenly Tribulation on their own initiative. Surviving the Tribulation will subdue the obsessions, and expand the Divine Realm by 1 Domain. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Construct the Divine Realm [/color]
				Various buildings can be constructed in the Divine Realm. By building them up, you can raise the many stats of a Shendao Cultivator. 
				A few things need to be clarified before constructing the Divine Realm. 
				1. Follower Cap: The Followers of a Shendao Cultivator are considered to be residing in their Divine Realm. By constructing the Realm, you may raise the cap of its population, allowing more Followers to dwell in it. When the number of Followers exceeds the cap, the excessive Followers will be rendered homeless in the Divine Realm, accumulating Hatred. Once Hatred reaches 100%, a Heavenly Tribulation will be triggered. 
				2. Followers under Control: The ability to answer Followers' prayers is determined by the Shendao Cultivator's Mental State. Once the number of Followers exceeds their limit, they will be unable to answer them, resulting in accumulation of Hatred. Once Hatred reaches 100%, a Heavenly Tribulation will be triggered. 
				3. Follower Demand: The buildings in a Divine Realm need a certain number of Followers' prayers to take effect. If the Follower Demand exceeds the current Follower number, they will be overworking themselves, resulting in accumulation of Hatred. Once Hatred reaches 100%, a Heavenly Tribulation will be triggered. 
				4. Core Follower Limit: Each Shendao Cultivator can only have a limited number of Core Followers. Once taken in, a Core Follower can't be dismissed, so make sure to be careful when choosing them. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Guard[/color] 
				By constructing Guard's Temple, a Shendao Cultivator can appoint Core Followers as their Guards. Different Guards can grant a Shendao Cultivator different powers. 
				As a Shendao Cultivator progress through the different states, more Guards will be unlocked. Other than that, a Shendao Cultivator can also gain new Guards through events like Fortuitous Adventures. 
				The higher the Guard's Temple grade, the stronger the power provided by Priests.  
			[color=#9e6404]4. Shendao Miracles[/color] 
				Some buildings in a Divine Realm will provide the Shendao Cultivator with abilities to perform various miracle. Some of them are especially unique and powerful.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="99" Root="9">
			<Title>Belief Tribulation</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				A Shendao Cultivator will be put to the tests of Belief Tribulations during their cultivation. 
				Each time they survive a Belief Tribulation, the next Tribulation will become more fierce in power. 
				There are 3 ways to trigger a Belief Tribulation: 
				[color=#9e6404]1. Divine Ascension[/color] 
					Once a Shendao Cultivator's Divinity reaches 100, a Belief Tribulation will be triggered. After successfully surviving it, they will leave their mortal body behind and Ascend as a Deity. 
				[color=#9e6404]2. Hatred Eruption[/color] 
					Once Hatred of the residents of a Divine Realm reach 100%, a Belief Tribulation will be triggered. After successfully surviving it, the Hatred will be reset to zero. 
				[color=#9e6404]3. Obsession Confrontation[/color] 
					A Shendao Cultivator can choose to confront their own inner obsessions at any time and trigger a Belief Tribulation. Surviving the Tribulation will subdue the obsessions, and expand the Divine Realm by 1 Domain. 
					The intensity of the Belief Tribulation is determined by following factors: 
						1. Tribulations Survived: The more Belief Tribulations survived by this character, the more intense the next Tribulation will be. 
						2. Virtue/Condemnation: The more Condemnation a character have, the more intense the incoming Tribulation; on the other hand, the more Virtue they have, the less intense it will be. 
						3. Popularity Bonus: If the Embodiment of a Shendao Cultivator has obtained Followers and achieved a certain degree of Attraction, the intensity of the Tribulation will be greatly weakened.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="101" Root="10">
			<Title>Secrets</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				When trying to unearth the truth of the Taiyi Sect's destruction, you will be encountered with various Mysteries to be deciphered. To work them out, you will need to figure out the Participant and their Motives, as well as the Evidence of your theory. 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Participant[/color] 
				Who were possibly involved in this Mystery? 
				If you learned the Participant by hearsay, you must get corresponding Proofs to make it credible. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Motive[/color] 
				Generally, there's a reason why someone was involved in a Secret. If you can't figure out the Motive, then you won't be able to point out the Participant. 
				If you learned the Motive by hearsay, you must get corresponding Evidences to make it credible. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Evidence[/color] 
				Evidences are used to lend credit to your theory about who were involved and why they did it. Some crucial Evidences may make one realize the obvious and reveal the Mystery instantly.
			Once you've learned the Participant, the Motive and the Evidence, the Mystery will be Revealed. 
			Revealing a Secret will bring about more Mysteries to be fathomed, or make the full story come out.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="102" Root="10">
			<Title>Characters</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				The info of people you have got to know will be recorded in the Characters Screen. You can find out the following fact by checking out Character Info: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Mystery[/color] 
				Secret Info known by this character. To learn about the Mystery from them, you must get to know the fact that they know the Mystery through other people. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Traces[/color] 
				The recent whereabouts of the character. You can find them in locations indicated by it. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Personality[/color] 
				A character's inherent qualities. There are several different types of Personalities: 
					Weak: Soul Interrogation will always make them open up. 
					Naive: Friendly Communication will always make them open up. 
					Greedy: They will open up when given Favorite items. 
					Tough: Soul Interrogation will never make them open up. 
					Withdrawn: Friendly Communication will never make them open up. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Weakness[/color] 
				The character's weak spot. After learning about a character's Weakness, you can us it to make them open up by talking to them at the right time. 
			[color=#9e6404]5. Acquirements[/color] 
				Manuals that has been studied by the character. After knowing this info, you can consult them on these Manuals. 
			[color=#9e6404]6. Favorites[/color] 
				Items that the character likes. You can give them these items as presents to greatly increase their Favor. 
				When paying a Formal Visit to a Sect Leader, you can give them their Favorite items to gain Connections and a big amount of Favor. 
			[color=#9e6404]7. Dislikes[/color] 
				Items that the character dislikes. You can give them these items as presents to greatly decrease their Favor. 
			[color=#9e6404]8. Personal Treasure[/color] 
				Rare items carried by the character.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="103" Root="10">
			<Title>Clue</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[When you are trying to reveal a Mystery, Participants, their Motives and the Evidence of your theory are all Clues. Not all the Clues are useful for your investigation. You have to use your reasoning to tell useful Clues from red herrings.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="104" Root="10">
			<Title>Social Interaction</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Every NPC character now has their own feelings, desires and stories. You can get to know them, ask them about info you need, and obtain treasures with their help. You can interact with an NPC character by the following means: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Chat[/color] 
				Have an occasional chat with the character. You may learn from them Secrets or some special info. 
				Chatting with a character will increase their Favor before it reaches 30. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Discuss[/color]
				Discuss anything shown on the Secret Panel with the character. 
				By choosing your topic carefully, you may obtain useful information or achieve a certain objective in your mind. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Interact[/color] 
				Do something to this character. You may invite them to join your sect, or give them something as a present. 
			[color=#9e6404]4. Goodbye[/color] 
				If you do meet again, you shall smile; if not, then this parting was well made.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="111" Root="11">
			<Title>Introduction to Pets</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Pets, or Spirit Pets, are a special type of animal. In a way, they are like Disciples in their possession of the full complement of behaviors. At the same time, once a pet's Stats have reached a certain level, they unlock access to stronger Miracles and Spells. Different pets unlock different miracles and spells. Pets have the following characteristics: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Training[/color]
			Players can affect change to their behavior using training, thus enabling them to develop pets in a particular way or direction.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Conduct[/color]
			A pet will choose how to behave on its own according to its behavioral factors.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Summon[/color]
			Disciples can summon pets once they have entered other maps.
			[color=#9e6404]4. Death and Rebirth[/color]
			Pets won't just die, rather once their Qi is empty, erect a Statue and they will be reborn.
			[color=#9e6404]5. Replace[/color]
			Players can only have one pet. If one wants to replace their pet with another, then they have to erect a Statue to do so.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="112" Root="11">
			<Title>Base Stats</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Pets have the following Base Stats: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Growth[/color]
				Pets will slowly grow over time. A pet is still young until reaching 30% growth, which also means that you can't manage their diets. From 30%-100%, pets will grow and their training speed is pretty quick. Once a pet has reached 100%, they are fully mature.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Intelligence[/color]
				Affects a pet's training speed, at the same time, it unlocks more behaviors the higher it gets.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Qi[/color]
				Affects a pet's maximum Qi, making it more difficult for them to die, allowing them to use more Spells, and also increasing the amount of Qi for Internal Core.
			[color=#9e6404]4. Protection[/color]
				Affects a pet's Qi Barrier's ability to absorb Damage.
			[color=#9e6404]5. Spell[/color]
				Affects the Damage and Cost of a pet's Spells.
			[color=#9e6404]6. Core[/color]
				Affects the attack of a pet's Internal Core.
			[color=#9e6404]7. Blessed/Cursed[/color]
				Blessed or Cursed is the overall combination of the good and the bad associated with each behavior. If a pet enjoys helping people out, then they have a high Blessed value; on the other hand, if a pet enjoys killing, then they have a high Cursed value. Once a certain degree is reached, their external appearance will change as a result, as will their Stats. A higher Cursed value leads to excelling at attacking, and a higher Blessed value leads to excelling at defending.
			[color=#9e6404]8. Obesity[/color]
				Obesity will increase or decrease based on Food eaten and behavior. The skinnier a pet is, the quicker their Spell cooldown will be. On the other hand, the fatter a pet is, the slower their movement speed, but the higher their Qi is.
			[color=#9e6404]9. Physique[/color]
				Physique will increase or decrease based on Food eaten and behavior. The thinner a pet is, the stronger their Spells and the stronger they are, and, in turn, the stronger their Core.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="113" Root="11">
			<Title>Pet Behavior</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Pets have all types of behaviors. Some behaviors are more beneficial for building a Sect, others are beneficial for battle, and others still are just unusual. Players can affect change to their behavior using training, thus enabling them to develop the pets in a desired way or direction. Encouragement can place a greater degree of importance on a specific behavior; however opposing a behavior could lower the degree of importance or lead to a pet not repeating a behavior. Pet Behavior has the following types:
			[color=#9e6404]1. Eat [/color]
				Pets will try to eat different types of Food. You can train them to eat or not to eat certain types. You can also use the diet menu to prioritize certain types of foods.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Defecate[/color]
				After pets have had a certain amount to eat and enough time has passed, nature WILL call. Pets CAN be trained to relieve themselves in specified areas.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Attack[/color]
				Pets can attack Enemies manually, and they can also be trained to automatically attack as well. Pets also have Spells that they can use of their own volition.
			[color=#9e6404]4. Leisure[/color]
				Once a pet's Leisure is empty, it will amuse itself.
			[color=#9e6404]5. Rest[/color]
				Once a pet's Energy is empty, it will find a place to sleep.
			[color=#9e6404]6. Help[/color]
				Pets will help Outer Disciples to complete all types of tasks.
			[color=#9e6404]7. Advanced Help[/color]
				Pets will help Inner Disciples to Practice, though their Intelligence needs to be quite high to do so.
			[color=#9e6404]8. Haul[/color]
				Pets will haul all types of people's corpses or unconscious characters to a chosen location, though their Intelligence will have to be pretty high to do so.
			[color=#9e6404]9. Exercise[/color]
				When a pet's Leisure is full, they may well try to exercise. Exercise can affect all Stats and the effects of it can be improved with food and drink.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="114" Root="11">
			<Title>Pet Diet</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				All items of nutritonal value that a pet has consumed will show up here. Using different items of nutritional value can increase the effects of exercise, they may also have a positive or negative effect on the pet's physique/obesity. The types of food are as follows: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Fruit[/color]
				Boosts Intelligence Growth.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Cooked Food[/color]
				Boosts Protection Growth.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Mushrooms[/color]
				Boosts Qi Growth
			[color=#9e6404]4. Tubers[/color]
				Boosts Spell Growth.
			[color=#9e6404]5. Meat[/color]
				Boosts Core Growth.
			[color=#9e6404]6. Medicine[/color]
				Includes all manner of Medicine. Medicine requires three days to be fully absorbed after consuming. Other Medicine consumed during this time period will have no effect.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="121" Root="12">
			<Title>About Shapeshifting</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				If an animal wants to Shapeshift, there are three stages involved: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Awakening[/color]
				Animals must first have an understanding of Intelligence before they can be trained. They can be fed specific Elixirs to begin their enlightenment. They can be caught in the wild or awakened animals can be bought from sects, merchants, and Auction Houses.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Halfway Shapeshifting[/color]
				Animal Shapeshifting requires that the body be able to endure the intensity of human Practice and that they possess Intelligence on a level on par with humans, which is why Stamina and Intelligence Shards are needed. An Intelligence Shard requires Thought of each type: Realization, Rationality, and Perception. Thought requires 3 Intelligence Shards be ruminated upon (by Thinking) to obtain. After gain enough shards, it can awaken intelligence, then become intelligent and halfway Shapeshifted.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Shapeshifting[/color]
				After becoming halfway Shapeshifted, the Shapeshifting Heavenly Tribulation has to be passed. The time for the Shapeshifting Heavenly Tribulation depends upon the number of Intelligence Shards, the more there are, the quicker it comes.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="122" Root="12">
			<Title>Int. &amp; Stamina</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				Intelligence Shards are a special resource for animals that have not yet fully shapeshifted. These shards can raise some of their Stats, making them extremely valuable. If you want the pet to become Halfway Shapeshifted, a sufficient quantity of Stamina and Intelligence Shards will be required. Stamina accumulates slowly alongside digestion. Intelligence Shard must be synthesized via three types of thought: (Realization/Rationality/Perception)
			[color=#9e6404]1. Rationality[/color]
				Red, represents thought about circumstances, its Stat relies primarily on Cultivation Speed.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Perception[/color]
				Blue, represents thought about emotions, its Stat relies primarily on Base Stats, but it can decrease elemental resistance.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Realization[/color]
				Green, represents thought about things, its Stat relies primarily on all types of Skills.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="123" Root="12">
			<Title>Thought and Thinking</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Animals will produce Thought Shards over time that, once full, must be synthesized into Thought via Thinking. Pay attention to the following key points if you wish to accelerate this process:
			[color=#9e6404]1. Comfort[/color]
			Animals will produce Thought Shards over time, and the higher their Comfort level, the quicker they will be produced. At the same time, special Thought Shards can also be gained through observation.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Contemplate[/color]
			Thinking allows you to take three Thought Shards of the same type and synthesize them into a Thought. All Thought Shards will be forgotten though. Thought Shards can be placed in Memories to retain them, so that they will only be forgotten after Thinking about them multiple times. If you want to obtain better Thoughts, you have to make good use of Memories to save better Thoughts, or those that you just prefer to keep.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Observe[/color]
			The majority of Thought Shards can be obtained through Observation. If you have already obtained two of the same Thought Shard, the third one can be obtained through Observation.
			[color=#9e6404]4. Forget[/color]
			Be careful as Thoughts and Memories both will eventually be forgotten. Don't try to wait around for the ideal shard.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="131" Root="13">
			<Title>Obtaining Essence</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Physical Training requires expending essence to remold your body in the direction(s) that you're interested in. There are two primary methods to obtain essence from training:
			[color=#9e6404]1. Breathing [/color]
			Through a special method of breathing, a physical cultivator can use their strong body to extract essence, which can be used to Remold the body. Breathing in different places and for different amounts of time yield different essences.
			Players can manually give the Breath to a physical cultivator so that Refresh will be performed at the specified location.
			Players can use Refresh plan to arrange physical training to automatically Refresh at a specified time.
			Players can automatically determine the location in which Breathing is performed by placing a Cushion or Bed and assign them to Physical Cultivators.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Devour[/color]
			Those engaging in physical training benefit from having a strong digestive tract, no longer will their digestion be simple like your average person. They can eat everything and extract essence to remold their bodies as they do so.
			The Tier of the Item that can be devoured has to do with physical training's observation skill's level. Physical training can continue to increase the observation skill by repeatedly consuming Items. Other than this, players can also improve this Stat by Remolding the organs of their digestive system.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="132" Root="13">
			<Title>Remolding your Body</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Physical training obtains Cultivation by Remolding the Body. As State increases, the parts of the body that can be Remolded gradually increase.
			Physical training will lead to different growth based on the body part Remolded.
			[color=#9e6404]1. Muscles and Blood[/color]
			Remolding muscles and blood increases agility, attack accuracy, and defense success rate.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Bones[/color]
			Remolding bones increases might and toughness.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Organ[/color]
			Remolding organs increases physical training abilities and the one affected depends on the organ remolded.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="133" Root="13">
			<Title>Secret Body Training</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[color=#9e6404]1. Secret Body Activation[/color]
			If a physical cultivator meets certain requirements by remolding part of the body, then the secret body will be activated and stat bonuses will be obtained.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Secret Body Application [/color]
			After activation, the effects won't take effect, rather they have to be applied in the Gear Page to truly take effect. Physical Cultivators will try to attack with their Offensive Secret Body, and defend with their Defensive Secret Body. The Effective Secret Body can't take part in the battle, rather they will merely stay in effect.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="134" Root="13">
			<Title>Battle of Physical Cultivators</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[[color=#9e6404]1. Actively Release Attack Secret Body[/color]
			Once a physical cultivator engages in battle, the player can manually release any one of the cultivator's activated Attack Secret Bodies. Manual release requires additional True Qi consumption, but the attack will have 100% accuracy and 300% Qi barrier penetration rate.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Furious Berserk[/color]
			Physical cultivators can hold in negative emotions and then release them at once through Furious Berserk to greatly improve combat prowess during battle.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Flourish[/color]
			With an Attack Secret Body is manually released, there is a chance of triggering Flourish. Once triggered, it resets the Secret Body's CD and allows continuous releases without cost for a while.
			Trigger chance increases by 100% under Furious Berserk.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="141" Root="14">
			<Title>Illuminating Methods</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Everything on Earth is affected by the changes in the cosmos, as well as from masters' opening minds and bringing Intelligence, this is also how sentient spirits are born. A thing could be illuminated in following situations:
			[color=#9e6404]1. Awakening by a Master[/color]
			Cultivators with deep Attainment have Epiphanies about heaven and earth that frequently affect those around them. With enough luck, this kind of influence could even lead to Intelligence.
			[color=#9e6404]2. Celestial Phenomena[/color]
			Natural celestial phenomena represent the tumultuous changes in the rules of heaven and earth. When one happens, there's a chance that it will result in the birth of Intelligence.
			[color=#9e6404]3. Miracles[/color]
			There are some miracles that can force a thing to be illuminated, but it's not easy and typically requires sustained effort.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="142" Root="14">
			<Title>Spirits &amp; Elements</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Humans are naturally infused with all five elements in balance; the sentient spirits are not. During Body Genesis, the ratio of Five Elements that a sentient spirit has will influence the Five Attributes and talents that its body will have once created. Although the Five Elements being unequal may bring shortcomings, it can also forge a Body of Element that could never be achieved in a human body.
			Sentient Spirits adjust the ratio of Five Elements that they possess by eating items with different amounts of each of the Five Elements so as to prepare for Shapeshifting.
			If the proportion of Five Elements is acceptable, the player can perform the Miracle “Body Genesis” to create a body for the sentient spirit, which will cause it to transform into a person.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="143" Root="14">
			<Title>Spirit Talents</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			The sentient spirit differs from its original body, and it may possess powerful properties. This gift is difficult for other creatures to comprehend. It's difficult for an insentient object to be illuminated and then transform. During this process, it's made even more difficult as cultivators' attention and greed may well be drawn to them. Perhaps this is the intended compensation demanded by the Creed of Heaven.
			Sentient spirits' characteristics are as follows:
			    Sentient Elixir: There won't be any Medicine Tolerance produced the first time that you take a Pill.
			    Sentient Edible: Naturally possesses high Qi Absorption capabilities and Stamina conversion ratio.
			    Sentient Dark Soul Gem: Increases success rate of specter refinement and spiritual refinement by 100%.
			    Sentient Spirit Stone: Naturally possesses a larger amount of Base Qi.
			    Sentient Talisman: Enables the wearing of an additional talisman.
			    Sentient Gear: Increases the effect of gear equipped by 100%.
			    Sentient Relic: Increases the effect of Feng Shui Relics by 100%. 
			    Sentient Material: Can grow by consuming items of the same type as the consumer.
			    Sentient Artifact: Enhances the ability to use artifacts, making them easier to use.
			    Sentient Building: Can quickly restore missing sections of its body by consuming building materials.
			    Sentient Plant: Has indeterminate growth, i.e. it continues growing as time passes.
			    Sentient Other things: Possesses extremely high Luck.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="P11" Root="P1">
			<Title>Character Epilogue</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				For every character that has Ascended, been kicked out of the Sect or died, there will be a Character Epilogue for them. 
				Character Epilogues are categorized according to the saved games. You can check a character's Epilogue by finding the saved games they are from. 
				Accessing Character Epilogues via title screen will automatically show Epilogues of characters from your latest saved game.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="P12" Root="P1">
			<Title>Manual Pavilion</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			New Building: Manual Pavilion is added. You can now record and manage your Manuals through the Manual Pavilion. Each Shelf has its Capacity. The more Attainment is needed to study a Manual, the more space the Manual will take on the Shelf. You can record Manuals by the following means: 
			[color=#9e6404]1. Record by Law[/color] 
				Record all non-advanced Manuals of a Law. 
			[color=#9e6404]2. Record Single Manual[/color] 
				Record a Single Manual. 
			[color=#9e6404]3. Record by Learner[/color] 
				Record all non-advanced Manuals learned by a single character.  
			The more Manuals stored in Manual Pavilion, the greater the bonus received by all your disciples in Sect. They will need less Attainment to study a Manual.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="P13" Root="P1">
			<Title>Building Blueprint</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
				New Feature: Building Blueprint is added. 
				You can now select an area no larger than 20 x 20 tiles and save the layout as a Blueprint. The saved Blueprint can be used in all your saved games. 
				You can also share it via the Workshop.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		<Help Name="P14" Root="P1">
			<Title>Message &amp; Sect Rules</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			Players can now set whether they want certain types of messages to show up on the Sect page. The player can choose to ignore certain types of message and prevent from popping up.
			Players can now configure sect rules on the Sect page. Disciples will automatically make decisions according to the sect rules while out Adventuring.]]></Text>
		</Help>
		
		<Help Name="P15" Root="P1">
			<Title>Spirit Contracts</Title>
			<Text><![CDATA[
			After equipped with a spirit contract, one can gain a huge amount of adventure speed. Besides, characters will gain extra properties if they reach higher states. After reaching the golden core state, they will gain extra Max Qi. After the Primordial state, they will gain different special abilities for different contracts, as below:
	    
			·Added 12 different spirit contracts
			    Rabbit: Extra Adventure Speed.
			    Chicken: Extra Perception.
			    Wolf: Extra Artifact Mastery.
			    Snake: Extra Spell.
			    Boar: Extra Constitution.
			    Bear: Extra Constitution, extra Artifact Mastery.
			    Frog: Extra Qi Sense.
			    Turtle: Extra Protect.
			    Cat: Extra Artisanry.
			    Bull: Extra Constitution, extra Alchemy.
			    Tiger: Extra Battle, extra Artifact Mastery.
			    Panda: Extra Luck.[Deep in the Bamboo forest]

			·Added 2 special spirit contracts
			    There are 2 different special spirit contracts: Lushu and Fei contract. They can only be bought from auctions. These contracts cannot benefit for battles but can enable characters to use Lushu and Fei's original miracle to call rain or dispel clouds.·

			·Sixteen Supreme Step Law: Seal Contract
			    It can be cast to an unconscious monster in a lower state than you can seal it into a spirit contract. The higher the monster state is, the higher the contract effect will be.

			·Added a new setting: Spirit Fly(beside mindful dresser). 
			    After it is ticked, this character will always ride on the contract while moving.
			]]></Text>
		</Help>
	</List>
</Helps>