<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="BodyAnimal">
			<IVNUMBER.0.Animal.DisplayName>Rabbit Cage</IVNUMBER.0.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.0.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a rabbit at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.0.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.1.Animal.DisplayName>Chicken Cage</IVNUMBER.1.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.1.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a chicken at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.1.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.2.Animal.DisplayName>Wolf Cage</IVNUMBER.2.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.2.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a wolf at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.2.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.3.Animal.DisplayName>Snake Cage</IVNUMBER.3.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.3.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a snake at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.3.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.4.Animal.DisplayName>Boar Cage</IVNUMBER.4.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.4.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a boar at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.4.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.5.Animal.DisplayName>Bear Cage</IVNUMBER.5.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.5.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a bear at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.5.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.6.Animal.DisplayName>Turtle Cage</IVNUMBER.6.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.6.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a turtle at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.6.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.7.Animal.DisplayName>Frog Cage</IVNUMBER.7.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.7.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a frog at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.7.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.8.Animal.DisplayName>Cat Cage</IVNUMBER.8.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.8.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a cat at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.8.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.9.Animal.DisplayName>Bull Cage</IVNUMBER.9.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.9.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a bull at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.9.Animal.Tip>
			<IVNUMBER.10.Animal.DisplayName>Tiger Cage</IVNUMBER.10.Animal.DisplayName>
			<IVNUMBER.10.Animal.Tip>Inside it is a tiger at the Awakening State, it has some understandings in the Law of Physical Cultivation.</IVNUMBER.10.Animal.Tip>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>