<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Item_CapeBase" sParam="Item">
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Silk,Yarn,Satin</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Nomal1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fire Mantle</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle for decoration, a famous style among Cultivation Realm.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Nomal2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Cloud Mantle</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle for decoration, a famous style among Cultivation Realm.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Nomal3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dark Mantle</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle for decoration, a famous style among Cultivation Realm.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Nomal4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Bright Mantle</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle for decoration, a famous style among Cultivation Realm.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Zhou Flow</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle with exquisite pattern, with is the symbol of KunLun Fair Spell winner.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sky Fire Extinct</ThingName>
			<Desc>A symbol of beating the Phoenix. The pattern on the mantle is a nature appearance of the essence within its body and looks pretty mysterious.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Freeze Cloud Blizzard</ThingName>
			<Desc>A symbol of beating the Flood Dragon. The pattern on the mantle is a nature appearance of the essence within its body and looks pretty mysterious.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fortune</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle with exquisite pattern, with is the symbol of KunLun Fair Arifact Craft winner.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp5" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dan Xi</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle with exquisite pattern, with is the symbol of KunLun Fair Alchemy winner.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp6" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Bu Ying</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle with exquisite pattern, with is the symbol of KunLun Fair Artifact winner.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp7" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Living Beings</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle comes from other world. Its pattern means winter is over and spring is coming and everything is coming out.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp8" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dark Body's Shadow</ThingName>
			<Desc>A symbol of beating the Torch Dragon. The pattern on the mantle is a nature appearance of the Yin essence within its body and looks pretty mysterious.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp9" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Bright Feather's Light</ThingName>
			<Desc>A symbol of beating the Torch Dragon. The pattern on the mantle is a nature appearance of the Yang essence within its body and looks pretty mysterious.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Cape_Sp10" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Tao Principles</ThingName>
			<Desc>A mantle with exquisite pattern, with is the symbol of KunLun Fair Debate winner. It is said that Follow ancient path and conquer the present, to know the ancient is to know the Tao Principles.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>