<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="FishBase" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fish (General)</ThingName>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Surimi,Fish,Bone</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_StoneCrab" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Crab</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common crab that lives in dirt and rocks.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_Ji" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common freshwater fish that lives in all kinds of water bodies.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t6" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue Dwarf Cichlid</ThingName>
			<Desc>Fish that is commonly seen on Mt. Kunlun.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t8" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Red Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>A large killifish that only lives on mountains and endures cold weather.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue Amur Bream</ThingName>
			<Desc>Bream that only lives at Heavenstep Peak. Likes to eat Iceflower.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s7" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Highland Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Flatfish that only lives on northwestern mountains.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s9" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blackstone Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Flatfish that only lives on Mt. Blackstone. Affected by the Sword Pillars, it is black and tough and likes items of metal element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_ChillyCrab" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Rime Crab</ThingName>
			<Desc>Crab with tasty meat that is only seen in cold areas.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Surimi,Shell,Bone</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_BaiHuang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Snow Naked Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>A rare kind of naked carp that only lives in Lake Jakestone and shows up during winter. Its meat taste good and can be eaten directly.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>White Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>A large killifish as white as snow that only rarely shows up in cold water areas.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r6" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Red-fin Pond Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>A rare pond loach with sharp red fins that lives in cold areas and is said to only shows up during winter.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_QingHei" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Green Snakehead</ThingName>
			<Desc>A kind of snakehead with a green head that is difficult to catch.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Crucian Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common fish that is mainly seen around Mountainsouth.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Bream</ThingName>
			<Desc>A flat, common fish that is mainly seen in streams and rivers near Mountainsouth.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r8" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue-fin Swamp Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>It is said that it only shows up near Taiyi Sect and comes with Polar Night. It has a large amount of stamina, so it has a name of "Water Fairy"</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s5" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Pink Amur Bream</ThingName>
			<Desc>A pink Amur bream that is said to be a hybrid of carp and bream. During autumn, it swims from sea to river to spawn eggs and its body turns soft to adjust to the rocks in freshwater rivers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Moonlight Fish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare fish that has sweet, tasty meat. Lives in Celestial Pool and only shows up after autumn midnight.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t5" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Pink Dwarf Cichlid</ThingName>
			<Desc>A small fish that is often seen near Mt. Nelumbo.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Pond Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>A long, slim fish that lives in dirt near creeks.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>White Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare flatfish that lives on Mt. Shu.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r11" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Jade Essence Fish</ThingName>
			<Desc>A rare fish seen around Mt. Shu that likes Jade Essence. Maybe it is drawn by its Earth Qi.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_FenLi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Pink Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Carp that is pink all over its body. Some think it is affected by the peach blossoms nearby.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t11" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Demon Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Killifish that lives in swamps in Wild South and is said to have patterns all over its body because it has inhaled Demon Emperor's aura. Only shows up during spring.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Black Pond Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>A black, large pond loach that only shows up in Wild South.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_Black" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Snakehead</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common freshwater fish that mostly lives in rivers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_BlueFish" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare blue carp that lives in large rivers. Its body has turned blue after absorbing Water Qi for generations.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_Huang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Naked Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Golden fish that mostly lives in large rivers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_HongHuang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Red-cap Naked Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Naked carp that has a red cap and rarely shows up in large rivers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r13" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>White Swamp Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>A white swamp eel with tasty, chewy meat that only lives in large rivers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_RedFish" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Rainbow Trout</ThingName>
			<Desc>A red freshwater fish that lives deep in the river near Galepeak Town and only floats above during winter.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t10" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Jade Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Killifish that lives in Spiritual Water.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_JadeCrab" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Jade Crab</ThingName>
			<Desc>Very rare crab that only shows up during the day. Its body has been affected by the Spiritual Water and become jade-like. Some cultivators pet them on Mt. Nulumbo.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Surimi,Shell,Bone</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s6" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Peacock Bream</ThingName>
			<Desc>A beautiful, translucent green bream that lives in Spiritual Water. All sects have kept some for ornamental purposes.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r5" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Peach Pond Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>Pond loach that only lives in Spiritual Water and likes to eat Spirit Stones.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r12" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Shinning Swamp Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare swamp eel that lives in Spiritual Water, only shows up during summer and feeds on precious Spirit Roots.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_XieLi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Demon Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Carp that only shows up in Thin Blood with demonic patterns on its body.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dark-eye Snakehead</ThingName>
			<Desc>Snakehead with giant, pitch black eyes that only shows up in Blood Water.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Red Bream</ThingName>
			<Desc>Bream that only lives in Thin Blood and often attacks animals passing nearby.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s11" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Demon Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare flatfish that lives in Blood Water with a strong odor that keeps it away from its predator. So, blood water ofter smells awful in Springs.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_FireCrab" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fire Crab</ThingName>
			<Desc>Crab that lives in a hot region with a shell that helps it endure cold weather.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Surimi,Shell,Bone</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_HongGui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sockeye Salmon</ThingName>
			<Desc>A red salmon with a whitish cap that shows up near Great Desert.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Golden Dwarf Cichlid</ThingName>
			<Desc>Fish that lives in desert. Born to endure hungry. Maybe it's because it only feeds on food of Wood element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s10" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Brown Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Flatfish that is seen in Great Desert.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Igneocopper Pond Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>Pond loach that lives near Igneocopper mines and feeds on minerals in the ores. Its body can emit heat.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r7" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sand Loach</ThingName>
			<Desc>A kind of loach that lives in desert.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t7" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Big-mouth Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Fish with a thick mouth that is often seen in sea.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t9" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Black Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare killifish that lives in sea.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_t12" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Flame Killifish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Killifish that can only be seen during summer. Only few people have seen it in Poison Dragon Lake.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s12" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dark-eye Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>A large fish that lives in deep sea and only spawns in shallow areas.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_s8" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue-fin Flatfish</ThingName>
			<Desc>Flatfish that is commonly seen in sea.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r9" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sea Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>Eel that is commonly seen in sea.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_r10" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Spotted Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>Rare eel that lives in sea. The spotted pattern is possibly caused by it feeding on volcanic ash at the bottom of the sea.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>River Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common shrimps, live in all fresh waters.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sea Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Common shrimps in the sea, with bigger size.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Purple Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that only live in mountains near the Skydome Palace.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp4" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Red Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Special red shell shrimps, can bear high temperature.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp5" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sand Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that live in the desert, with small size.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp6" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Acele Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that live near the great river, with small size.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp7" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blue Stripe Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that live near the Central Plain, not easy to catch.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp8" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yellow Spot Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that live near the Wild South, taste bitter.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp9" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blood Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that live in blood water, very fierce.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp10" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>High Blood Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>A shrimp that appears in the blood water on the mountains and only eats food of Fire element. Also shows up in other types of water due to its invasiveness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp11" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fluorescence Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that only appear at Five Dragon Pond on summer nights. Their body glow, which is said because they only eat Metal element food.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Shrimp12" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Peach Shrimp</ThingName>
			<Desc>Shrimps that only appear at Perennial Miasma in springs. Their pink bodies are effected by peach blossom.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>