<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_WuDuZhuXianSword" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Venombane</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato perverso registrado no Livro dos Cem Venenos. Primeiro, uma incubação de espada é formada pela mistura de nove Phoenixwood com um certo número de Beast Blood que combina com as trinta e seis estrelas celestiais. Então, cinco Espíritos Primordiais altamente venenosos de Snake Demons são necessários para torná-lo no produto final. Ao atacar alguém com esta espada, sua brisa venenosa pode até penetrar na Barreira de Qi e causar danos diretamente ao inimigo.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Mate 5 Demônios Cobra carregando este item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>A cada 15 golpes, ele atacará o próprio corpo do cultivador, penetrando no escudo e causando dano adicional.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_BaiLingZhanXianSword" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Immortal Slayer</ThingName>
			<Desc>Técnica de espada antiga transmitida da antiga Seita Wutai. É feito primeiro derretendo dez Cristais Espirituais junto com uma Pérola da Alma para formar uma Incubação de Espadas e, em seguida, sacrificando as Bênçãos de cem seres vivos a ela. Cada vez que a espada é usada, sua Bênção e poder aumentarão gradualmente, até serem infundidos com Qi novamente.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Mate 100 seres vivos durante a incubação.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>O poder base do artefato é aumentado em 1% a cada 1 segundo que a espada continua voando. O efeito é limpo quando retorna.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ShiErShaShenMoLingSha" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sand of Destruction</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato cruel registrado no Livro dos Cem Venenos. Ele é criado misturando primeiro milhares de libras de Pó de Igneocobre com os cinco Líquidos Espirituais e os prepara em um pequeno saco de Pó Espiritual, depois sacrificando doze seres vivos com nível de cultivo do Espírito Primordial para incitar a ferocidade. Ao usar este artefato, pode-se poluir o artefato de seu oponente, tornando-o indisponível por um período de tempo.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Mate 12 seres vivos com Espírito Primordial enquanto carrega a incubação.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Para cada 12 ataques em um mesmo artefato, ele pode desabilitar o alvo por um determinado período de tempo correspondente ao seu nível.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianMoHuaXueShenDao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Bloodsucker</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato perverso do reino dos Demônios. Primeiro, milhares de quilos de essência de Igneocobre são refinados em uma incubação. Então, a essência yang primordial de 27 seres vivos masculinos é necessária para formar seu espírito. Ao usar este artefato, quanto menor for a Saúde de um, maior será o poder do artefato.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Mate 27 seres vivos do sexo masculino enquanto carrega esta incubação rara.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Para cada 1% de Vida menor, o Poder do Artefato aumenta em 5%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_YinHunZhu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Vortex Orb</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato do Legado Secreto transmitido da antiga escola demoníaca do Blood Master Searcher. Ele é criado combinando 9 Soul Pearls enquanto utiliza rancores como catalisador para formar um pequeno orbe e, em seguida, aproveitar as vidas de 36 seres vivos com o nível de cultivo do Espírito Primordial. Ao matar com este orbe, pode-se gradualmente incitar a ferocidade dentro dele. Cada pessoa morta aumentará seu poder em 10%, até um máximo de 36 pilhas. No entanto, um único dia sem sangue e ele voltará a dormir.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Mate 36 seres vivos com o Espírito Primordial enquanto carrega a incubação.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Cada ser vivo morto aumentará seu poder em 10%, até um máximo de 36 acúmulos. O efeito é cancelado se não beber sangue por 1 dia.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_JiuTianYuanYangChi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heavenly Measure</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato guardião passado por Guangcheng Zi, o imortal dourado do Culto Chan. Tem nove flores douradas e um fio de Qi roxo morando nela. Cada flor dourada é congelada da essência de um Núcleo Lumina, enquanto o Qi roxo é refinado do Sopro da Tribulação. A cada nove ataques com este artefato lançará um fio de yang Qi para atacar o próprio corpo do alvo com um poder terrível.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Refinar a incubação espiritual 9 vezes.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Cada 9º ataque lançará um feitiço no inimigo alvo.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_LongXinYinYangGui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Draconic Tablet</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato Legado inspirado nos restos do espírito primordial do Dragão da Tocha. Seu núcleo é formado pela condensação de cem libras de Jade e a essência do Torch Dragon juntos, auxiliados pelo poder de mudança aproveitado de nove meios-dias e meia-noites consecutivos para se tornar espírito. Melhora significativamente a compreensão da proteção.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Refinamento de espectro ao meio-dia ou meia-noite com sucesso por 9 dias contínuos.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Nível de habilidade de proteção aumentado em 10.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_DaiShenZhu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Illusion Sphere</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato de Legado transmitido do Livro dos Cem Venenos. Usando uma Besta Soul Pearl como base, ela é fundida com drogas dos Cinco Elementos para formar um núcleo. O orbe é então infundido com drogas dos Cinco Elementos sucessivamente com a técnica de refinamento do espírito. Embora o objeto não possa ser usado para atacar nem defender, ele pode trazê-lo de volta da morte uma vez em caso de calamidade fatal. Muito misterioso.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Tente refinar espiritualmente o artefato 25 vezes.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Ao custo de ser destruído, desafie a morte uma vez e restaure todo o dano causado a você.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_QiJueShenZhen" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Needles of Tribulation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato criado pelos antigos cultivadores para lutar contra o próprio céu com suas vidas. Sete agulhas divinas foram congeladas a partir de sete materiais preciosos, que são então repetidamente temperados para atingir um estado entre tangibilidade e intangibilidade e fundidos em uma incubação. Devido ao conflito entre as propriedades físicas, a agulha divina neste ponto teria se tornado um objeto mortal novamente. Seu poder precisa ser reativado gradualmente através do refinamento do espectro para que ele seja concluído. Ao usar este artefato, quanto mais próximo você estiver do fim de sua vida útil, mais poderoso ele se tornará.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Refinar com sucesso o artefato 11 vezes.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Quanto mais próximo o usuário estiver da vida útil máxima, mais poderoso será o artefato.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_XiXingShenSuo" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Stardust Shuttle</ThingName>
			<Desc>Artefato secreto do antigo Culto Taiyin. Uma incubação é forjada combinando a essência do Cristal de Gelo com os canais meridianos da cauda de um Dragão de Inundação, e então nutrida com o sopro de uma donzela. Ao atacar com este artefato, uma parte do dano causado pode ser convertida no próprio Qi do artefato.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Carregado e nutrido por uma menina solteira por um ano.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>10% do dano causado será reposto no Qi do artefato.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TaiYiFenGuangJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Borealis</ThingName>
			<Desc>Divine sword passed on from an ancient Taoist school. Refine a thousand pound of jade mixed with a hundred ounce of Jade Essence jade to congeal into a sword incubation, and then quench it with the power of Heavenly Tribulation to create Swordsprite. Once drawn, the sword will split out multiple swordsprites. Very miraculous.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Survive 7 Ascension Tribulations while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>For every 7 attacks, generate a swordsprite that lasts 7 seconds.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_WuqiLeiFu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Thunder Talisman</ThingName>
			<Desc>Ancient artifact of the Mystic Unity Sect. After drawing the talisman with Divine Mind, on shall harness the power of Heavenly Tribulation of Five Elements to make it spiritual. Significantly improves one's comprehension of Spell.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Survive a Heavenly Tribulation of Metal element while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.1.des>Survive a Heavenly Tribulation of Wood element while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.1.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.2.des>Survive a Heavenly Tribulation of Water element while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.2.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.3.des>Survive a Heavenly Tribulation of Fire element while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.3.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.4.des>Survive a Heavenly Tribulation of Earth element while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.4.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Spell skill level increased by 10.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_JinFabao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>White Cloud Banner</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the five Vast Banners. It uses bone of Phoenix as the pole, drawing with Sagacity Fruit essence on a Tough Demon Beast Hide as the flag, and then utilized the power of a Tier I Golden Core of Earth element in the making to complete itself. Although this one is a copy, it's still quite marvelous. This artifact deals double damage to targets of Wood element.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Generate a Tier I Golden Core of Earth element while carrying this incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Increases damage to targets of Wood element by 100%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_MuFabao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Green Lotus Banner</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the five Vast Banners. It uses bone of Phoenix as the pole, drawing with Gnarled Vine essence on a Tough Demon Beast Hide as the flag, and then utilized the power of a Tier I Golden Core of Water element in the making to complete itself. Although this one is a copy, it's still quite marvelous. This artifact deals double damage to targets of Earth element.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Generate a Tier I Golden Core of Water element while carrying this incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Increases damage to targets of Earth element by 100%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ShuiFabao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Black Vulture Banner</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the five Vast Banners. It uses bone of Phoenix as the pole, drawing with Prismatic Lotus essence on a Tough Demon Beast Hide as the flag, and then utilized the power of a Tier I Golden Core of Metal element in the making to complete itself. Although this one is a copy, it's still quite marvelous. This artifact deals double damage to targets of Fire element.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Generate a Tier I Golden Core of Metal element while carrying this incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Increases damage to targets of Fire element by 100%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_HuoFabao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Soaring Flame Banner</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the five Vast Banners. It uses bone of Phoenix as the pole, drawing with Crimson Fruit essence on a Tough Demon Beast Hide as the flag, and then utilized the power of a Tier I Golden Core of Wood element in the making to complete itself. Although this one is a copy, it's still quite marvelous. This artifact deals double damage to targets of Metal element.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Generate a Tier I Golden Core of Wood element while carrying this incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Increases damage to targets of Metal element by 100%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TuFabao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yellow Apricot Banner</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the five Vast Banners. It uses bone of Phoenix as the pole, drawing with Ochre Essence on a Tough Demon Beast Hide as the flag, and then utilized the power of a Tier I Golden Core of Fire element in the making to complete itself. Although this one is a copy, it's still quite marvelous. This artifact deals double damage to targets of Water element.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Generate a Tier I Golden Core of Fire element while carrying this incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Increases damage to targets of Water element by 100%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_JinLianShenZuo" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Golden Lotus Stand</ThingName>
			<Desc>Long-lost Legacy Artifact of Buddhist tradition. Using Prismatic Lotus as the incubation, it is infused with thirty-six Dark Scales of Flood Dragon, and then nurtured with its own essence to become spiritual. This artifact has such a huge Qi Capacity that, although it cannot be used to attack, it can protect one's body from any artifact damage.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Spend 100,000 stamina while carrying this artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Surrounding the whole body, it focuses on defense and will not attack.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TunLingShenJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Spellbound Scissors</ThingName>
			<Desc>Amazing artifact crafted by ancient Taoist school that imitated the Spellbound Beasts. This artifact was created by using 2 Flood Dragon's Horns as the basis and then smelting ten thousand pounds of Spirit Stone to quench it into being. The more Qi spent while using this artifact, the more powerful it becomes.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Spend a total of 100,000,000 Qi while carrying the incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>For every 10,000 Qi consumed, damage is increased by 10%, up to a maximum of 1000%. The effect is reset when replenishing Qi to the artifact.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ShenNongDing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Cauldron of the Harvest</ThingName>
			<Desc>It is said to be a imitation of the cauldron used by Divine Farmer of old. The cauldron's body is carved out of Divine Jade, and forged by using Phoenix Fire Jade as the Spark of fire while combined with the powerful potency from ten thousands pounds of Spirit Leaf. When using this artifact, the more types of Elixir the user has taken, the more extent to which they will be able to stimulate its power.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Concoct 36 Elixirs while carrying the incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>For each kind of Elixir consumed, its power is increased by 5%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_QingNingFeiYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Feather of Agility</ThingName>
			<Desc>Precious artifact from the Otherworld. Combine Phoenix's Oblivion Feather and Mantle Feather, and then neutralize its blaze with the essence of ten thousand pounds of Purity Leaf to create the incubation. Which then needs to undergo a process of closed-door self-training in a quiet and tranquil location in order to become spiritual. When using this artifact to attack, there is a chance of activating Breath of Tranquility to compensate yourself, reducing Spell Cast Delay by 1 second.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Stay on Heavenstep Peak for 36 days while carrying the incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Every 2 attacks reduce skill cooldown by 1 second.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_YuanShenXinJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Truthbringer</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret artifact of Buddhist tradition according to legends. Skeleton remains left by ascended immortals are used as the core, which is then infused into 99 swords. More than a hundred years of meditation with a Heart of Sword is then needed for it to become a spirit. Significantly improves one's Comprehension in Sword Mastery.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Meditate for 360 years while carrying the incubation.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Sword Mastery skill level increased by 10.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ZhuXianJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ragestriker</ThingName>
			<Desc>Divine blade passed on from ancient times. Although this one is a copy, it possesses deadly killing power nonetheless. This sword used Flood Dragon's Horn as the core, combined with nine Lumina Cores to create the incubation of Metal element, which then absorbs Celestial Thunders to become spiritual. Its power multiplies when fighting against enemies that are also using artifacts. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Thunderstorm)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Thunderstorm 9 times.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Deals 1.5x damage when fighting against other artifacts.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_LuXianJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Deathbringer</ThingName>
			<Desc>Divine blade passed on from ancient times. Although this one is a copy, it possesses deadly killing power nonetheless. This sword used Flood Dragon's Horn as the core, combined with a hundred pound of Fire Essence ore to create the incubation of Fire element, which then absorbs Foehn Wind to become spiritual. There is a chance of spirit power spike occurring when attacking with it, dealing multiplied damage. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Foehn Wind)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Foehn Wind 9 times.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>When dealing damage, there is a 10% chance of dealing 5x damage.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_XianXianJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Endless Fury</ThingName>
			<Desc>Divine blade passed on from ancient times. Although this one is a copy, it possesses deadly killing power nonetheless. This sword used Flood Dragon's Horn as the core, combined with nine branches of Phoenixwood to create the incubation of Wood element, which then absorbs Noxious Air to become spiritual. Its attacks are accompanied by a power of corrosion, dealing additional damage to Qi Barrier. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Noxious Air)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Noxious Air 9 times.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Deals 1.5x damage when attacking the enemy's body itself.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_JueXianJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Wrathbringer</ThingName>
			<Desc>Divine blade passed on from ancient times. Although this one is a copy, it possesses deadly killing power nonetheless. This sword used Flood Dragon's Horn as the core, combined with nine Holy Stones to create the incubation of Earth element, which then absorbs Sandstorms to become spiritual. When launching an attack, there is a small chance of dealing a special damage, the amount of which is relative to the enemy's Qi. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Sandstorm)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Sandstorm 9 times.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>When attacking the enemy's body itself, there is a 1% chance of dealing an additional damage that is equal to 30% of the current target's Qi.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianLangDing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sirius Spike</ThingName>
			<Desc>Wicked artifact from another realm. Using the remaining evilness left by ascended immortal as the catalyst, the essence of Gnarled Vine's power is condensed onto a Demon Wolf's Fang. Nurture it with your own essence to make it spiritual. This artifact is extremely thin and sensitive when being used in battle. Once triggered, it will split into 9 apparitions to attack the enemy. It is a vicious weapon. (Once equipped, right click to feed essence to it)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Feed the artifact 18 times with your essence.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>For every 3 attacks, generates 9 spike apparitions that last 3 seconds.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianShu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Dubhe</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Power. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Power Bonus by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianQuan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Megrez</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Qi. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Qi Bonus by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianJi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Phegda</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact's Knockback Resistance. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact's Knockback Resistance by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianXuan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Merak</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Turn Speed. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Turn Speed by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_YuHeng" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Alioth</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Qi Recovery Rate. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Qi Recovery Rate by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_KaiYang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Mizar</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Knockback. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Knockback by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_YaoGuang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Elkeid</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the divine weapons of Grand Chariot passed on from ancient times. One may use Flood Dragon's Claw along with forty-nine units of Darksteel to create the incubation, and then harness the power of the Grand Chariot stars to make it spiritual, fundamentally improving its Artifact Fly Speed. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Grand Chariot Starlight)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Grand Chariot Starlight continuously for 7 days.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Fundamentally increases your Artifact Fly Speed by 30%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_KuiHuaShenJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Unus</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret sword forged according to the Sunflower Refining Law, it is made by carving and piecing 3 Divine Jade together and mounted with 1 Fortune Seed. It then needs to absorb the breath of Polar Night Ouroboros to become a spirit. Every time this sword is used against the enemy, the first strike is several times of its original power. (Once equipped, right click to try to absorb Breath of Polar Night)</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Absorb Breath of Polar Night 12 times.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Power of first sword strike increased by 500%. The effect is reset when replenishing Qi to the artifact.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ZhuXianZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Slayer's Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Ragestriker Formation. It is said to be the most ruthless Formation of all on ancient battlefields, being virtually invincible and unstoppable.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_QiXingZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Conqueror's Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Conqueror's Formation. It is said to be capable of harnessing the Grand Chariot's divine light of Aloofness, which grants it omniscient demon-slaying powers.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_TianDiWuFangZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Impregnable Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Impregnable Formation. It is said to be capable of deploying a indestructible field with the Five Directional Banners of Heaven and Earth to protect anything in the universe.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_LiuYuZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Divine Law Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Divine Law Formation. It is said to be a Formation of divinators of the six gods of Celestial Court, capable of turning the Mortal Realm into a paradise and making people live in spiritual harmony.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_LongXingZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dragonrider Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret Formation Diagram that records the Dragonrider Formation. It is said to be a dragon controlling Formation. When deployed, one can draw the power of Dragonsoul to perform some powerful Formation miracles.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_FengHunZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Phoenix Sword Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Phoenix Sword Formation. It is said to be a phoenix-controlling formation. When deployed, one can draw the power of Phoenixsoul to perform some powerful Formation miracles.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_YinYangZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yin Yang Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Yin Yang Formation. It is said that this Formation is deployed according to the Rule of Yin and Yang. Utilizing the transformation of Yin and Yang, the Formation becomes extremely flexible.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_SanYinZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dark Force Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret Formation Diagram that records the Dark Force Formation. It is said to be a Formation formed by pure Yin energy, which can greatly enhance your power.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_BaMenZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Abyssal Sword Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret Formation Diagram that records the Abyssal Sword Formation. It is said to be a Formation that is deployed according to the rules of the Eight Trigram Gates, with both offensive and defensive capabilities. Very miraculous.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ShenMuZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Wood Spirit Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Wood Spirit Formation. It is said to be a Formation capable of awakening the Qi of vitality among heaven and earth, rejuvenating all living things.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_WuYueZhenTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Convergence Formation</ThingName>
			<Desc>Secret chart of Formation Diagram that records the Convergence Formation. It's said that once deployed, this Formation presents the form of the Five Peaks to ward a location, rendering it indestructible.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspiration</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to meditated on the Formation Diagram.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_BaBaoGongDe" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Merit</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Pool of the Eight Virtues, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_WanDaoZunFaZuo" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Law</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Throne of Ten Thousand Taos, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_QiQingQingTongShu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Emotion</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Sacred Wood of Emotions, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_ZhouTianXingDouPan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of the Stars</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Astral Plate of Universal Cycle, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_WuLongXuanJinTa" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of the Sun</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Draconic Pagoda of Yang, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_ShuShanJianChi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of the Sword</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Blue Lotus Pool of Sword, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_LingYuFeng" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Numinous Peak, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_WanGuXieFaTan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Crimson</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Altar of Deathly Sorcery, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_XuanCiTianKeng" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of Stone</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Crater of Meta-magnetic, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_QiShaShenBei" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of the Seven-Slaughtering</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Divine Stele of Seven Slaughters, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_XuanYinShengQuan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Heart of the Moon</ThingName>
			<Desc>The true essence formed in the Sacred Spring of Yin, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_YaoZuYiHai" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ancestral Yaoguai's Remains</ThingName>
			<Desc>The concentrated substance formed by the remaining spirit within the Ancestral Yaoguai's Remains, which is also the root of all its profoundness.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_QianKunLingJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Universe Spirit Crystal</ThingName>
			<Desc>A strange crystal with a mysterious power of space dwelling within it. It seems to have some special uses.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>