<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPracticeBase" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Base</ThingName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_TaiXu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Illusion Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Energies left behind by the power of creation from the beginning of heaven and earth. This kind of peculiar essence is very hard to find nowadays.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XuanTian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Nimbus Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Energies left behind by the power of creation from the beginning of heaven and earth. This kind of peculiar essence is very hard to find nowadays.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_JieMie" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Tribulation Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence with the power of annihilation, can only be collected in a heavenly tribulation.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_JiuYang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ignis Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The most condensed energy in the blazing sun, very difficult to collect.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XuanYue" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Aqualuna Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The most condensed energy in the freezing moon, very difficult to collect.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_TaiYang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Solar Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence of the Sun, can only be collected at midday.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_TaiYin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Lunar Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence of the Moon, can only be collected at midnight.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_EXJin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Innate Metal Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the primordial essence of the Five Elements, can only be found in environments and items with very strong Metal element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_EXMu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Innate Wood Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the primordial essence of the Five Elements, can only be found in environments and items with very strong Wood element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_EXShui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Innate Water Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the primordial essence of the Five Elements, can only be found in environments and items with very strong Water element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_EXHuo" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Innate Fire Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the primordial essence of the Five Elements, can only be found in environments and items with very strong Fire element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_EXTu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Innate Earth Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the primordial essence of the Five Elements, can only be found in environments and items with very strong Earth element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Jin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Metal Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the acquired essence of the Five Elements. They can be collected anywhere in the world if you just look for it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Mu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Wood Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the acquired essence of the Five Elements. They can be collected anywhere in the world if you just look for it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Shui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Water Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the acquired essence of the Five Elements. They can be collected anywhere in the world if you just look for it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Huo" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fire Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the acquired essence of the Five Elements. They can be collected anywhere in the world if you just look for it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Tu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Earth Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>One of the acquired essence of the Five Elements. They can be collected anywhere in the world if you just look for it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_FengShuiLing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blessed Feng Shui Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that only slowly forms in places with the most exceptional Feng Shui.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_FengShuiSha" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Cursed Feng Shui Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that only slowly forms in places with the most horrible Feng Shui.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Chun" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Germination Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that naturally forms between heaven and earth as the seasons flow, representing the energies of sprouting in spring.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Xia" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blossom Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that naturally forms between heaven and earth as the seasons flow, representing the energies of florescence in summer.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Qiu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Withering Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that naturally forms between heaven and earth as the seasons flow, representing the energies of deterioration in autumn.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Dong" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Reversion Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that naturally forms between heaven and earth as the seasons flow, representing the energies of desolation in winter.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_YongYe" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Everlasting Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Mysterious essence that permeate the space between heaven and earth in the Polar Night. Their exact origin is unknown, as if do not belong to this world.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_JiaoLongYuanJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Flood Dragon Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that contains Flood Dragon's mystery of life, which could be a great reference for Physical Cultivators.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XiongFengYuanJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Phoenix Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that contains Phoenix's mystery of life, which could be a great reference for Physical Cultivators.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ZhuLongYuanJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Torch Dragon Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence that contains Torch Dragon's mystery of life, which could be a great reference for Physical Cultivators.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_GuShouJingXue" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ancient Beast's Blood Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>A drop of blood essence from the Ancient Beast, it contains the mystery of its powerful body.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_GuShouGuFen" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ancient Beast's Bone Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Some powder made from bones of the Ancient Beast, it contains the mystery of its powerful body.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_DaYaoYuanJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yaoguai Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence inside the body of a monster with great cultivation, it may contain the secrets of Yaoguai's innately strong bodies.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ShengMingLv1" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Pure Life Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence of pure vitality, it can be a great supplement to your body.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ShengMingLv2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Intrinsic Life Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>A wisp of the original intrinsic essence of postnatal lives.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ShengMingLv3" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Destiny Life Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Breath of life that naturally generate between heaven and earth. It is also the source of primordial lives.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_SiWang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Wraith Breath</ThingName>
			<Desc>After the death of a living being, part of its intrinsic life force will diffuse into heaven and earth, while the other part will transform into this substance.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_WuHui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Filth Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Although the origin of this substance is obscure, it is also a concentration of all living beings' turbid energies, which embodied the profound mystery of reincarnation and changes.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_WuXing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ethereal Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>A very peculiar essence, invisible and intangible, but truly exist. Can be extracted from ethereal items.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XianDaoJingHua" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Immortal Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>Collective term for the products of all kinds of essence in the world being processed with Qi by Golden Core cultivators. Due to the infusion of Qi, these essence are ineffective to Physical cultivators. If one forcefully use these essence to Remold body, it will cause the cultivation progress of the designated body part to nullify due to the Qi repulsion effect, reversing it to its original state.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XianSui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Immortal Marrow</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence of the Immortal Body formed by a Golden Core cultivator. The extremely strong effect of this substance will create an intense stimulation in Physical cultivators. It's not known what might happen if one uses it for Remolding.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ShenSui" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Divine Marrow</ThingName>
			<Desc>Essence of the Divine Body formed by a Shendao cultivator. The extremely strong effect of this substance will create an intense stimulation in Physical cultivators. It's not known what might happen if one uses it for Remolding.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_BaBao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Universe Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of universe.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_WanDao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Genesis Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the creation of cosmos.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_QiQing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yin Yang Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of Yin and Yang.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_ZhouTian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Spacetime Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the derivation of time.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XuanYang" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Begin-end Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of beginning and end.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_Jian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Life-death Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of life and death.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_LingYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Thriving Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the thriving of beings.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_WanGu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Nullification Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the nullification of time.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XuanCi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Desolation Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the desolation of cosmos.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_QiSha" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Obliteration Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of the obliteration of beings.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BodyPractice_XuanYin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Destiny Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>In the beginning, at the creation of cosmos, everything evolves. This is the essence manifested from the evolution of the ways of creation and formation.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>