<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Item_WuDang_HuangJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Soil Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>A sweet and refreshing herb that can not only reduce hunger but also replenish nutrients. Thought to be Ganoderma by immortals, the herb is known as Soil Essence because it absorbs the essence of the earth.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Fruit, Bead, Bolus, Ball</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_WuDang_HuangJingFen" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Soil Essence Powder</ThingName>
			<Desc>Ground powder of dried Soil Essence. Though slightly potent, it's more often used to concoct elixirs.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Sand, Crystal, Dust, Powder, Miasma</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_WeaponFuChen" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Fly-Whisk</ThingName>
			<Desc>A fly-whisk often used by immortals and Taoists.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Soft. Whisk</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_WeaponDaoSword" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sword of Tao</ThingName>
			<Desc>A sword compatible with magic that is specifically used for Taoist rituals.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Sword</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_XuanTianShangDiPai" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Sacred Nimbus Plate</ThingName>
			<Desc>A pendant plate engraved with the sacred title of Perfected Warrior Emperor. Wear to obtain the Emperor's blessings and improve Luck and Mental State.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Plate</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Dan_WuQiNoHunger2" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Qi Fasting Pill</ThingName>
			<Desc>A secret fasting pill of the Wudang Mountains. Compared with normal fasting pills, it lasts longer (for a total of 30 days).</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Dan_SanHuaHuangJing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Trimerous Essence Pill</ThingName>
			<Desc>A secret elixir of the Wudang Mountains. Take to increase Max Qi by a fixed amount. Though it's not very useful to experienced cultivators, it's recommended to help lay foundations for new disciples. But its effect will be significantly decreased if taken multiple times.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ZhenWuDangMoShenJian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Perfected Warrior Sword</ThingName>
			<Desc>Also known as the Exorcist Prime, the Perfected Warrior used this precious sword to expel all evils. About 3 inches long, the sword is reforged from jade stones with the true powers of exorcism; it thus has an imposing purplish glow around it. Once drawn, it transforms into inch-long violet lightening bolts that destroy everything they touch.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Kill 1 Snake Demon while carrying this item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.1.des>Kill 1 Wolf Demon while carrying this item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.1.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.2.des>Kill 1 Bear Demon while carrying this item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.2.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.3.des>Kill 1 Turtle Demon while carrying this item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.3.des>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.4.des>Kill 1 Boar Demon while carrying this item.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.4.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Deals 3x damage when attacking alien races (non-human races).</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.1.Desc>Deals 3x damage when equipped by a human.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.1.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_MiBao_ZiXiaoChi" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Purple Cloud Measure</ThingName>
			<Desc>A secret artifact of Wudang Sect. Carved from a complete Holy Stone, the measure has scales engraved with 7 Heaven's Breaths and astral powers and is forged after 7 Heavenly Tribulations. Once mastered, the artifact can be used to measure the contributions of all lives with the creed of heaven, and even speed up the enemy's Heavenly Tribulation.</Desc>
			<Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>Survive 7 Ascension Tribulations while carrying an artifact.</Item.Fabao.ActiveCondition.0.des>
			<Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>Attacks deal damage based on the difference between the Attainment of both sides. A gap of 1 Attainment increases damage by 1%.</Item.Fabao.SpecialAbility.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_SkySnake" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Cloud Eel</ThingName>
			<Desc>A special eel unique to the Sea of Clouds. Since Qi fills its body, the eel's meat is as soft and light as air.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Surimi,Fish,Bone</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_SkyFish" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Night Carp</ThingName>
			<Desc>A carp that lives in the clouds and only shows up at night.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fish_SkyCrab" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Golden Claw</ThingName>
			<Desc>A crab that lives in the Sea of Clouds and has the toughest body. It's said they feed on the lightning energy in the clouds.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_XuanWuEgg" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Black Tortoise Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>A jade sent by the Wudang Sect as a gift. It seems to be one of a set of items.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspect</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Inspect Black Tortoise Jade</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Wonder_ZhenWuShenNian" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Perfected Guidance</ThingName>
			<Desc>A small amount of Perfected Guidance. It can be used to build the Perfected Warrior Statue.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>