<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="NoDEnv">
			<DisplayName>Plains</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Temperate plains with rich flora and fauna, as well as a diverse ecosystem.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Valley">
			<DisplayName>Canyon</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A canyon in the mountain range with few trees and soil not conducive to plant growth.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Forest">
			<DisplayName>Forest</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Dense jungle fraught with greenery and wild animals, but lacks in mineral veins.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Wet">
			<DisplayName>Wetland</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Mudflats on the edge of great lakes, with fertile soil and vast waters.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Battle">
			<DisplayName>Ancient Battlefield</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having been the scene of protracted and bloody battles resulting in countless casualties, this place is under the heavy influence of curse and fury. Some of the dead bodies may come alive at night due to the dense Yin Qi…</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Desert">
			<DisplayName>Desert</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Covered with level sand, this place is hot and arid. Although the land is barren, there are large deposits of spirit stones.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="HighLand">
			<DisplayName>Plateau</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This area is at a high altitude with low temperatures and a thin distribution of spiritual water.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NoDMemonto">
			<DisplayName>None</DisplayName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="HotPot">
			<DisplayName>Fiery Chasm</DisplayName>
			<Desc>There is a natural cavern here that leads all the way down to the core of the earth. The high temperature surrounding it is unbearble. May cause adverse weather.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ColdHole">
			<DisplayName>Frozen Furnace</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A forgotten furnace frozen with ice that never melts, emitting cold air ceaselessly. May cause adverse weather.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="OuterWorld">
			<DisplayName>Otherworld Rift</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Space here has been shattered due to a battle between powerful sages, leaving an Otherworld Rift allowing items or cultivator from other planes passing it from time to time.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingShu">
			<DisplayName>Illumitree</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A curious plant named Illumitree grows here. It can turn soil nearby into spiritual soil. However, the pollen it releases may cause blocked meridians and suppressed Qi.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YinYang">
			<DisplayName>Yin Yang Stela</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A fascinating stone construct shaped by the natural flow of Yin and Yang is located here, embodying a profound secret. However, whenever someone tries to study it, a weather anomaly will emerge.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="DiMu">
			<DisplayName>Earthmother Shrine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Heartland of the ancient cult of Earthmother, and there is still a shrine dedicated to her. One can make a wish to the remnant of Earthmother’s will by offering it with Spirit Stones, although this may bring natural disasters.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NoDAnimal">
			<DisplayName>None</DisplayName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Fei">
			<DisplayName>Fei</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The temperature here rarely fluctuates, attracting Fei to inhabit this place.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Lushu">
			<DisplayName>Lushu</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The temperature here varies greatly, attracting Lushu to inhabit this place.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>