<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Pessimism">
			<DisplayName>Pessimist</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is very pessimistic, always assuming the worst.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Optimistic">
			<DisplayName>Optimist</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is very optimistic, always looking on the bright side.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Numbness">
			<DisplayName>Numb</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The stresses of day-to-day living have left this person feeling numb. However, this means that [IT] is even tired of thinking at all, is used to this numbness, and will not slack in their work due to their low spirits.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Sensitive">
			<DisplayName>Sensitive</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is very curious about the world beyond, and cannot bear to live out a dull life.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Enthusiasm">
			<DisplayName>Amiable</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is very friendly towards everyone.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Distrust">
			<DisplayName>Withdrawn</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] does not believe in true love, or place their trust in anybody.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Strong">
			<DisplayName>Strong</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is strong-willed and can endure greater suffering than others.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Weak">
			<DisplayName>Weak</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] has always been sheltered and cannot bear the slightest pain.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="BadMentality">
			<DisplayName>Ill-tempered</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is always too irritated to get any work done.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GoodMentality">
			<DisplayName>Good-tempered</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] has a good temper, and is not easily annoyed or saddened.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Rugged">
			<DisplayName>Careless</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is careless in their work, always finishing fast and paying little attention to the details.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Careful">
			<DisplayName>Meticulous</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is very meticulous in their work, always taking time to improve the details.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Lazy">
			<DisplayName>Lazy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] does not want to work.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Industrious">
			<DisplayName>Hardworking</DisplayName>
			<Desc>[IT] is hardworking and efficient.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Feminization">
			<DisplayName>Effeminate</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Despite being a man, [IT] has a somewhat feminine manner and personality.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Masculinity">
			<DisplayName>Masculine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Despite being a woman, [IT] has a somewhat masculine manner and personality.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Affinity">
			<DisplayName>Agreeable</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is very agreeable and charming.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Cruel">
			<DisplayName>Harsh</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is very harsh, often upsetting other people.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="HeartKnot">
			<DisplayName>Troubled</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person has a troubled soul, always depressed and sleep-deprived as a result of their nightmares.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Depressed">
			<DisplayName>Unhappy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person has gone through a very bad breakup and is always unhappy.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Anatman">
			<DisplayName>Liberated</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person has reached a mental state of liberation, free from worldly troubles.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FearFlame">
			<DisplayName>Pyrophobia</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is extremely afraid of fire and cannot do any fire-related work.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>