<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="JuQing_dialogue_0">
			<Nodes.0.Text>Entrance</Nodes.0.Text>
			<Nodes.1.Text>What do you want to know?</Nodes.1.Text>
			<Nodes.2.Text>Who are you?</Nodes.2.Text>
			<Nodes.3.Text>What is this place?</Nodes.3.Text>
			<Nodes.4.Text>What exactly is the Universe?</Nodes.4.Text>
			<Nodes.5.Text>What is the Book of Heavenly Edicts?</Nodes.5.Text>
			<Nodes.6.Text>Me? I'm just a failure who should have been buried in time. But since you are standing here, maybe I'm not such a failure? I decide the fate of Heaven, HAHAHA. You can call me Fu Pikong.</Nodes.6.Text>
			<Nodes.7.Text>Did you forget how you came in? This place, of course, is the Universe.</Nodes.7.Text>
			<Nodes.8.Text>Do you know there were two great wars between immortals and demons in ancient times?</Nodes.8.Text>
			<Nodes.9.Text>The Book of Heavenly Edicts is the symbol of power held by Eastern Palace's sect leaders. It is an unbreakable scroll made with otherworldly material. Maybe it has a different title in your time? But since you are here, the Book of Heavenly Edicts must have opened the portal for you.</Nodes.9.Text>
			<Nodes.10.Text>Open the Universe Realm? Why? Are the demons going to invade us again? But I don't think we need to panic. For generations, the world of cultivators has never been as prosperous as it is right now. There are disputes between large sects, but with a large number of powerful cultivators, we shouldn't be afraid of demons! Why escape?</Nodes.10.Text>
			<Nodes.11.Text>Fu Pikong? I think I've heard the name somewhere before.</Nodes.11.Text>
			<Nodes.12.Text>It's nothing strange. Two people could have the same name. It just proves that we are destined to meet!</Nodes.12.Text>
			<Nodes.13.Text>The Universe? Haven't heard of it. But I came via the secret device named "Mini Universe". Maybe it's connected to the Universe? I always thought the Mini Universe was just a storehouse.</Nodes.13.Text>
			<Nodes.14.Text>HAHA, the Universe is not that simple. It's a divine device unparalleled in this realm. Technically, this is the rift between the Universe and the Boundless Universe, the most special place amongst all the Bounded Universes. I left a spiritual catalyst as a secret gate connected to this place, which should be the Mini Universe you spoke of. I didn't expect it to be used as a storehouse now.</Nodes.14.Text>
			<Nodes.15.Text>What? What exactly is the Universe? How can it contain all the Bounded Universes? The Mini Universe is just a gate? How is that possible?</Nodes.15.Text>
			<Nodes.16.Text>*sneers* Everything is possible. You look like you don't know what I'm talking about. Those old-timers really kept everything secret? But since you're here, you must have been approved by the Book of Heavenly Edicts. I'll consider you trustworthy.</Nodes.16.Text>
			<Nodes.17.Text>Fu Pikong? I think I've heard the name somewhere before.</Nodes.17.Text>
			<Nodes.18.Text>You? Are you…</Nodes.18.Text>
			<Nodes.19.Text>Are you Fu Pikong, the last sect leader of Eastern Palace and the Emperor of Demons, who destroyed half of the cultivators' world all on his own?</Nodes.19.Text>
			<Nodes.20.Text>Oh, you know me? So the Eastern Palace's tradition lives on? But how is that possible?</Nodes.20.Text>
			<Nodes.21.Text>The Eastern Palace no longer exists, but its legacy lives on. It became the Taiyi Sect after a hundred years, and that is where I'm from. And I only came to know all the stories because I tried to seek revenge for the destroyed Taiyi Sect. (With some reservations, [NAME] told the man who claimed to be Fu Pikong about the history of Taiyi.)</Nodes.21.Text>
			<Nodes.22.Text>*sneers* I didn't think those old-timers could completely keep quiet about it, and they even hunted down every last one of our successors. Thankfully, we are blessed. Since you are my descendent, ask away if you've got any questions. And I also need your participation for future plans.</Nodes.22.Text>
			<Nodes.23.Text>The Universe? I haven't heard of it.</Nodes.23.Text>
			<Nodes.24.Text>The Universe? The Universe has been taken by Mt. Hundred Insects.</Nodes.24.Text>
			<Nodes.25.Text>The Universe? The Universe has been taken by Mt. Hundred Insects when the Taiyi Sect was destroyed. I came here through a storage device left in our sect called the Mini Universe.</Nodes.25.Text>
			<Nodes.26.Text>HAHA, the Universe is not that simple. It's a divine device crafted with all of our resources in Eastern Palace. Technically, this is the rift between the Universe and the Boundless Universe, the most special place amongst all the Bounded Universes. I left a spiritual catalyst as a secret gate connected to this place. I didn't expect it to be used as a storage device, what a brilliant disguise.</Nodes.26.Text>
			<Nodes.27.Text>So, does that mean the inside of the Universe is actually a whole? You can go in through any entrance?</Nodes.27.Text>
			<Nodes.28.Text>It's not really accurate, but your understanding isn't far off. The Universe is all connected inside, but you can't access it all you want. You couldn't have broken the seal and come here if you didn't have the approval of the Book of Heavenly Edicts.</Nodes.28.Text>
			<Nodes.29.Text>There's nothing wrong…</Nodes.29.Text>
			<Nodes.30.Text>Now that you mentioned it.</Nodes.30.Text>
			<Nodes.31.Text>I've heard about it, but we don't know much about what happened in the world of cultivators in ancient times, and people rarely talk about it. Only that the cultivators won the war and banished all the demons for eternity. Maybe the Universe was created during the Wars of Immortals and Demons?</Nodes.31.Text>
			<Nodes.32.Text>Banished all the demons for eternity? HAHAHA, interesting. That's a creative way to put it. But the truth is the opposite. We only barely won both wars, and it was generally believed that our realm could not hold off another invasion from the demons. That's why the cultivators in ancient times decided to put in all the resources and build a sanctuary.</Nodes.32.Text>
			<Nodes.33.Text>And you mean that's the Universe?</Nodes.33.Text>
			<Nodes.34.Text>Correct! The Universe is this sanctuary, a manmade Heavenly Abode that can accommodate millions of people to live in. But I didn't know that as time passed by, all the painful past would be forgotten, and our hard-won battle would be reduced to rumors about the eternal banishment of demons. *sigh*</Nodes.34.Text>
			<Nodes.35.Text>Could it be the Secret Codex of Taiyi? I didn't know this book was so important!</Nodes.35.Text>
			<Nodes.36.Text>Yes, that's it… (For a second, a strange look appeared on Fu Pikong's face.)</Nodes.36.Text>
			<Nodes.37.Text>[color=#ff0000]I felt the Nature is like Tide! Is it now? [/color]And Your plan?</Nodes.37.Text>
			<Nodes.38.Text>Finally, the time has come. What I do is just simple. I want to use the Book of Heavenly Edicts, or the Secret Codex of Taiyi, to completely open up the Universe with the order of Eastern Sovereign.</Nodes.38.Text>
			<Nodes.39.Text>Has never been as prosperous as it is right now? HAHAHAHA!</Nodes.39.Text>
			<Nodes.40.Text>What's so funny? You've probably been in slumber for too long to know what is going on out there. Numerous ancient sages have awoken and many true immortals roam the world. No matter how strong the realm of demons is, how can it compete with the cultivators now?</Nodes.40.Text>
			<Nodes.41.Text>HAHAHAHA, excuse me. Of course I know. After all, what is happening outside is the result of our wars. But let me ask you first, do you think there is something wrong with this world?</Nodes.41.Text>
			<Nodes.42.Text>Something wrong? What do you mean?</Nodes.42.Text>
			<Nodes.43.Text>I'll give you a hint. You look like you've practiced a lot, so during your daily practice, do you have any doubts?</Nodes.43.Text>
			<Nodes.44.Text>HAHAHA, how unsophisticated! But it's not your fault as you've been so used to it. Let me ask you, cultivation is against the Creed of Heaven, so when did it become so easy? True immortals and ancient cultivators are roaming the world?</Nodes.44.Text>
			<Nodes.45.Text>Now that you mentioned it, when I first started practicing, I did have some doubts. Why wasn't cultivation as difficult as it was recorded in ancient scrolls? According to the books, cultivation is against the Creed of Heaven and only one in a million can ascend toward immortality. But in fact, I've seen gifted cultivators ascend toward immortality in a month or so and become a Living God. I just became too used to it. Now that I think about it, it is truly incredible.</Nodes.45.Text>
			<Nodes.46.Text>Good, you are a promising kid. You could realize it, no wonder the Book of Heavenly Edicts chose you!</Nodes.46.Text>
			<Nodes.47.Text>Now that you mentioned it, many ancient scrolls say that cultivation is against the Creed of Heaven and only one in a million can ascend toward immortality. I once thought that ancient cultivators didn't master the practice and that was why it was so difficult. But come to think of it, I've seen gifted cultivators ascend toward immortality in a month or so and become a Living God. That is truly extraordinary and a bit strange.</Nodes.47.Text>
			<Nodes.48.Text>In fact, that is what's wrong with the world: Cultivation is against the Creed of Heaven. It's become so easy now because the Creed of Heaven in this world is too weak! Maybe you won't believe it, but the Creed in our world is broken.</Nodes.48.Text>
			<Nodes.50.Text>However, that is not the real problem. With the broken Creed of Heaven, our world is changing at a pace thousand times faster. Normally, a world should be able to last for billions of years. But our world will come to an end in only less than 10,000 years.</Nodes.50.Text>
			<Nodes.51.Text>Is that true? I can't believe it. So, the realm of demons is counting on our broken Creed of Heaven to invade us without sparing any effort? If it is true that our Creed of Heaven is broken, this world will be doomed. That's why you want to open up the Universe and enter the Bounded Universes to survive the catastrophe that is going to destroy the world?</Nodes.51.Text>
			<Nodes.52.Text>HAHAHA! Very imaginative! But unfortunately, you are wrong! On the contrary…</Nodes.52.Text>
			<Nodes.54.Text>You guessed it!</Nodes.54.Text>
			<Nodes.55.Text>Correct, that is the truth of this world. The broken Creed of Heaven isn't some plot of the demons. It is because this world is already broken. This world is the manmade realm in the Universe, and we are the group of people who escaped into it.</Nodes.55.Text>
			<Nodes.56.Text>No, no way. You mean the history I know is fabricated by all the sect leaders? We are living in a bottled world? How is that possible? How about all these rivers and plains? How about all my cultivation practice? And why should I believe what you say?</Nodes.56.Text>
			<Nodes.57.Text>It might sound heartless and cruel, but this world is nothing impressive. It's just a recreation that we made from one small part of the old universe, not even close to the magnificent Boundless Universe. You have earned a thousand years of life on earth, but you don't even know how profound the world is. But it doesn't matter.</Nodes.57.Text>
			<Nodes.59.Text>All right. Believe it or not, I've told you the truth I know of. I'm still alive now only because time does not apply here. Once I leave this place, time will catch up with me in an instant. So rest assured, I can't do anything about you. Now althought the time has come but it is still not the end. You will have enough time to decide whether you want to help me or not.</Nodes.59.Text>
			<Nodes.60.Text>[color=#ff0000]I felt the Nature is like Tide! Is it now? [/color]What on earth happened back then?</Nodes.60.Text>
			<Nodes.61.Text>What on earth happened back then? Rumors from all the sects say that demonic infestation drove you to destroy the world of cultivators and that's why you were banished by all. But I know the Five Elements paths in Taiyi Sect all come from you, and there is no sign of demonic infestation. The rumors aren't true. But I couldn't find more clues no matter how hard I tried.</Nodes.61.Text>
			<Nodes.62.Text>Demonic infestation? What a convenient excuse! Though it is a bit cliche. It's not completely wrong to say that I wanted to destroy the world of cultivators.</Nodes.62.Text>
			<Nodes.63.Text>So you were really planning to eliminate all cultivators? And it is also the reason why you will return this time?</Nodes.63.Text>
			<Nodes.64.Text>It is a long story. But before that, I will show you the truth of the world.</Nodes.64.Text>
			<Nodes.65.Text>The truth about this world?</Nodes.65.Text>
			<Nodes.66.Text>Let me ask you. Have you ever thought that there is something wrong with our world?</Nodes.66.Text>
			<Nodes.67.Text>What should I do?</Nodes.67.Text>
			<Nodes.68.Text>Hello, young one. Since you are here, it is either the world's end or that you are the most blessed person in the world. I've lost count of how many years have passed, and finally, here we are.</Nodes.68.Text>
			<Nodes.69.Text>The time has come, recently the distance between me and the real Boundless Universe is the shortest. Then you can give me the Book of Heavenly Edicts, I mean the Secret Codex of Taiyi. I will open up the Universe with the power of the Book of Heavenly Edicts, and then we can escape from this realm and return to the real Boundless Universe.</Nodes.69.Text>
			<Nodes.70.Text>So, what's the price?</Nodes.70.Text>
			<Nodes.71.Text>You already know that, don't you? By then, the Creed of Heaven here will return to the Boundless Universe. Our cultivation all comes from meditating on this realm, so we will lose all of our attainment, become mortal and start all over again.</Nodes.71.Text>
			<Nodes.72.Text>*grimaces* You're really trying to destroy all cultivators.</Nodes.72.Text>
			<Nodes.73.Text>You're right. But it is still over ten thousand years before this world comes to an end, long enough for all the immortals here to enjoy their lives. No wonder all the sect leaders weren't willing to forego their cultivation and start over. Now that the fate of this realm is in your hands, you are the real ruler of this realm only without a title.</Nodes.73.Text>
			<Nodes.74.Text>[color=#ff0000]I think I have made my choice.[/color]</Nodes.74.Text>
			<Nodes.75.Text>When will the end come?</Nodes.75.Text>
			<Nodes.76.Text>It probably won't take long for it to come here. You will be able to sense it then. And I'll also warn you through the Universe. Before that, you can take your time and decide what to do.</Nodes.76.Text>
			<Nodes.77.Text>Here, the Book of Heavenly Edicts!</Nodes.77.Text>
			<Nodes.78.Text>I haven't decided yet.</Nodes.78.Text>
			<Nodes.79.Text>I didn't bring the Book of Heavenly Edicts.</Nodes.79.Text>
			<Nodes.82.Text>New Feature</Nodes.82.Text>
			<Nodes.83.Text>New Feature</Nodes.83.Text>
			<Nodes.84.Text>(Dressed in outdated clothes, this man looks like an ancient cultivator. Without any indication of his ability, the man's presence is as profound and enigmatic as the Creed of Heaven.)</Nodes.84.Text>
			<Nodes.85.Text>I don't want to hear you talk anymore. Excuse me.</Nodes.85.Text>
			<Nodes.88.Text>[Debug Demo]</Nodes.88.Text>
			<Nodes.89.Text>New Feature</Nodes.89.Text>
			<Nodes.90.Text>New Feature</Nodes.90.Text>
			<Nodes.91.Text>Led by the sect leaders and I, all the immortals entered the Universe and found that cultivation was thousand times faster here. Overjoyed, we thought that it could lead to prosperity of immortality and that we could even fight back against the demons. But a hundred years later, we realized the danger lurking here: The Creed of Heaven was broken in the new world. Though quick, the cultivation practice would result in weak foundations for growing cultivators. And as time went by, even our abilities had been affected and greatly damaged by the broken Creed.</Nodes.91.Text>
			<Nodes.92.Text>I thought that we'd have no future staying in this realm, so I tried to go back to the Boundless Universe. But those old-timers were so scared of the demons that they even joined hands to destroy me just to be caged in this safe yet broken universe.</Nodes.92.Text>
			<Nodes.93.Text>I do have my mission and I also need your help. But now it is not the time and I need to recovery. If you are interesting, then come here when it is the time. I will explain all.</Nodes.93.Text>
			<Nodes.94.Text>Then why are you here? I guess you have predict your awakeness. What do you plan?</Nodes.94.Text>
			<Nodes.95.Text>And your choice?</Nodes.95.Text>
			<Nodes.96.Text>New Feature</Nodes.96.Text>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>