<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Huo" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Fire Spirit Root: Crimson Fruit Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Crimson Fruit, an Elemental Medicine. Grows in a place with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil. For its special trait, it has to grow in an environment above [temperature]200[/temperature].</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Jin" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Metal Spirit Root: Sagacity Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Sage Fruit, an Elemental Medicine. Grows in a place with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil. Extremely sensitive to high temperature, but relatively resistant to cold. It has to grow in an environment below [temperature]20[/temperature].</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Mu" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Wood Spirit Root: Gnarled Vine</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Gnarled Vine, an Elemental Medicine. Grows in a place with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil. It has a strict requirement for environment temperature, and only grows in between [temperature]15[/temperature]-[/temperature]35[/temperature].</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Shui" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Water Spirit Root: Prism Lotus</ThingName>
			<Desc>The Prism Lotus plant, an Elemental Medicine. Grows in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil. It prefers low temperature, and only grows in an environment below [temperature]-120[/temperature].</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Tu" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Earth Spirit Root: Ocher Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Ocher Essence, an elemental medicine. Grows in a place with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil. It avoids low temperature, and only grows in an environment above [temperature]30[/temperature].</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Huo_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Fire Spirit Root: Crimson Fruit Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Crimson Fruit, an Elemental Medicine. It is said to only grow in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Jin_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Metal Spirit Root: Sagacity Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Sagacity Fruit, an Elemental Medicine. It is said to only grow in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Mu_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Wood Spirit Root: Gnarled Vine</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Gnarled Vine, an Elemental Medicine. It is said to only grow in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Shui_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Water Spirit Root: Prism Lotus</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Prismatic Lotus, an Elemental Medicine. It is said to only grow in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Tu_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Earth Spirit Root: Ocher Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Ochre Essence, an Elemental Medicine. It is said to only grow in places with dense Qi, compatible element and fertile soil.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>