<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Stability">
			<Descript>Stability {1}{0:N1}%</Descript>
			<ToolTips>Formations will lose Stability when attacked. If a formation's Stability drops to 0, it will be broken.</ToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="FabaoAtkPower">
			<Descript>Artifact Mastery Ability {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>The pillar's artifact power will increase once the formation has been formed. \nArtifact mastery affects the degree of which the pillar's artifact power increase once a formation has been formed.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("The pillar's artifact power will increase once the formation has been formed.\nArtifact mastery affects the degree of which the pillar's artifact power increase once a formation has been formed.\nArtifact Power Increase: %.0f%%", (z.FabaoPowerK_Normal-1)*100)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="MagicPower">
			<Descript>Spell Ability {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>Spell ability affects the degree of which the pillar's artifact power increase once a formation has been formed. \nSpell ability affects the degree of which the pillar's spell power increase once a formation has been formed.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("The pillar's artifact power will increase once the formation has been formed.\nSpell ability affects the degree of which the pillar's artifact power increase once a formation has been formed.\nSpell Power Increase: %.0f%%", (z.MagicPowerK_Normal-1)*100)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Sheild">
			<Descript>Protection Ability {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>When the formation is being attacked, part of the damage received will be absorbed by the formation, and all the characters in the formation will share the remaining damage equally. \nThe formation will take reduced damage, and the final damage is shared equally among all of the characters in the formation</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("The formation will take reduced damage, and the final damage is shared equally among all of the characters in the formation.\nThe formation will take reduced damage, and the final damage is shared equally among all of the characters in the formation\nDamage Reduction: %.0f%%", (1-z.EffectDamageP) * 100)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="SkillCooldown">
			<Descript>Operation Ability {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>As the formation continues to operate, it will accumulate Energy. Formation Insight can be used to unleash special formation abilities. What's more, the Qi of all characters in the formation will be proportionally balanced as the formation continues to operate. \nOperation ability affects the accumulation rate of Energy and the cycle of the Qi balance.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("As the formation continues to operate, it will accumulate Energy. Formation Insight can be used to unleash some special formation abilities. In addition, the Qi of all characters in the formation will be proportionally balanced as the formation continues to operation.\nOperation ability affects the accumulation rate of Energy and the interval of the Qi balance.\nReduction Rate of the Operation Cycle: %.0f%%\nAccumulation Cycle of Insight: %.0f sec\nQi Balance Cycle: %.0f sec", (1-z.EffectZrPointCDP)*100, ZhenMgr:GetZRAddDuration(z), 15 * z.EffectZrPointCDP)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="ReduceCost">
			<Descript>Formation Efficiency {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>Once the formation is formed, maintaining it and using formation skills will cost Qi from every character in the formation. The Qi cost to maintain the formation is related to the Max Qi of the pillar character in the formation. The Qi cost to use any formation skill is related to the power of the skill. \nFormation efficiency affects the Qi cost of each formation action.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("Once the formation is formed, maintaining it and using formation skills will cost Qi from every character in the formation. The Qi cost to maintain the formation is related to the Max Qi of the pillar character in the formation. The Qi cost to use any formation skill is related to the power of the skill. \nFormation efficiency affects the Qi cost of each formation action. \nCurrent Cost Reduced: %.0f%%", (1 - z.EffectCostP)*100)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NpcNodeCountNumPowerup">
			<Descript>Formation Size {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>Size is determined by the number of nodes in a formation. The more nodes in a formation, the larger its size.  The ability of the pillar character determines the maximum formation size. If a character is hosting a formation whose size surpasses their ability, the formation stability will be greatly reduced. Otherwise, it will be increased.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("Size is determined by the number of nodes in a formation. The more nodes in a formation, the larger its size. \nThe ability of the pillar character determines the maximum formation size. If a character is hosting a formation whose size surpasses their ability, the formation stability will be greatly reduced. Otherwise, it will be increased. \nAdjusted Current Formation Stability: %.0f", z.fStabilityCoreNpcAddv)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NpcZhenPressurePowerup">
			<Descript>Formation Load {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>Formation load is determined by the complexity of the formation structure. A formation with auxiliaries further away from the pillar will have a greater load. The ability of the pillar character determines the maximum formation load. If the character is hosting a formation whose formation load surpasses their ability, the formation cost will be greatly increased. Otherwise, it will be reduced.</ToolTips>
			<LuaToolTips>string.format("Formation load is determined by the complexity of the formation structure. A formation with auxiliaries further away from the pillar will have a greater load. \nThe ability of the pillar character determines the maximum formation load. If the character is hosting a formation whose formation load surpasses their ability, the formation cost will be greatly increased. Otherwise, it will be reduced. \nQi Cost/sec: %.0f", z.CostLingPerSec)</LuaToolTips>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="NpcZhenPoint">
			<Descript>Formation Energy {1}{0:N1}</Descript>
			<ToolTips>As the formation continues to operate, it will accumulate Energy. Formation Energy can be used to unleash special formation abilities. However, a formation has limitation as to the amount of Energy it can store. Once the limitation has been reached, Energy will cease to increase.</ToolTips>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>