<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Gong_3_Jin">
			<DisplayName>Seven-Slaughtering Sword</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Legend has it that this is a secret Law from the demon realm for the realization of sword mastery. It leads its follower through seven states. Both the beginning and advancement in cultivation are relatively difficult. One will become very powerful in battles and have a strong intention to kill, which leads to the extremely dangerous triple thunders of tribulation. It is an absolute killer's Law.</Desc>
			<SelectDesc>One will excel in artifact mastery and become powerful in battles, but have to go through multiple Heavenly Tribulations due to all the killings. Are you sure you want to follow this Law?</SelectDesc>
			<Stages.0.DisplayName>Heart of Sword</Stages.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>Heart of Sword</Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>Find one's own Seven-Slaughtering Sword with a whole-hearted determination. If it goes wrong, start it again from scratch. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts. \nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low perception. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.1.DisplayName>Sword Aura</Stages.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>Sword Aura</Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>Form the sword aura to split open the mind gate with determination, spending one's fine energy, blood and life energy. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts. \nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low perception. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.2.DisplayName>Blade Pill</Stages.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Desc>Condense the sword aura into the essence of the blade, like the Golden Core combined with mixed elements.</Stages.2.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>Blade Pill</Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.DisplayName>Sword Will</Stages.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Desc>The thunder of tribulation falls as the sword core comes into shape. Use it to form the will of the sword.</Stages.3.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>Sword Will</Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.DisplayName>Sword Embryo</Stages.4.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Necks.0.DisplayName>Sword Embryo</Stages.4.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Necks.0.Desc>After the heavenly tribulation, return to the purest form and create the sword embryo from the sword core.</Stages.4.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.5.DisplayName>Sword Soul</Stages.5.DisplayName>
			<Stages.5.Necks.0.DisplayName>Sword Soul</Stages.5.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.5.Necks.0.Desc>Use the sword will to steal the heavenly Law to destruction from the tribulations to reach the state of a heavenly swordsman. If successful, one shall face the anger from heaven—the ultimate heavenly tribulation.</Stages.5.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.6.DisplayName>Sword Spirit</Stages.6.DisplayName>
			<Stages.6.Necks.0.DisplayName>Sword Spirit</Stages.6.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.6.Necks.0.Desc>Use the heavenly thunder to forge the sword soul as proof of pure Yang to ascend toward immortality.</Stages.6.Necks.0.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>