<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Gong_1_Shui">
			<DisplayName>Sixteen Supreme Steps Law</DisplayName>
			<Desc>One of the true elemental Laws of the Taiyi Sect, including 4 states and 16 different limits that require a step-by-step progress. It is not easy to reach a higher state in this Law, but it does not require much to begin with. You will make steadfast progress in cultivation, and immortality may eventually happen.</Desc>
			<SelectDesc>This Law requires a step-by-step progress and especially a stable foundation, but you have to experience the first tribulation during core shaping. Are you sure you want to follow this Law?</SelectDesc>
			<Stages.0.DisplayName>Qi Congealment</Stages.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Desc>The first state on this Law. Requires a peaceful mind and a long time of meditation. It is harder for an intelligent person to banish thoughts from their mind and pass this state.</Stages.0.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>Concentration</Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>Concentrate one's mind and banish other random thoughts in meditation. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough will be more difficult for characters with high intelligence.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.1.DisplayName>Introspection</Stages.0.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.1.Desc>After concentration, further perceive the internal change in one's body, like a blind person feeling their surroundings, and finally reach the state of being able to sense the condition of one's internal organs. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough will be more difficult for characters with high intelligence.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.2.DisplayName>Qi Motion</Stages.0.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.2.Desc>As introspection progresses, one will be able to find the first Qi Sense in meditation. It is the beginning of Stamina Conversion, which is called the 'First Perception'. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough will be more difficult for characters with low Qi sense. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.3.DisplayName>The Bounded Heavens</Stages.0.Necks.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.3.Desc>In this state, you need to gradually increase inner Qi and drive it through the Governing and Conception Vessels to create an inner cycle. This is called the 'Universal Cycle'.</Stages.0.Necks.3.Desc>
			<Stages.1.DisplayName>Core Shaping</Stages.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Desc>The second state in this Law. Requires risking one's life for a regulation between Water and Fire, in order to form one Golden Core.</Stages.1.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>Mind Gate</Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>Open up the mind gate to connect with heaven and earth. Leave all the worldly troubles behind.</Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.1.DisplayName>Fulfillment</Stages.1.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.1.Desc>Let Qi flow freely throughout one's whole body, allowing you to reach a state of completeness.</Stages.1.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.2.DisplayName>Inner Cauldron</Stages.1.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.2.Desc>Build an inner cauldron for core shaping using one's chest and abdomen as the cauldron, heart as fire, kidney as water, and life as fuel. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low Constitution. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.1.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.3.DisplayName>Core Congealment</Stages.1.Necks.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.3.Desc>Combine one's energy, Qi and spirit into one Golden Core, making it the foundation of the Law.</Stages.1.Necks.3.Desc>
			<Stages.2.DisplayName>Core Refinement</Stages.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Desc>The third state in this Law. Return to one's original and purest nature. One shall free one's mind and realize true self in this state.</Stages.2.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>First Tribulation</Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.0.Desc>Thunder of Tribulation will befall you after the formation of Golden Core.</Stages.2.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.1.DisplayName>Germinal</Stages.2.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.1.Desc>One's true self gradually forms inside the Golden Core, as if in the earliest stage of prenatal development. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low Intelligence.[/color]</Stages.2.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.2.DisplayName>Embryonic</Stages.2.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.2.Desc>One's true self slowly comes into shape and is ready to grow. [color=#D06508]This breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low Constitution.[/color]</Stages.2.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.3.DisplayName>Fetal</Stages.2.Necks.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.3.Desc>One's purest form in the Innerspirit starts to break through the confines of the mortal body, entering into a state of near immortality on earth.</Stages.2.Necks.3.Desc>
			<Stages.3.DisplayName>Great Vehicle</Stages.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Desc>The fourth state in this Law. The Innerspirit will survive the Thunder of Tribulation, become a being of pure Yang, leave the mortal body behind and ascend as an Immortal.</Stages.3.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>Spirit Forging</Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.0.Desc>Forge one's spirit with the Goddess of Earth's pure Yin breaths.</Stages.3.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.1.DisplayName>Spirit Soaring</Stages.3.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.1.Desc>Break away from one's mortal body and let the spirit roam the world. [color=#D06508]\nNote that breaking through will greatly damage one's lifespan.[/color]</Stages.3.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.2.DisplayName>Spirit Enlightened</Stages.3.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.2.Desc>Enlighten one's spirit with the blessing of heaven. One will face the Heavenly Tribulation after breaking this limit. [color=#D06508]\nIt is extremely difficult to break through, and there will not be any XP Bonus.[/color]</Stages.3.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.3.DisplayName>Ascension</Stages.3.Necks.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.3.Desc>Survive the curse of tribulation from heaven and earth and ascend toward immortality. Otherwise, it will obliterate one's entire existence.</Stages.3.Necks.3.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>