<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Gong_2_Mu">
			<DisplayName>Myriad Artifact Law</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Passed down by the Avarice Lord in the Supreme Clarity. The ultimate secret Law for artifact crafting of Mt. Sunshade. Only the most ingenious people can practice this Law. A master of this Law can craft anything into an artifact. This Law leads its follower through 5 heavens and 15 palaces. Once completed, one can leave the earth and ascend toward immortality.</Desc>
			<SelectDesc>One will excel in artifact crafting when cultivating in this Law, but will not be skilled in battles. Are you sure you want to follow this Law?</SelectDesc>
			<Stages.0.DisplayName>Heaven of Equanimity</Stages.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Desc>The first heaven. It seeks the natural enlightenment in a state of equanimity and starts the Law to immortality, thus called the 'Heaven of Equanimity'.</Stages.0.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>Palace of Five Centers</Stages.0.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>Meditate in a sitting position with the top of one's head and the center of soles and palms facing upwards. Let blood and Qi flow through the five centers. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough will be more difficult for characters with high intelligence.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.1.DisplayName>Palace of Five Qi</Stages.0.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.1.Desc>The flow of Qi and blood is the movement inside stillness. Sense the natural formation of the Five Qi inside the vessels, as it grows alongside the running blood. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough will be more difficult for characters with low Constitution. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.0.Necks.2.DisplayName>Palace of Spiritual Mind</Stages.0.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.0.Necks.2.Desc>Use the spiritual mind to return the Five Qi into the sea of Qi. Repeat it for a gradual progress of cultivation. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts.[/color]</Stages.0.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.1.DisplayName>Heaven of Longevity</Stages.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Desc>The second heaven. It will help to shape the Golden Core and increase one's lifespan and power of miracles, thus called the Heaven of Longevity.</Stages.1.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>Palace of Perception</Stages.1.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>Use Qi to open up the mind gate and connect with heaven and earth. Leave all the worldly troubles behind. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts.[/color]</Stages.1.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.1.DisplayName>Palace of Great Unity</Stages.1.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.1.Desc>Use one's own primeval Qi to attract natural Qi, progressing in the cultivation Law. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low Constitution. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.1.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.1.Necks.2.DisplayName>Place of Golden Spirit</Stages.1.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.1.Necks.2.Desc>Combine one's energy, Qi and spirit into one Golden Core, making it the foundation of the Law.</Stages.1.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.2.DisplayName>Heaven of Destiny</Stages.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Desc>The third heaven. Perceive the nature of all beings in the world, learn from others' experience to overcome one's own shortcomings, and lay the foundation for the birth of the Innerspirit.</Stages.2.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>Place of True Fire</Stages.2.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.0.Desc>Trigger the three true fires in the state of Golden Core to smelt everything. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough is more difficult for characters with low Constitution. \nFailing to breakthrough may lead to injury.[/color]</Stages.2.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.1.DisplayName>Palace of Creations</Stages.2.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.1.Desc>Enter the mortal realm and feel the ingenuity of all creations with the three true fires, strengthening one's determination.</Stages.2.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.2.Necks.2.DisplayName>Palace of Ingenuity</Stages.2.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.2.Necks.2.Desc>Meditate in isolation for 24 hours and smelt everything seen in the meditated state into one cauldron, as one has improved skills of artifact crafting and learned ingenuity from the Innerspirit.</Stages.2.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.3.DisplayName>Heaven of Pure Yang</Stages.3.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Desc>The fourth heaven. It shapes the Golden Core with the true fire and one's purest spirit and creates the pure Yang Innerspirit of supreme clarity, thus called the Heaven of Pure Yang.</Stages.3.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>Palace of Greater Inspiration</Stages.3.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.0.Desc>Sense one's true self and have an epiphany with the help of the Golden Core. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts.[/color]</Stages.3.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.1.DisplayName>Palace of True Self</Stages.3.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.1.Desc>Foster the Golden Core and fortify one's true self. [color=#D06508]\nThis breakthrough can be completed after repeated attempts.[/color]</Stages.3.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.3.Necks.2.DisplayName>Palace of Divine Incubation</Stages.3.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.3.Necks.2.Desc>The Golden Core breaks as the Innerspirit is born.</Stages.3.Necks.2.Desc>
			<Stages.4.DisplayName>Heaven of Ultimacy</Stages.4.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Desc>The fifth heaven. Survive the final thunder of tribulation, form the pure Yang spirit of supreme clarity, and ascend above the Heaven of Ultimacy.</Stages.4.Desc>
			<Stages.4.Necks.0.DisplayName>Palace of Liberation</Stages.4.Necks.0.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Necks.0.Desc>Forge one's spirit with primeval Qi, allowing it to leave the mortal body and roam the world. [color=#D06508]\nNote that this breakthrough will greatly damage one's lifespan.[/color]</Stages.4.Necks.0.Desc>
			<Stages.4.Necks.1.DisplayName>Palace of Serenity</Stages.4.Necks.1.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Necks.1.Desc>Enlighten one's spirit with the blessing of heaven. One will face the Heavenly Tribulation after breaking this limit. [color=#D06508]\nIt is extremely difficult to breakthrough, and there will not be any XP Bonus.[/color]</Stages.4.Necks.1.Desc>
			<Stages.4.Necks.2.DisplayName>Palace of Emperor</Stages.4.Necks.2.DisplayName>
			<Stages.4.Necks.2.Desc>Leave the mortal body behind and ascend toward immortality.</Stages.4.Necks.2.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>