<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Housing">
			<DisplayName>Divine Residence</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Prédio de residência fornecido para pessoas do Reino Divino. Aumenta o número máximo de residentes divinos.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Guard">
			<DisplayName>Guard's Temple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Instalação dedicada ao culto da Guarda, através da qual os cultivadores da Lei de Shendao podem obter a bênção da Guarda para melhorar sua própria habilidade.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_FaithWay">
			<DisplayName>Temple of Miracles</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Cada Templo da Performance pode se comunicar com uma estátua cultuada na Agência de uma cidade do Mundo Mortal. Através deste sistema, os cultivadores da Lei de Shendao são capazes de adquirir a Crença acumulada em estátuas dos crentes mortais, e fazer alguns truques legais com ela..</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoRateUp">
			<DisplayName>Sacred Pavilion</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Um templo construído sobre o poder da Crença, é a projeção do próprio Artefato Sagrado no Reino Divino. O aumento no nível do Pavilhão Sagrado irá aprimorar o próprio Artefato Sagrado.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd1">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Storm</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Parte do Pavilhão Sagrado. Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o Qi do vento e da nuvem, tornando-a mais ágil e elegante.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd2">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Weight</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Parte do Pavilhão Sagrado. Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o Qi do vento e da nuvem, tornando-o mais ágil e elegante.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd3">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Aplomb</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Parte do Pavilhão Sagrado. Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder da verdadeira integridade, tornando-a mais sólida e resistente.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd4">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Pliancy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Parte do Pavilhão Sagrado. Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder de flexibilidade, tornando-a mais flexível e resistente.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd5">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Blade</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder da lâmina, que é implacavelmente afiada.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd6">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Majesty</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder da majestade, que é excepcionalmente destrutivo.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd7">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Seed</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder da mustard seed, tornando-a minúscula e imperceptível.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd8">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Thunder</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder do trovão celestial, cujo poder é ilimitado.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd9">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Pantheon</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder de todos os espíritos, uma energia profunda e turbulenta.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd10">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Gale</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder do howling gale(vendaval uivante), que é tão rápido quanto instantâneo.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoLabelAdd11">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Charge</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder do dark charging(carregamento escuro), tornando-o imparável.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd1">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Poisons</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder dos five poisons(cinco venenos). Para cada 36º golpe, ele atacará o corpo do cultivador inimigo, penetrando no escudo e causando dano adicional.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Para cada 36º ataque, ele atacará o corpo do cultivador inimigo, penetrando no escudo e causando dano adicional.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd2">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Spirit</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder de spirit charging(carregar espíritos). Cada 18º ataque lançará um feitiço no inimigo alvo.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Cada 18º ataque lançará um feitiço no inimigo alvo.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd3">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Guard</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Sacred Relic(Relíquia Sagrada) o poder de holy protection(proteção sagrada). Nível de habilidade de proteção aumentado em 5.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Nível de habilidade de proteção aumentado em 5.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd4">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Magic</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede à Relíquia Sagrada o poder da holy magic spell(magia sagrada). Nível de habilidade de magia aumentado em 5.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Nível de habilidade de magia aumentado em 5.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd5">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Mastery</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concede a Relíquia Sagrada o poder da holy mastery (maestria sagrada). Nível de habilidade de Artifact Mastery skill(Maestria de Artefato) aumentado em 5.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Nível de habilidade de Artifact Mastery skill(Maestria de Artefato) aumentado em 5.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd6">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Recall</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of spirit recalling. 3% of damage dealt will be replenished to the artifact's Qi.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>3% of damage dealt will be replenished to the artifact's Qi.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd7">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Specter</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of Spectral. For every 15 attacks, a swordsprite is generated that lasts 15 seconds.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>For every 15 attacks, a swordsprite is generated that lasts 15 seconds.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd8">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Breath</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of alleviating breath. Every 7 attacks reduce skill cooldown by 1 second.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Every 7 attacks reduce skill cooldown by 1 second.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd9">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Nine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of the Nine Extremities. When dealing damage, there is a 4% chance of dealing 9 times the damage.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>When dealing damage, there is a 4% chance of dealing 9 times the damage.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd10">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Infinity</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of infinity. Power of first sword strike increased by 3 times. The effect is reset when replenishing Qi to the artifact.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Power of first sword strike increased by 3 times. The effect is reset when replenishing Qi to the artifact.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_GodFabaoAbilityAdd11">
			<DisplayName>SP: Hall of Wind</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Grants Sacred Relic the power of breaking the wind of positivity. Deals 1.25x damage when attacking the enemy's body itself.</Desc>
			<Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>Deals 1.25x damage when attacking the enemy's body itself.</Levels.0.Effects.0.Ability.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_WishTree">
			<DisplayName>Tree of Prayers</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The wishes and prayers of ordinary people have concentrated and formed into a tree. You can harness its Qi of mortals to slightly reduce Divinity.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_XinyangShendian">
			<DisplayName>Temple of Faith</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Temple that concentrates the power of Belief. It can increase the efficiency at which Divine Realm produces Belief.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_LiuLiShenDian">
			<DisplayName>Temple of Glaze</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Temple that magnifies the power of Guards. It can enhance abilities granted to you by Guards.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_ThunderDefend">
			<DisplayName>Heavenly Palace</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Concentrate the power of Belief to shelter you from the might of heaven. It can reduce the power of Heavenly Tribulation.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_FengShenTai">
			<DisplayName>Altar of Guards</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Place where the gods consecrate the sub-gods, anointing Core Followers with 100% Belief into Guards.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_CoreHousing_A">
			<DisplayName>Residence of Metal</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Increases Max Core Followers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_CoreHousing_B">
			<DisplayName>Residence of Wood</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Increases Max Core Followers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_CoreHousing_C">
			<DisplayName>Residence of Water</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Increases Max Core Followers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_CoreHousing_D">
			<DisplayName>Residence of Fire</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Increases Max Core Followers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_CoreHousing_E">
			<DisplayName>Residence of Earth</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Increases Max Core Followers.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Housing_Lv2">
			<DisplayName>Generality Residence</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Advanced Divine Residence. Can accommodate a large number of Divine Residents.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Housing_Lv2_2">
			<DisplayName>Connection Residence</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Advanced Divine Residence. Can accommodate a large number of Divine Residents.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_HongChenKuHai">
			<DisplayName>Mortal Melancholia</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Brings the sufferings of the mortals into the Divine Realm, greatly reducing Divinity.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Magic_1">
			<DisplayName>Hall of Rallying</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Provides the following Miracles at level 1, level 2 and level 3 respectively: Divine Rallying Spell, Wish-fulfilling Spell, Sole Reverence Spell. Increase the base material output of the area your Embodiment resides in within a certain period of time.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Magic_2">
			<DisplayName>Pavilion of Heart</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Level 1 provides Miracle - Pacification: Release on a non-Shendao cultivating character and reduce its Mood multiplier by 25%, lasting 7 days. \nLevel 2 provides Miracle - Clean Mind: Resolve an Obsession for the character, and obtain an Obsession Gem.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Magic_3">
			<DisplayName>Pavilion of Might</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Level 1 provides Miracle - Deification: Cast a spell to temporarily raise your Divinity to extreme, greatly improving combat prowess.\n Level 2 provides Miracle - Divine Mercy: Consume humanity to attempt to illuminate a plant. The illumination result will need some time to appear. The plant cannot be illuminated with psychic power again while in an illumination session.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="GodCity_Magic_4">
			<DisplayName>Hall of Devotion</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Level 1 provides Miracle - Persuasion: Persuade ally or neutral Inner disciple characters to try to convert them into Core Followers. \nLevel 2 provides Miracle - Divinity Tracing: Select a character to try to learn their whereabouts. The more Divine Residents and information you have, the higher the success rate of learning target's whereabouts.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>