<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Place_Level2Base">
			<Desc>Lv.2 Location Templates</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_DanXia1">
			<DisplayName>Supreme Clarity Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A natural karst cave at the foot of Mt. Sunshade, with winding passages and spectacular scenery. Deep inside the cave, there is a statue of the Avarice Lord erected for people to worship. It is a perfect place to retreat into isolation for practice.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_DanXia2">
			<DisplayName>Sunshade Precipice</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A precipice at the top of Mt. Sunshade. Under the dimming sunlight at dusk, it offers a breathtakingly glorious view of mountain scenery.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_DanXia3">
			<DisplayName>Five Dragons Pond</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A magical pond located deep in Mt. Sunshade. Lotus flowers sprout vigorously in the lake, which seems bottomless, connecting to the water vein on the earth's crust. It is said that the Prism Lotus—the Spirit Root of the Sunshade Abode is planted here.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_KunLun1">
			<DisplayName>Immortal Summit</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A stone platform at the southern foot of Mt. Kunlun, with many enigmatic patterns carved on it. It is said that in the ancient age, the Eastern King granted immortality here to his subordinates and ascended into heaven, leaving a Taoist Law for later generations to find.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_KunLun2">
			<DisplayName>Drake Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>An endless cave deep in Mt. Kunlun, with complex and confusing passages and streams. It is said to be directly connected to and blessed by the Dragon's Vein, and thus the Kunlun Palace cultivates its Spirit Root—the Ocher Essence here.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_KunLun2_1">
			<DisplayName>Mystic Cavern</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A regular cavern inside the Drake Cave. It looks fairly ordinary, but emits a strange and mystical aura, which cannot be sensed unless it was someone who knew the Drake Cave inside and out. There seems to be some peculiar, natural patterns at the entry of the cavern.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_TianJi1">
			<DisplayName>Nimbus Ravine</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A deep ravine between the soaring precipices at the Heavenstep Peak, creating a giant vortex of Qi that spins without halt; even birds cannot fly over it. It is told that the Skydome Palace has the Spirit Root—Sage Fruit planted on the precipice of the ravine.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_TianJi2">
			<DisplayName>Celeste Pass</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A narrow pass on the way to the top of the Heavenstep Peak. Purity Leaf grows everywhere on the sides of the pass, anyone who approaches will forget all troubles and feel soothed and peaceful, thus the name Celeste Pass. Through it is the top of the Heavenstep Peak, where the Skydome Palace is based.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_JiuHua1">
			<DisplayName>Lucian Village</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A village at the foot of Mt. Lucian. Blessed by the Purple Cloud Temple, the village is populated and thriving as a community. There is a huge vein of jade stones nearby, on which the villagers make a living by extracting and selling them to the Purple Cloud Temple.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_JiuHua2">
			<DisplayName>Wyvern Pool</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A popular scenic spot on Mt. Lucian. Standing by the Wyvern Pool, one can see the magnificent view of the surging sea of clouds. Legend has it that a sage once grazed dragons here in the ancient age.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_JiuHua3">
			<DisplayName>Phoenix Cliff</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A popular scenic spot on Mt. Lucian. The dry trunks of two giant sycamore trees still remain till this day. Legend has it that a phoenix once perched on this cliff in the ancient age.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_LongHu1">
			<DisplayName>Skypass Falls</DisplayName>
			<Desc>An ultimate attraction on Mt. Tiger Paw. The water rushes straight down from the top of the climbing mountain, roaring as loud as a majestic dragon flying across the sky.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_LongHu2">
			<DisplayName>Mistwood Forest</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A thick forest at the foot of Mt. Tiger Paw, in which many trees are well over several hundred years old. Rumor has it that Phoenixwood also grows here. Mt. Tiger Paw has its Spirit Root planted here for its richness in Wood Qi.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Shu1">
			<DisplayName>Jadestone Cliff</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Standing on the western peak of Mt. Shu, the cliff has a beautiful scenic view and is populated with spiritual and magical animals. This is where the earth's vein leaks out Qi, thus creating many rare ores like Fire Copper inside the mountain. The Immortal Caerulea planted the spiritual medicine Red Fruit here due to its abundance in the element of Fire.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Shu2">
			<DisplayName>Thunderclap Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>One of the twelve caves in Mt. Shu, also where the founder of Blue Lotus Temple retreated into seclusion. Legend has it that the Immortal Caerulea left a secret here before his ascension; however, no one seems to be able to found it for thousands of years.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Shu3">
			<DisplayName>Glimmer Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>One of the renowned caves in Mt. Shu, hidden atop the northern peak of the mountain. Exposed Fire Copper veins abound in the cave, causing an overflow of Fire Element for thousands of years and creating the glimmer inside, hence the name Glimmer Cave. It is a perfect place for practice.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Shu4">
			<DisplayName>Gemspring Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>One of the twelve renowned caves in Mt. Shu. Legend has it that a holy spring of Earth Flux is hidden deep inside the cave, and only destiny can be one's guide to finding it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Shu5">
			<DisplayName>Bladesmith Tomb</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A dark and meandering cave inside Mt. Shu, with the swords carried by each generation of sword immortals from the Blue Lotus Temple hidden in it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_WuLian1">
			<DisplayName>Celestial Pool</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A sacred pond that lies within a caldera atop the once volcanic Mt. Nelumbo. The Immortal Nelumbo performed a miracle stolen from the ways of heaven to seal the volcano and established the sect here. Legend has it that there is a Life Spring in the pool, and only the most fortunate of all will be able to find it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_WuLian2">
			<DisplayName>Pearlwood Rainforest</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A mystical forest at the back of Mt. Nelumbo. When it rains, the forest becomes misty and atmospheric like a fairyland. There once was a scholar with terminal disease who dove into and then came back from the forest. He speaks of an immortal with a wooded sword in their left hand that controls the force of nature and a white jade in their right hand that cures all diseases, calling themselves the 'Immortal Pearlwood'. Hence the name 'Pearlwood Rainforest'.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BaiMan1">
			<DisplayName>Deathknell Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Every time the disciples at Mt. Hundred Insects kill magic beasts, they will bring their bodies to the Deathknell Cave and seal them inside. The bodies will then transform into puppets via the Qi of death to guard the mountain. If a new body sent there has not completed the transformation, one might be able to take out its Soul Pearl .</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BaiMan2">
			<DisplayName>Serpent Pit</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A pit used by Mt. Hundred Insects to keep and feed serpents. Once a serpent becomes mature enough, it will be taken out and its blood will be collected for the disciples' cultivation.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BaiMan3">
			<DisplayName>Beast Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A place for Mt. Hundred Insects to keep their beasts and animals, where something went horribly wrong. It has been gradually abandoned and no one is allowed to enter.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_XianKong1">
			<DisplayName>Abyss</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A bottomless pit in Mt. Pitfall, and its emission of a magnetic field oftentimes attracts meteors here. It is said that a cultivator once found a piece of lumina core here. However, the treasure is enigmatic, and most people would leave empty-handed.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Hei4">
			<DisplayName>Millspine Forest</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A forest at the foot of Mt. Blackstone, the bowels of which are covered with thistles and thorns that few men and animals can set foot in. It has barely been visited by people since the ancient times; thus, there are rare trees that have survived over a thousand years all around the forest. It is abundant in Wood Element, making a perfect place for cultivation.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_HeHuan1">
			<DisplayName>Safeward Seas</DisplayName>
			<Desc>There is a big island near the Exultant Isle, inside of which is a misty lake called Safeward Seas. Once inside, one can have visions of all kinds of love-hate relationships, and will possibly indulge oneself and forget about time if not careful.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_HeHuan2">
			<DisplayName>Poison Dragon Lake</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A deep lake on the Exultant Isle. Legend has it that deep inside the lake, there is a den of Toxagons that often attack nearby cultivators. It is also told that there is a holy spring of Earth Flux and the Toxagon den is only a misleading story made up by the Exultant Isle.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Desert1">
			<DisplayName>Daemonia Temple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A large evil sect hidden deep in the Great Desert. It usually avoids attracting too much attention and has been in hiding for a thousand years, thus barely known to the outside world. It was not until recently when the Dragon Cliff inscriptions were found in the sanctum of evils, did the sect reemerge in the world.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Desert2">
			<DisplayName>Mirage Wastelands</DisplayName>
			<Desc>An area of barren wastelands deep in the Great Desert, constantly hit with sandstorms. The air here is filled with a dense Qi of the Earth Element. It is a great place for cultivation, only if one can withstand the terrible environment.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Desert3">
			<DisplayName>Blazenest</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A bizarre cave hidden deep in the Great Desert. It is extremely hot inside, which is said to possess a natural treasure of the Fire Element.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Desert4">
			<DisplayName>Village of Dunes</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A small village at the edge of the Great Desert. Most residents in the village are demon descendants. They are generally belligerent and fearless, and hunt beasts in the desert for a living.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_SouthForest1">
			<DisplayName>Perennial Miasma</DisplayName>
			<Desc>There used to be a forest of peach trees that spread over hundreds of miles on the bad lands of the Wild South, but few people have come here to pick the ripe fruits before they drop to the ground and rot. For thousands of years, the rotten peaches gradually formed the noxious air that never dissipates.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_SouthForest2">
			<DisplayName>The Demon Emperor's Tomb</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The founder of the southern demonic cult—the Demon Emperor's tomb. The chamber was built out of a whole meteorite stone and buried deep in the ground. The tomb is strictly surrounded by the Cosmos Spirits. Without the secret way to open it, anyone who touches the tomb will immediately die no matter how experienced they are.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_SouthForest3">
			<DisplayName>Wormwrought Valley</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A valley deep in the Wild South, most of which are dangerous thick woods with snakes and insects crawling inside. However, its damp environment is especially suitable for the growth of the magical medicine—Gnarled Vine, so cultivators often come here to seek an easier way to immortality.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Snowfield1">
			<DisplayName>Skye Conch Valley</DisplayName>
			<Desc>An untrodden valley in the Great Snowland, filled with Qi. Some ginseng here have been growing for over a hundred years.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Snowfield2">
			<DisplayName>Lake Jadestone</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A magical lake deep in the Great Snowland that never freezes. It is told that there is a Prism Lotus growing in the lake, but only the luckiest cultivator will be able to find it. The source of the water connects directly to the deep end of the earth's crust—the core of the magnetic field. No one can escape the pull once stuck inside. Before Fu, the ultimate overlord as well as the Emperor of Demons that once ruled the society of cultivators, was struck dead by the hand of the gods, he hid all his possessions in a golden box and let it sink down the lake. The box was caught by the pull of the magnetic field, and it never faced the light of day again.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_Snowfield3">
			<DisplayName>Blizzard Plains</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Snow-covered plains that stretch to no end, where blizzards never stop. This place is rich in Ice Crystal Ores.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_FertileField1">
			<DisplayName>Galepeak Town</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A small town north of the great river.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_FertileField2">
			<DisplayName>Sunstop Town</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A small town on the northern plains of the river. People here are honest and peace-loving. most of which make a living by mining the jade stone ores near the village.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_FertileField3">
			<DisplayName>Ratoon Village</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A village built by the lake, and the villagers mostly make a living on farming and fishing.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_FertileField4">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Cassia</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A famous mountain south of the river, with beautiful views of scenery, an agreeable weather, and most of all, abundant Lingzhi mushrooms.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_FertileField5">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Rue</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A famous mountain south of the river. The Law leading through it is meandering and confusing, which means even animals as agile as monkeys cannot climb over it. There are a few exposed ore veins of spirit stone in the mountain. Though not worthy of any large-scale mining operation, rogue cultivators would often go in and mine some for their own use. Rumors has it that a cultivator once sensed strong Qi of Metal Element here, and it seems that the Sage Fruit, one of the Spirit Roots, is hidden somewhere in the mountain.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_CentralPlains1">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Cloudsreach</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A famous mountain surrounded by thick clouds in the hinterland of Central Plains, thus the name Mt. Cloudsreach. It is rich in Cinnabar, and alchemist cultivators often come here to gather them.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_CentralPlains2">
			<DisplayName>Alchemist's Peak</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The genius doctor used to practice alchemy here, but now only an abandoned mansion is standing here with nothing left inside. Most of the spiritual herbs in the garden have dried up; only the resilient Spirit Leaves were able to survive and spread across the mountain. It is said that the genius doctor used to plant the Spirit Root Ocher Essence here, which has attained spirituality. Only the luckiest of the adventurers is able to find it.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_CentralPlains3">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Mesa</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A bizarre mountain in the hinterland of Central Plains, with its top flat as an open field, created through the hands of the gods. At the top of the mountain, there is a List of Talents that recorded the name of all notable people in the world. Therefore, it has strong and dense Qi of Metal Element, making it a good place for cultivation.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_CentralPlains4">
			<DisplayName>Blossomfall</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A village built against mountains in the hinterland of Central Plains. Generations of villagers have been practicing medicine, making a living through herb gardens on mountains nearby.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_CentralPlains5">
			<DisplayName>Reed Village</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A village in the hinterland of Central Plains, famous for its textile manufacture.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace11">
			<DisplayName>Nanping Village</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A small village, where most residents make a living on farming and hunting.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace12">
			<DisplayName>Mt. FullMoon</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A small mountain on the southern borderlands, densely covered in trees and other types of vegetation, where people sometimes go and gather herbs to make a living.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace13">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Barren</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A brown-colored stone mountain, used to be a quarry for the government, later abandoned because of the war. Now, many villagers at the foot of the mountain plant and pick cotton for a living.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace14">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Coppertomb</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A stone mountain, rich in metallic ores but seldom visited by people.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace15">
			<DisplayName>Ruins of Taiyi</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The ruins of Taiyi Sect.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_BirthPlace16">
			<DisplayName>Black Beach</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The sand here is as black as ink. On the bank, there is a mysterious entrance to an underground casino. Only people lucky enough will be able to find it.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>