<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Place_Level3Base">
			<Desc>Lv.3 Location Templates</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_QingLianShan">
			<DisplayName>Mt. Caerulea</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This mountain used to be the hermitage for the Immortal Caerulea before his ascension, the entirety of which is hidden inside one drop of True Water in the South Sea. Without the guidance of a secret Law, nobody will be able to find this mythical mountain.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_ChiLianYuan">
			<DisplayName>Emerald Palace</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A private residence left by this realm's first-ever ascended immortal named Nangong, hidden inside the blessed abode between heaven and sea. Without the guidance of a secret Law, nobody will be able to find this place.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_LongTai">
			<DisplayName>Dragon's Platform</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The legend states that the dragons had amassed thousands of treasures upon Dragon's Platform, and with their magic, they sealed and buried them to conceal them from society. This was long ago, however, and with the flowing of time, most of these seals began to fail. There is no shortage of hopefuls who dare venture into Dragon's Platform to test their luck.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_XuanKongDong">
			<DisplayName>Ethereal Cave</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The place where the ancient immortal Yuan retreated into seclusion. Legend has it that Yuan left all the fortunes she had amassed in this palace for the future generations to find. Young and inexperienced cultivators from just sects will come here to try out their luck.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_GuZhanChang">
			<DisplayName>Heavenly Battlefield</DisplayName>
			<Desc>As ruínas do campo de batalha do primeiro Clash entre Imortais e Demônios no final da era antiga. É abundante em tesouros, mas também cheio de espaço-tempo fraturado e extremamente perigoso. Naquela época, começou a aparecer uma divisão mais clara entre os cultivadores bons e maus. A divisão entre os antigos cultivadores cresceu, tornando-se irreparável; e um confronto final ocorreu nas fronteiras do sul. A batalha se estendeu por meses, ameaçando toda a vida no mundo. Os caminhos de Yin e Yang foram tão severamente afetados que assumiram a forma física de Torch Dragon no mundo mortal. Torch Dragon ficou furioso e fez com que a terra afundasse e o mar subisse. As fronteiras do sul entraram em colapso, encerrando assim a primeira grande guerra entre imortais e demônios. Foi assim também que as terras selvagens do sul de hoje surgiram.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Place_YiJieLieFeng">
			<DisplayName>Otherworld Rift</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Diz a lenda que esse espaço-tempo fraturado leva a todos os tipos de tempo e espaço anormais, e é o resultado do segundo confronto de imortais e demônios na era antiga. Ele se foi há milhares de anos, mas inesperadamente, reapareceu neste reino agora. A fenda é extremamente perigosa e, sem um tipo especial de Sorte, até os imortais mais experientes podem se perder lá.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>