<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="SYS_LOST">
			<DisplayName>Empty</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A lost building that nobody recognizes. \n(Empty)</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences1">
			<DisplayName>Fierce Warrior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This reincarnation has cost all cultivated Laws, but the ultimate move of the Fierce Warrior has not been forgotten. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Manual: [color=#D06508]Wild Punch[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences2">
			<DisplayName>A Beautiful World</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A strange box, containing numerous people's hopes for a better world. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Legacy Artifact: [color=#D06508]A Beautiful World[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences3">
			<DisplayName>Otherworld Traveler</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You are from another world, carrying a strange-looking sword. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Weapon: [color=#D06508]Daraboomba[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences4">
			<DisplayName>Techno Sword</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This sword is a token from the leader of the Future Technology Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Weapon: [color=#D06508]Techno Sword[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences5">
			<DisplayName>Awakened Heart</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A magical manual that can focus Qi within your skull, and increase your Intelligence. As well as... \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Manual: [color=#D06508]Awakened Heart[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences6">
			<DisplayName>Stardom</DisplayName>
			<Desc>A sealed-away memory of the Wanderer marrying his daughter off in another dimension.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial Treasure: Sealed-Away Memory: Stardom[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences7">
			<DisplayName>Lucky Trick</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person was born lucky, with an ingenious Law imprinted in their mind. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Heaven Stealing Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Constitution.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences8">
			<DisplayName>Dark Swordmaster</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is a famous swordsman reincarnate, who once struck back and killed the Korean Master of Poison to alleviate a dire situation. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Weapon: [color=#D06508]Banedragon Sword[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences9">
			<DisplayName>Incredible Force</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person has a unique skill that can push their limits to grant super strength in dire situations, at the cost of consuming their lifespan. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Manual: [color=#D06508]Incredible Force[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences10">
			<DisplayName>Magical Talisman</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person carries a magical talisman box with three mysterious talismans inside. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Treasure: [color=#D06508]Magical Talisman Box[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences11">
			<DisplayName>Blessed Talisman</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person carries a magical talisman box with one extremely rare talisman inside. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Treasure: [color=#D06508]Magic Talisman Casket[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences12">
			<DisplayName>Kunlun Immortal's Law</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having strived to attain a cultivated existence their whole life, this person finally finds a manual written by an ancient immortal in the Mt. Kunlun. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Manual: [color=#D06508]Kunlun Immortal's Law[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences13">
			<DisplayName>Blessed Incarnation</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person is the incarnation of the prayers of others, and thus is born with magical powers. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Manual: [color=#D06508]Prayer Talisman[/color]. \nInitial Treasure: [color=#D06508]Heart of Prayer[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences14">
			<DisplayName>Reincarnated Immortal Swordsman</DisplayName>
			<Desc>This person was a sword immortal of great renown in a past life. As such, they are born with a special artifact. Despite losing its magical power, this artifact is still extraordinary in nature. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Treasure: [color=#D06508]Spike of the He Sect[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LunHui_Experiences15">
			<DisplayName>Myriad Artifact Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You are the descendent of the Supreme Clarity. After coming of age, your memories came back and naturally inherited the Myriad Artifact Law. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Myriad Artifact Law[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1">
			<DisplayName>Sixteen-steps Disciple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You have always wanted to be a disciple under the Sixteen-steps School of Taiyi Sect. After toiling tirelessly, you successfully unlocked the Sixteen Supreme Steps Law, one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Sixteen Supreme Steps Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Constitution, Mediocre Charisma, Mediocre Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences2">
			<DisplayName>Plough Disciple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You have always wanted to be a disciple under the Plough School of Taiyi Sect. After toiling tirelessly, you successfully unlocked the Grand Chariot Wisdom Law, one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Grand Chariot Wisdom Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Perception, Mediocre Constitution, Mediocre Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences3">
			<DisplayName>Reincarnation Disciple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You have always wanted to be a disciple under the Reincarnation School of Taiyi Sect. After toiling tirelessly, you successfully unlocked the Six Paths Reincarnation Law, one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Six Paths Reincarnation Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: Mediocre Constitution, High Perception, High Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences4">
			<DisplayName>True Sun Disciple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You have always wanted to be a disciple under the True Sun School of Taiyi Sect. After tireless efforts, you successfully unlocked the True Sun Refining Law, one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]True Sun Refining Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: Mediocre Perception, Mediocre Constitution, Mediocre Charisma, Mediocre Intelligence, Mediocre Luck.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences5">
			<DisplayName>Sunflower Disciple</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You have always wanted to be a disciple under the Sunflower School of Taiyi Sect. After tireless efforts, you successfully unlocked the Sunflower Refining Law, one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Sunflower Refining Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Perception, High Charisma, High Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences6">
			<DisplayName>Casual Cultivator</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You only want to gain a foundational understanding of cultivation, and are not particularly interested in a specific Law among the five schools of the Taiyi Sect. You are willing to go with the flow. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Five Senses[/color] increased.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1G1_1">
			<DisplayName>Alchemy Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You accidentally inherited the Primordial Alchemy Law prior to joining the Taiyi Sect, which leaves you afraid of drawing too much attention as a result. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Primordial Alchemy Law[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1G1_2">
			<DisplayName>Myriad Artifact Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You accidentally inherited the Myriad Artifact Law prior to joining the Taiyi Sect, which leaves you afraid of drawing too much attention as a result. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Myriad Artifact Law[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1G1_3">
			<DisplayName>Sword Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You accidentally inherited the Seven-Slaughtering Sword prior to joining the Taiyi Sect, which leaves you afraid of drawing too much attention as a result. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Seven-Slaughtering Sword[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1G1_4">
			<DisplayName>Heaven stealing Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You accidentally inherited the Heaven Stealing Law before joining the Taiyi Sect, which leaves you afraid of drawing too much attention as a result. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Heaven Stealing Law[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences1G1_5">
			<DisplayName>Emotion Severing Legacy</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You accidentally inherited the Emotion Severing Law before joining the Taiyi Sect, which leaves you afraid of drawing too much attention as a result. \n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Emotion Severing Law[/color]\nThe start of this Law can be difficult. Not recommended for first-time players.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences23">
			<DisplayName>Artifact Savior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of the attack, the artifact room was breached. You couldn't bear to see such rarities get looted, and so you risked your life to save a few. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial Resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Artifacts[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences24">
			<DisplayName>Elixir Savior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of the attack, the elixir room was breached. You couldn't bear to see such rarities get looted, and so you risked your life to save a few. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Elixirs[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences25">
			<DisplayName>Manual Savior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of the attack, the manual room was breached. You couldn't bear to see such rarities get looted, and so you risked your life to save a few. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Manuals[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences26">
			<DisplayName>Talisman Savior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of the attack, the talisman room was breached. You couldn't bear to see such rarities get looted, and so you risked your life to save a few. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Talismans[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences31">
			<DisplayName>Loner</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you became utterly dedicated to the practice, unwilling to spend time socializing with others. On the night of the attack, nobody was interested in following you, and so you escaped alone. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] reduced by 2.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences27">
			<DisplayName>Reticent</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you paid little mind to networking, as you knew that practicing the basics is of the greatest importance. On the night of the attack, you escaped with just one friend. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] reduced by 1.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences29">
			<DisplayName>Sociable</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you went on to meet many like-minded friends. On the night of the attack, they all escaped alongside you. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] increased by 1.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences30">
			<DisplayName>Leadership</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you spent a lot of time bringing your fellow outer disciples together, and gained a great reputation among them. On the night of the attack, they all escaped alongside you. \n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] increased by 2.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences7">
			<DisplayName>Hedonism</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You view cultivation as a means by which to gain more pleasure in life. As such, having joined the Taiyi Sect you would often exploit your position as an immortal's disciple to have fun beyond the sect. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Charisma [/color]increased. \n[color=#D06508]Social [/color]skills increased. \nInitial gears added: [color=#D06508]Clothes and Accessories[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences8">
			<DisplayName>Spare Food</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you were trapped within a magic seal for a month while out adventuring. Having felt the agony of extreme hunger in the past, you learned to always bring enough food with you. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Constitution [/color]increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]resources of food and drinks[/color] substantially increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Fasting Pill[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences9">
			<DisplayName>Builder</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you were given the responsiblity of building the sect's outer disciples' areas. Your job required that you carry all kinds of resources with you, and work in different places around the sect. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Perception [/color]increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]building resources[/color] substantially increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Materials[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences10">
			<DisplayName>Manual Guard</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you were made responsible for the security of the Manual Pavilion. You took the opportunity to transcribe and record some of the Novice Manuals for future reference. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Intelligence [/color]increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Manuals: Collection of Basic Talismans, Introduction to Elixirs[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences11">
			<DisplayName>Swordsman</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you acquired a famous sword while out on an adventure. You kept it with you at all times, hoping to one day craft it into an artifact. As such, you would often ask the senior disciples questions relating to the various methods of artifact mastery. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Artifact Mastery [/color]skill increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Weapon (Sword)[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences12">
			<DisplayName>Enchanted</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you often borrowed tomes on spells from the Manual Pavilion. Once while perusing such a book, a light emanated from within its pages, and shot deep into your mind. Ever since that day, you have shown a special talent for spells. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Spell [/color]skills increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]Spell Power [/color]increased.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences13">
			<DisplayName>Ironclad</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you once ate a strange fruit while out on an adventure. A senior lecturer conducted an examination, and concluded that the fruit actually improved your Qi and Meridians. It resulted in an increase in your Protection Qi. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Protection [/color]skills increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]Qi Barrier Power[/color] increased.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences14">
			<DisplayName>Student of Elixirs</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you were assigned to work in the elixir room. You carried all kinds of medicines to aid the senior cultivators in practicing alchemy. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Healing [/color]skills increased. \n[color=#D06508]Magic Crafting [/color]skills increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]medicinal resources[/color] substantially increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Medicine[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Experiences15">
			<DisplayName>Student of Artifacts</DisplayName>
			<Desc>Having joined the Taiyi Sect, you were assigned to work in the artifact room. You carried all kinds of resources to aid the senior cultivators in crafting artifacts. \n\n\n[size=10][color=#D06508]Crafting [/color]skills increased. \n[color=#D06508]Magic Crafting [/color]skills increased. \nInitial [color=#D06508]material resources[/color] substantially increased. \nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Materials[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>