<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences0">
			<DisplayName>Intelligent Beast</DisplayName>
			<Desc>You used to be just a wild beast living in the mountain of Taiyi Sect. Illuminated by the Qi of Earthly Paradise for many days and nights, you had gradually become sentient. On the night of destruction, the threat of life and death forced you to spontaneously crossed the final boundary and halfly shapeshifted into a demon beast.\n Out of gratitude towards Taiyi Sect as well as instincts, for all your life you had been a beneficiary in their shelter, you launched a final charge towards the invaders. Yet by the grace of fortune, your suicidal attempt was captured by the eyes of a dying Taiyi elder.\n Craving for hope, this elder gathered strength and passed on to you through magic a lot of memories and supplies originally intended for his disciple to use for escape, and temporarily implanted the idea of fleeing into your brain. Driven by this infused conviction, you ran for your life and managed to escape Taiyi Sect.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences1">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of Sixteen-steps</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was from Sixteen-steps School, thus among the memories that were passed on to you there is the Sixteen Supreme Steps Law, which is one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Sixteen Supreme Steps Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Constitution, Mediocre Charisma, Mediocre Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences2">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of Plough</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was from Plough School, thus among the memories that were passed on to you there is the Grand Chariot Wisdom Law, which is one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Grand Chariot Wisdom Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Perception, Mediocre Constitution, Mediocre Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences3">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of Reincarnation</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was from Reincarnation School, thus among the memories that were passed on to you there is the Six Paths Reincarnation Law, which is one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Six Paths Reincarnation Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: Mediocre Constitution, High Perception, High Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences4">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of True Sun</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was from True Sun School, thus among the memories that were passed on to you there is the True Sun Refining Law, which is one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]True Sun Refining Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: Mediocre Perception, Mediocre Constitution, Mediocre Charisma, Mediocre Intelligence, Mediocre Luck.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences5">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of Sunflower</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was from Sunflower School, thus among the memories that were passed on to you there is the Sunflower Refining Law, which is one of the true Laws of the Taiyi Sect.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Sunflower Refining Law[/color]\nRequired Stats: High Perception, High Charisma, High Intelligence.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences6">
			<DisplayName>Legacy of Body Refinement</DisplayName>
			<Desc>The dying Taiyi Sect elder was proficient in all kinds of ancient legacies. Thus upon seeing you waken up a intelligent beast, the elder included the contents of Primordial Unity Body among the memories that were passed on to you, which is an ancient Law of body refinement.\n\n\n[size=10]Unlock Law: [color=#D06508]Primordial Unity Body[/color]\nThis Law is extremely hard in early stages, not recommended for beginners.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences23">
			<DisplayName>Luck with Artifact Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, you passed by the Artifact Room on the way to escape. Influenced by the memories you were infused with, you instinctively felt that there was something important in there. So you risked your life to infiltrate inside and took a few invaluable artifacts away with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Artifact[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences24">
			<DisplayName>Luck with Elixir Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, you passed by the Elixir Room on the way to escape. Influenced by the memories you were infused with, you instinctively felt that there was something important in there. So you risked your life to infiltrate inside and took a few invaluable bottles of elixirs away with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Elixir[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences25">
			<DisplayName>Luck with Manual Pavilion</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, you passed by the Manual Pavilion on the way to escape. Influenced by the memories you were infused with, you instinctively felt that there was something important in there. So you risked your life to infiltrate inside and took a few invaluable manuals away with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Manual[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences26">
			<DisplayName>Luck with Talisman Room</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, you passed by the Talisman Room on the way to escape. Influenced by the memories you were infused with, you instinctively felt that there was something important in there. So you risked your life to infiltrate inside and took a few invaluable talismans away with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Advanced Talisman[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences31">
			<DisplayName>Determined Fugitive</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, you concentrated on the matter of escape and tried hard to avoid any living beings. Eventually, you escaped Taiyi alone.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] reduced by 2![/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences27">
			<DisplayName>Circumstantial Fellowship</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, having inherited the memories of an elder and considering yourself a Taiyi disciple, you escaped from danger and came across a fellow disciple who was lying on the ground unconscious. You decided to take him with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] reduced by 1![/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences29">
			<DisplayName>Good Samaritan</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, having inherited the memories of an elder and considering yourself a Taiyi disciple, you escaped from danger and came across one after another fellow disciples lying on the ground unconscious. You decided to take them with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] increased by 1![/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences30">
			<DisplayName>Determined Savior</DisplayName>
			<Desc>On the night of destruction, having inherited the memories of an elder and considering yourself a Taiyi disciple, you escaped from danger and came across several fellow disciples lying on the ground unconscious. You decided to take them all with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]disciples[/color] increased by 2![/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences8">
			<DisplayName>Food Storage</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, driven by animal instincts, you collected a large amount of food along the road as reserve, even killing several snakes and a bear over it. \n\n\nInitial[color=#D06508]\nInitial [color=#D06508]resources of food and drinks[/color] substantially increased.[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences9">
			<DisplayName>Beastly Instinct</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, you used what remains of your keen animal instincts and managed to collect lots of good stuffs in the area surrounding the battlefield.\n\n\nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Treasure[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences11">
			<DisplayName>Spiritual Congeniality</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, perhaps due to having sensing your primordial and pure spirit, an Panacea Pill that had been hiding the fact that it became sentient went into your arms willingly, fleeing the place of death with you.\n\n\n[size=10]Receive 1 [color=#D06508]Sentient Panacea Pill[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences14">
			<DisplayName>Elixir Relics</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, you came across another disciple from the Elixir Room who also escaped but failed to survive due to the his grave injury. With teary eyes, you collected the relics he left behind.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]medicinal resources[/color] substantially increased.\nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Medicine[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences15">
			<DisplayName>Artifact Relics</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, you came across another disciple from the Artifact Room who also escaped but failed to survive due to the his grave injury. With teary eyes, you collected the relics he left behind.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]material resources[/color] substantially increased.\nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Materials[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences16">
			<DisplayName>Foreign Relics</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, you came across another disciple from the Foreign Affairs Hall who also escaped but failed to survive due to the his grave injury. With teary eyes, you collected the relics he left behind.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial [color=#D06508]construction resources[/color] substantially increased.\nInitial resources added: [color=#D06508]Rare Materials[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="YaoGuai_Experiences17">
			<DisplayName>Manual Relics</DisplayName>
			<Desc>During the escape, you came across another disciple from the Manual Pavilion who also escaped but failed to survive due to the his grave injury. With teary eyes, you collected the relics he left behind.\n\n\n[size=10]Initial resources added: [color=#D06508]Collection of Basic Talismans, Introduction to Elixirs[/color].[/size]</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>